<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
Clue: Supernova generate lots of heat

	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Here is the last shipment of ore from <![CDATA[<color=orange>mining site 2b,</color>]]> Root!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: You have my gratitude, Cycad! We are truly sorry to have troubled you with so many shuttle trips for this delivery.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Worry not, my friend. I do not mind traveling by shuttle! In fact, if I had not traveled here by shuttle, I might have missed something rather curious..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: During my many journeys here in the shuttle, I could not help but notice a station in orbit around <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hollow's Lantern!</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: If I had not traveled by shuttle, I would surely have missed this discovery! Might you have any idea what this structure is, Root?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: Around <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hollow's Lantern?</color>]]> Ah! You must have caught a glimpse of the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Quantum Weather Lab,</color>]]> Cycad!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Caught a glimpse? Does that mean the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Quantum Weather Lab</color>]]> exists in quantum superposition around <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hollow's Lantern?</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: No, my friend! The <![CDATA[<color=orange>Quantum Weather Lab</color>]]> is named as such, because it was built to study how meteors launched from <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hollow's Lantern</color>]]> are affected as the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Quantum Moon</color>]]> orbits <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow.</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: The station is difficult to glimpse due to its artificial, stationary orbit around <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hollow's Lantern</color>]]> - which causes it to often be cloaked in shadow behind <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hollow's Lantern,</color>]]> or <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow.</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	
<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: How intriguing.. I must visit this <![CDATA[<color=orange>Quantum Weather Lab</color>]]> to learn more if I get the chance!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LV R3</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>