<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
Clue: Supernova generate lots of heat

	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Here is the additional shipment of ore you requested from <![CDATA[<color=orange>mining site 2b,</color>]]> Root!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: You have our gratitude, Cycad. We are truly sorry to have troubled you with this last, unforeseen delivery!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: It is no trouble, friend.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: However, we are curious why the Volcanic Testing Site needed so much more ore suddenly!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: (To be specific, Coleus wished to inquire, so that we may have an estimate if any additional ore is needed.)
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: Ah, that would be for the construction of the new <![CDATA[<color=orange>Quantum Weather Lab,</color>]]> Cycad. You may have caught a glimpse of it on your way to <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hollow's Lantern!</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Caught a glimpse? Does this <![CDATA[<color=orange>Quantum Weather Lab</color>]]> exist in quantum superposition around <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hollow's Lantern?</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: No, no, my friend! The <![CDATA[<color=orange>Quantum Weather Lab</color>]]> was given its name, because it was built to study how meteors launched from <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hollow's Lantern</color>]]> are affected as the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Quantum Moon</color>]]> orbits <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow.</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: Due to its artificial, stationary orbit around <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hollow's Lantern,</color>]]> it is often cloaked in shadow behind <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hollow's Lantern</color>]]> or <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow,</color>]]> thus making it difficult to see normally.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: We will be using this ore to build a protective shell that will protect the station's interior from meteor impacts, which it will doubtless need to weather often.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: What an exciting project! I look forward to visiting this <![CDATA[<color=orange>Quantum Weather Lab</color>]]> to learn more once its construction is complete, my friend.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	

<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LV R3</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>