<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
Clue: Supernova generate lots of heat

	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		ROOT: Goodness! Why have you delivered such a large chunk of ice to our <![CDATA[<color=orange>Volcanic Testing Site</color>]]> today, Clary? I am surprised it has not already melted in this heat!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: Isn't it marvelous? This spherical chunk of ice was taken from an asteroid belt far outside the star system for sample testing.. I brought it back to study its properties further!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: Formed in the cold depths outside the star system, it seems to have a much higher melting point than ordinary ice.. though of course, it does not compare to the ore we are testing!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: I brought it today because I thought it would be perfect to seal aboard the <![CDATA[<color=orange>diving bell</color>]]> for our final test of the ore's durability today!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: A wise idea, Clary! With the ice stored within it, we should be able to easily tell if the <![CDATA[<color=orange>diving bell's</color>]]> protective shell was able to adequately insulate heat from its interior.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: Now, let us seal the <![CDATA[<color=orange>diving bell</color>]]> completely, before we lower it into the lava pool's deepest point!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: Afterwards, we shall raise it and let it cool - before finally penetrating the protective shell to reveal the results of this test.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LV R3</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>