<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
Clue: Supernova generate lots of heat

	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CLARY: Friends, the lava diving bell has returned from its journey into the lava pool's deepest point.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: I am ecstatic to report that the interior shell was indeed completely insulated from the intense heat at the bottom of the lava pool! The lava diving bell has proved our theories correct!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PYE: How impressive, Clary! According to the measurements, the lava diving bell has withstood temperatures comparable to that of a supernova at the deepest point of the lava pool!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PYE: Now, we can be confident that a protective shell built from this ore will be capable of insulating both the Ash Twin Project, and any lifeforms sheltered within the Sanctuary.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: It brings me great relief to know any sentient lifeforms sheltered within the Sanctuary during the operation of the Ash Twin Project will be spared of any harrowing experiences, even those in theory.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: But, Pye.. How will we transports lifeforms into the Sanctuary?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: I have heard that this structure will not be accessible by warp to save on resources, and that we will be accessing it using Daz's new invention. But how will anything physically enter the Sanctuary, in that case?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PYE: Worry not, my friend. Our friends on Timber Hearth have found a quantum shard on the planet that travels between the surface of the planet and an underground cave.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PYE: If the Sanctuary is built around this underground cave, we should be able to transport both external materials and the lifeforms into the structure using this quantum shard!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	

<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LV EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LV EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>6</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LV EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>7</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>