<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
Clue: Supernova generate lots of heat

	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		ROOT: Friends, it brings me great pride to share that the last shipment of ore has been fully processed by the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Lava Diving Bell!</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: I am relieved to end our intrusion on the native life of <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Timber Hearth,</color>]]> now that we have all the ore necessary to fortify all critical structures from the supernova.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		POKE: Root, are you sure we cannot at least prepare a small surplus of this ore - if only for cerebral peace?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		POKE: We should insulate as much as we are able to with this wondrous ore, to ensure that as many structures and systems continue to operate during the supernova..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		POKE: For instance: the memory statues that allow Nomai to be paired to the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project</color>]]> are not insulated from the supernova.. When the supernova destroys them, won't this connection be broken?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: Your concerns are wisely placed, Poke.. But fear not: the system is not so fragile!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: If a memory statue is destroyed, the paired individual will only be unable to recall memories beyond that point, as their experiences are no longer being recorded by the memory statue to the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project.</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: However, as the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project</color>]]> remains connected to any individuals once paired, the temporary destruction of the memory statues is not a concern.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		POKE: That sounds reassuring.. but also quite disturbing!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<Text>
		POKE: Suppose something catastrophic were to occur only after our memory statues are destroyed... None of us would be aware of that impending danger!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: The memory statues won't be destroyed by the supernova simultaneously, Poke!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>12</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>11</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: As they have been placed on different planets, the memory statues will only be destroyed as each planet is engulfed by the supernova - giving us ample time to notice anything amiss in that scenario.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>13</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>12</ParentID>
		<Text>
		POKE: But suppose something catastrophic occurs only after that!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>14</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>13</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: Then I suppose it would be quite exciting to find out about it, my friend!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	

<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LV EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LV EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>6</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LV EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>7</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>