<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PLUME: My friends, after much debate, we have decided we must abandon this tower.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: The interior of this dwelling has rapidly taken on a quantum nature after prolonged exposure to the quantum shard. As much as it pains me, I believe we must relocate to one of the planet's outer islands.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PLUME: Does anyone have any proposals for which island we should relocate our settlement to?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: The island we arrived on our first expedition would be a good choice. The height of that island's cliffs offers the most protection from the ocean's waves!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		THATCH: I believe one of the other islands would be suitable site to build a construction site as well.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		THATCH: Of note: there appears to be a smaller quantum shard that travels across each of the planet's outer islands. This is troubling, if this shard may invade our settlement as this tower was invaded..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>	
	<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: An update: thankfully, it appears that this smaller shard has a much smaller sphere of influence. This means it should be safe to settle on these islands without worry that they will become quantum as well!
		</Text>
			</TextBlock>



	<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC R4</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC EX4.5</FactID>
			<Condition>6</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>