<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	

	<![CDATA[<i>Excavation Site</i>]]>
	

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>
			COLEUS: The <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Quantum Moon</color>]]> was orbiting <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Giant's Deep!</color>]]> Phlox wins the jellyfish game again!</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			PLUME: Yay! I won, I won!</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			PHLOX: What? I do not believe this.. Even with a set of eyes outside the planet, your guesses are too consistently precise, my son!</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		MELORAE: I am unsure what are the rules of this game, but it is quite entertaining! How does one play this jellyfish game?
			</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
			COLEUS: The rules are simple, Melorae: whoever guesses the planet the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Quantum Moon</color>]]> is currently orbiting, wins!</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		MELORAE: Oh, how delightful! Is this game named after how jellyfish are drawn to the ocean's surface by the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Quantum Moon's</color>]]> gravity? If so, what a wonderful way to incorporate our research into this game!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		MELORAE: But in that case, to have won so many games in succession.. Did you perhaps leave a set of eyes at the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Quantum Moon Locator!</color>]]> Phlox?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: Ah, I should have known! Nobody could know where the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Quantum Moon</color>]]> is so consistently without a set of eyes at the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Quantum Moon Locator!</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: Haha, I knew papa would figure it out eventually! You're the smartest, papa!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LCJ EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LCJ EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>7</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LCJ EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>9</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			

</ShipLogConditions>


</NomaiObject>