<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		RAMIE: Is this the <![CDATA[<color=orange>relocation site</color>]]> you had in mind, Melorae?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		MELORAE: It is! I believe this location would be much more favorable for harnessing energy during sunless days.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		MELORAE: Once the relocation is complete, we will no longer need to worry about <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Ash Twin's</color>]]> shadow regularly depriving us of energy!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		RAMIE: And the <![CDATA[<color=orange>High Energy Lab</color>]]> will be free from accusations of rerouting the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sunless City's</color>]]> energy without warning!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		MELORAE: I apologize for my accusations, Ramie.. But surely you must understand the difficulty in discerning between a sunless day, and the <![CDATA[<color=orange>High Energy Lab's</color>]]> experiments leaving the city in the dark!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		RAMIE: I must disagree, Melorae.. Surely it cannot be so difficult to tell when a solar eclipse is occurring.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		MELORAE: Ramie, my friend: Recall that the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sunless City</color>]]> is located underground. We are not so easily able to detect a solar eclipse!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		RAMIE: That.. may be true. But in that case, may I suggest leaving a set of eyes on the planet's surface?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		RAMIE: A set of eyes on the surface would allow one to detect the presence of a sunless day even while underground, would it not?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<Text>
		MELORAE: What a wise idea, Ramie! Perhaps you would like to be that set of eyes for us?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<Text>
		RAMIE: I must humbly decline your offer, my friend!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>R_SLR EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>R_SLR EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>6</Condition>
		</RevealFact>	
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>R_SLR EX4</FactID>
			<Condition>9</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>