<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		MELORAE: Friends, Coleus and I shall be departing for our expedition with our friends on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow</color>]]> soon. Please wish us both well!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: I cannot wait, Melorae! Have our friends on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow</color>]]> decided which planet we shall be exploring first?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		MELORAE: They have. We shall be traveling to the stormy planet with them, while another group explores the forested planet. Oh, how excited I am!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: You seem particularly pleased about this arrangement, Melorae. I am excited too, of course - but what about this stormy planet brings you such excitement?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		MELORAE: Our friends have reported that the planet's clouds are so immensely thick, we are unable to probe its hidden interior... Doesn't that fill you with intrigue, Coleus?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: A little, I suppose.. But it fills me with greater terror! We have no way of knowing what awaits us once we penetrate those thick clouds!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		MELORAE: Come now, Coleus.. Look on the sunward side: it also means enjoying a stay on a planet dark, cool and far from the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>sun's</color>]]> dreadful heat!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: Hah, so that was the true source of your glee! Indeed, it shall be a pleasure to depart this scorching planet at last..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: I cannot wait to learn what knowledge this stormy planet will share with us!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	

</NomaiObject>