<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		YARROW: The bramble seems capable of receding and entering a dormant state to protect itself in inhospitable conditions.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: 
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		OENO: As the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hourglass Twins</color>]]> orbit around each other, they become aligned along a straight line with the sun at regular intervals, causing a sunless day on the twin farther from the sun.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: The twin farther from the sun feels not only the sun's great gravity - but also gravity from the twin closer to the sun, pulling it in the same direction.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: These combined gravitational forces cause an extraordinarily strong pull of gravity that pulls on anything in its path, including the vision orbs powering the doors.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: The sunless day is also what causes sand to be pulled towards the other twin at the alignment point, creating the striking funnel of sand between the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hourglass Twins.</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: What an enlightening report, Oeno! Now that we know the issue, we will know how to amend it in the future. You have my gratitude for your hard work.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: Though the Hourglass Twins feel a pull of gravity from each other, this force alone should not be enough to cause vision orbs to activate.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SS Tower EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SS Tower EX2.5</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SS Tower EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SS Tower EX4</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SS Tower EX5</FactID>
			<Condition>6</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>