<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	Clue: There is another QM locator on BH and you can learn to use the rule of imaging from afar there?

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		SOLANUM: Ilex, I apologize for the wait! I did not think you would reach <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Ember Twin</color>]]> so quickly.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ILEX: Of course! I did not wish to risk being late for your pilgrimage today, my friend.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		ILEX: Still, I believe I could have simply visited the new <![CDATA[<color=orange>Quantum Moon Locator</color>]]> on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow</color>]]> to support your pilgrimage.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		SOLANUM: Wait.. There was a second <![CDATA[<color=orange>Quantum Moon Locator</color>]]> built on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow?</color>]]> This is the first time I have heard of it!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ILEX: There is. I was curious why you did not use this newer locator - especially when it is able to track when the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Quantum Moon</color>]]> visits the sixth location, unlike this locator!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		SOLANUM: That sounds quite curious! I wonder why Bells never mentioned this locator to me.. Would it have made the pilgrimage too simple?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		SOLANUM: I shall be returning to <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow</color>]]> shortly to begin my expedition.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		SOLANUM: If time allows, I shall try to find this second <![CDATA[<color=orange>Quantum Moon Locator</color>]]> on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow</color>]]> to learn its secrets!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>BH_QML R1</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>R_SLR R3</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>BH_QML R3</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>