<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	Clue should be guiding players towards rotating doors on warp towers activating on their own
	Actors should be
	Context should be Pye visiting the solar tower crew? One of the members warping from TH notices?
	
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		CLARY: Yarrow, the column of sand is roaming <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Ash Twin</color>]]> right now!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: I worry for your safety.. You should cease construction of the <![CDATA[<color=orange>solar tower</color>]]> until it subsides!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		YARROW: Worry not, Clary! As the column of sand only ever travels along the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hourglass Twins'</color>]]> equator, we are safe here on the planet's poles.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: Still, your concern is deeply appreciated, my friend.. It is heartwarming that you came all this way to warn me!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: Oh? I had not noticed that the column of sand only roamed along the equator before you mentioned it!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: There are so many things I do not understand about this strange flow of sand between the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hourglass Twins.</color>]]> What could even cause such a phenomenon?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: Ah, I did not realize you were unaware of the cause of the sand transfer, Clary! I would be happy to explain the phenomenon known as the sunless day to you.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: Though, it may be a difficult concept to explain without some demonstration... Ah, I know.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: There is a station in orbit around the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hourglass Twins</color>]]> called the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Hourglass Observatory.</color>]]> If you accompany me there, I could more clearly explain the mechanisms behind the sand transfer there!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: I'd be thrilled if you would explain this phenomenon to me, Yarrow! However, there is some work I need to tend to first.. Where should I meet you once I am ready?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<Text>
			YARROW: I understand. Let us meet at the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Hourglass Observatory's</color>]]> warp tower on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Ember Twin's</color>]]> equator when you are ready then!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>12</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>11</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: You have my gratitude, Yarrow. I look forward to visiting the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Hourglass Observatory</color>]]> together with you!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SLR_T EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SLR_T EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>