<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	Clue should be guiding players towards rotating doors on warp towers activating on their own
	Actors should be
	Context should be Pye visiting the solar tower crew? One of the members warping from TH notices?
	
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		BUR: Yarrow, I may need an extended rest soon. I fear this terrible heat is affecting my mind..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: What!? Bur, do you require medical assistance? Are you physically unwell?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		BUR: No, I am physically well.. However, when I was resting in one of the towers along the equator earlier, I saw the tower's rotating doors opening and closing by themselves!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		BUR: I decided to seek shelter in a different tower, but I saw the same thing occurring there too!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		BUR: I am not one for superstition, but there was no one nearby when this incident occurred.. Either these doors are aberrant, or my brain must be!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: How strange! I am sure it must be some sort of defect in these towers' rotating doors.. I shall seek Oeno's assistance in investigating this issue when I return.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: But first: allow me to accompany you home to seek aid, Bur!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	
<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SLR_T EX0</FactID>
			<Condition>6</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SLR_T EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>