<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	Clue should be guiding players towards rotating doors on warp towers activating on their own
	Actors should be
	Context should be Pye visiting the solar tower crew? One of the members warping from TH notices?
	
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		CLARY: Yarrow, the sand column is roaming <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Ash Twin</color>]]> right now! I worry for your safety.. You should cease construction of the <![CDATA[<color=orange>solar tower</color>]]> for now!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: It is alright, Clary! The sand column does not travel over the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hourglass Twins'</color>]]> poles.. We are safe here.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		CLARY: Oh.. That is a relief to hear. How fortunate I am able to learn so much about the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hourglass Twins</color>]]> from you, Yarrow!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: But even after all this time, I am still not sure what causes this strange flow of sand between the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hourglass Twins.</color>]]> What could cause such a phenomenon?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: Oh? I would love to explain the cause of the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hourglass Twins'</color>]]> sandflow to you, Clary!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: There is a station in orbit around the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hourglass Twins</color>]]> called the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Hourglass Observatory..</color>]]> If you accompany me there, I'd be happy to explain the mechanisms behind the sand transfer to you!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: I'd be thrilled to visit this <![CDATA[<color=orange>Hourglass Observatory</color>]]> with you, Yarrow! But I need to return to <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow</color>]]> briefly first. Where should I meet you when I am ready?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: I understand. When you wish to visit the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Hourglass Observatory,</color>]]> I shall be waiting for you at the warp tower on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Ember Twin's</color>]]> equator, Clary.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: You have my gratitude, Yarrow. I look forward to this journey with you!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SLR_T EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SLR_T EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>