<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	Clue: There is another QM locator on BH and you can learn to use the rule of imaging from afar there?

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		BELLS: Friends, what incredible devices you have constructed in our separation... To think you have built a device capable of tracking the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Quantum Moon's</color>]]> precise location at all times!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ANNONA: I am pleased you were able to gleam the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Quantum Moon Locator's</color>]]> purpose so clearly! It is heartwarming to be able to share all the things we have built and done in our time apart after the crash, my friends.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		ANNONA: The artificial gravity technology developed on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow</color>]]> is particularly impressive.. I eagerly await the day Nomai on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Ember Twin</color>]]> will be able to visit you by a shuttle of our own.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		BELLS: An update: Annona, I only just noticed this locator only tracks five of the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Quantum Moon's</color>]]> orbits around the star system.. Why is that?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ANNONA: We have theorized the existence of a sixth location, but we have not yet been able to confirm this hypothesis - let alone track this hypothetical orbit. Have the Nomai on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow</color>]]> already found a method to do so?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		BELLS: I am unsure how it functions exactly, but.. I am fairly sure the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Quantum Moon Locator on Brittle Hollow</color>]]> is able to track the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Quantum Moon,</color>]]> even when it visits the sixth location!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ANNONA: How intriguing.. Bells, would you mind guiding me to this <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sixth Location Locator</color>]]> on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow</color>]]> sometime? I would be quite keen to learn more about it.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ANNONA: Though it would be thrilling to explore <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow</color>]]> on my own, I would prefer not to become lost searching for this <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sixth Location Locator!</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		BELLS: Of course! It would be my honor, my old friend.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>BH_QML R1</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>R_SLR R3</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>BH_QML R3</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>BH_QML R2</FactID>
			<Condition>8</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>