<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Friends, I have delivered two new memory statues aboard the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Quantum Weather Lab!</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>	

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PRIVET: You have my thanks, Cycad. I am impressed by Phlox's speed in sculpting these new statues!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PRIVET: With the help of these statues, we should be able to pair to the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Deep Storm Station</color>]]> to begin studying the negative time interval.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: I have heard about the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Deep Storm Station,</color>]]> but why would being paired to it allow one to study the negative time interval, Privet?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PRIVET: It is quite simple! The <![CDATA[<color=orange>Deep Storm Station</color>]]> powers a 6-second negative time interval using energy from <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Giant's Deep's</color>]]> electric core.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PRIVET: We have been using this shorter interval to test the mechanisms of a negative time interval.. It was during one such interval that Spire discovered the discrepancy we are studying here!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: I see.. What a wise plan! This shorter interval will allow us to ensure the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project</color>]]> is theoretically sound before its operation.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: I must return to <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Giant's Deep</color>]]> shortly.. I shall look forward to visiting the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Deep Storm Station</color>]]> while there!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Workshop R3</FactID>
			<Condition>8</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>