<DialogueTree xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/dialogue_schema.xsd">

	<NameField>Chert</NameField>



	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Questions</Name>
			
		<DialogueOptionsList>
		<DialogueOption>
		<RequiredPersistentCondition>Mica_Chert</RequiredPersistentCondition>
				<Text>I heard you delayed your launch date several times! Why’s that?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>Chert SW1</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Chert SW1</Name>
			<Dialogue>
				<Page>Ah, I’m guessing you heard about this from Mica?</Page>
				<Page>I hope you didn’t take too long to take off - or they’ll be telling future space cadets about how you delayed your launch for generations to come, too!</Page>
				<Page>As I've told them many times.. The reason I delayed my launch date was because the Hourglass Twins' sand was flowing towards Ash Twin on the day I was setting off.</Page>
				<Page>Since I was planning to explore Ash Twin on my first trip, it'd have been silly to set off while it was being buried by oceans of sand.</Page>
				<Page>That’s why I opted to delay my launch, though more times than I'd have liked.. But surely I can't be blamed for that - I have no control over the universe's whims!</Page>		
				<Page>Still, it certainly sparked a lifelong curiosity about the Hourglass Twins. To this day, I can't help but wonder if there's more to the sand flowing back and forth than natural phenomenon.</Page>		
			</Dialogue>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
				<DialogueOption>
					<Text>The sand flows <![CDATA[<i>back</i>]]> to Ash Twin?</Text>
					<DialogueTarget>Chert SW2</DialogueTarget>
				</DialogueOption>
				<DialogueOption>
					<Text>What made you want to explore Ash Twin?</Text>
					<DialogueTarget>Chert SW3</DialogueTarget>
				</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Chert SW2</Name>
			<Dialogue>
				<Page>Well, have you seen the colossal towers of solar panels on each of the Ash Twin's poles? They are truly a magnificent sight to behold.</Page>
				<Page>I first noticed them while stargazing, and wished to visit Ash Twin to get a closer look at these wondrous structures.</Page>
				<Page>With solar panels of such scale, the Nomai must have been able to harness an incredible amount of energy with them! I highly recommend visiting them when you get a chance.</Page>
				<Page>Fantastic view aside: you might be able to glean more about them with that new translator tool of yours. I highly recommend visiting them when you get the chance!</Page>
				<Page>Oh, but do be careful! I believe my scout detected some ghost matter surrounding one of the towers during my visit. Be mindful if you visit that one.</Page>
				</Dialogue>
							<RevealFacts>
     						   <FactID>SLR_T R1</FactID>
    					  </RevealFacts>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
				<DialogueOption>
					<Text>I will, but tell me more about the Twins' shifting sands!</Text>
					<DialogueTarget>Chert SW3B</DialogueTarget>
				</DialogueOption>
				<DialogueOption>
					<Text>Will do!</Text>
					<DialogueTarget>Chert5</DialogueTarget>
				</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Chert SW3</Name>
			<Dialogue>
				<Page>Why, yes! Haven’t you noticed before?</Page>
				<Page>Right now, sand is flowing from Ash Twin to Ember Twin - but the process eventually reverses.</Page>
				<Page>In fact, if you wait, you should be able to see it beginning to flow back to Ash Twin!</Page>
				<Page>Even stranger, the process seems to happen in very precise and consistent intervals.. Flowing from one twin to the other, and back again after the same length of time.</Page>
				<Page>It's a mystery that has bothered me for quite some time!</Page>
				<Page>But until we can find more evidence to the contrary, all we can conclude is that it seems to be a very strange natural phenomenon.</Page>
			</Dialogue>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
				<DialogueOption>
					<Text>How long do you think it'd take for sand to start flowing back to Ash Twin again?</Text>
					<DialogueTarget>Chert SW3.5</DialogueTarget>
				</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>
<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Chert SW3B</Name>
			<Dialogue>
				<Page>Gladly!</Page>
				<Page>Right now, sand is flowing from Ash Twin to Ember Twin - but did you know the process eventually reverses?</Page>
				<Page>If you wait, you should be able to see it beginning to flow back to Ash Twin!</Page>
				<Page>Even stranger, the process seems to happen in very precise and consistent intervals.. Flowing from one twin to the other, and back again after the same length of time.</Page>
				<Page>It's a mystery that has bothered me for quite some time!</Page>
				<Page>But until we can find more evidence to the contrary, all we can conclude is that it seems to be a very strange natural phenomenon.</Page>
			</Dialogue>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
				<DialogueOption>
					<Text>How long do you think it'd take for sand to start flowing back to Ash Twin again?</Text>
					<DialogueTarget>Chert SW3.5</DialogueTarget>
				</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Chert SW3.5</Name>
		<SetCondition>Sandflow</SetCondition>
			<Dialogue>
				<Page>Hm... It will take a while longer, I believe.</Page>
				<Page>Come back once more of the sand has drained off from Ash Twin, and I might be able to give you a more precise answer then!</Page>
				<Page>If you’re feeling impatient, feel free to take a nap by a campfire to pass the time.</Page>
				<Page>I set up this camp here to avoid the sand column's path - so please, put away any worry about the sand column wandering this way while you rest.</Page>
			</Dialogue>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
				<DialogueOption>
					<Text>Cool, cool. Tell me about what you found on Ash Twin, though!</Text>
					<DialogueTarget>Chert SW2.5</DialogueTarget>
				</DialogueOption>
				<DialogueOption>
					<Text>Good to know! Thanks, Chert.</Text>
					<DialogueTarget>Chert5</DialogueTarget>
				</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Chert SW2.5</Name>
			<Dialogue>
			<Page>Goodness! That's right, that's what we were discussing at first, wasn't it? My apologies for rambling!</Page>
				<Page>Well, have you seen the colossal towers of solar panels on each of the Ash Twin's poles? They are truly a magnificent sight to behold.</Page>
				<Page>I first noticed them while stargazing, and wished to visit Ash Twin to get a closer look at these wondrous structures.</Page>
				<Page>With solar panels of such scale, the Nomai must have been able to harness an incredible amount of energy with them! I highly recommend visiting them when you get a chance.</Page>
				<Page>Fantastic view aside: you might be able to glean more about them with that new translator tool of yours! I highly recommend visiting them when you get the chance.</Page>
				<Page>Oh, but do be careful! I believe my scout detected some ghost matter surrounding one of the towers during my visit. Be mindful if you visit that one.</Page>
				</Dialogue>
							<RevealFacts>
     						   <FactID>SLR_T R1</FactID>
    					  </RevealFacts>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
				<DialogueOption>
					<Text>I will, but tell me more about the Twins' shifting sands!</Text>
					<DialogueTarget>Chert SW3B</DialogueTarget>
				</DialogueOption>
				<DialogueOption>
					<Text>Will do!</Text>
					<DialogueTarget>Chert5</DialogueTarget>
				</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>FoundSomethingMenu</Name>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
			<RequiredLogCondition>SS Tower EX5</RequiredLogCondition>
					<Text>I found out what causes the sand to flow between the twins.</Text>
					<DialogueTarget>ChertSW5</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>ChertSW5</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>How fascinating..</Page>
				<Page>So if I understand correctly.. Gravity from the sun and the twin closer to the sun cause a combined force that pulls sand to the other twin when the twins orbit into alignment?</Page>
				<Page>It sounds peculiar.. but it makes complete sense now that you've spelled it out!</Page>
				<Page>Surely, the gravitational centre of the solar system combining its pull with another planet would cause some interesting tidal effects. And you said the Nomai called this phenomenon the "sunless day"?</Page>
				<Page>Excellent work, hatchling. Solving a mystery that has puzzled me for ages on your first expedition is truly something else!</Page>
				<Page>After we gather more conclusive data on this phenomenon, we should mark your findings with a new exhibit in the village museum, then celebrate with some sap wine!</Page>
				</Dialogue>
</DialogueNode>

</DialogueTree>

