<DialogueTree xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/dialogue_schema.xsd">

	<NameField>Chert</NameField>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Chert3</Name>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
		<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Sounds good.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>Chert5</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Chert3.5</Name>
		<SetPersistentCondition>Chert_Natural</SetPersistentCondition>
		<Dialogue>
				<Page>Watch out for falling sand, okay? I’ve had to dig myself out once or twice, and that’s not half as fun as it sounds.</Page>
			</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Questions</Name>
			
		<DialogueOptionsList>
		<DialogueOption>
				<RequiredLogCondition>MICA EX2</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>Hey Chert, how did you know when the sand would start flowing between the Hourglass Twins again?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>Chert SW1</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<RequiredPersistentCondition>Sandflow</RequiredPersistentCondition>
				<Text>How much longer do you think it'd take for the sand to stop flowing between the Twins?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>Chert SW S</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Chert SW1</Name>
			<Dialogue>
				<Page>Oh? You heard about this from the village, I presume!</Page>
				<Page>The village always seems to be amazed when I tell them my predictions for the next sand transfer. It's a fun party trick, isn't it?</Page>
				<Page>But there's no magic to it - the Hourglass Twins' sand transfer simply occurs at very regular intervals.</Page>
				<Page>After spending some time studying this phenomenon, I have found that after each time the sandflow subsides, it takes a consistent, precise three weeks for the sand to flow back to the other twin again.</Page>
				<Page>That the process takes place with such consistency only makes it even more puzzling to me, though.. I simply can't think of any natural phenomenon that occurs with such precision!</Page>
				</Dialogue>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
				<DialogueOption>
					<Text>When do you think the sand will stop flowing between the Twins?</Text>
					<DialogueTarget>Chert SW4</DialogueTarget>
				</DialogueOption>
				<DialogueOption>
					<Text>What do you think even causes sand to flow between the Twins?</Text>
					<DialogueTarget>Chert5</DialogueTarget>
				</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Chert SW3</Name>
		<SetPersistentCondition>Chert_Natural</SetPersistentCondition>
			<Dialogue>
				<Page>Oh, how I wish I knew the answer to that question too, young hatchling.</Page>
				<Page>For sand to flow from one planet to the other.. then back to the other planet.. There is simply no rational explanation for it.</Page>
				<Page>The fact that the process takes place with such consistency only makes it even more puzzling to me. I cannot think of any natural phenomenon that occurs in this way, and with such precision!</Page>
				<Page>But still.. Until we find any evidence to the contrary, we can only conclude that it is some natural phenomenon we do not fully comprehend yet.</Page>
				<Page>If you plan on exploring the Twins in search of an answer to this mystery, I do have another detail about the sand column, and some accompanying advice to share with you!</Page>
				<Page>For whatever reason, the sand only drains from one Twin to the other, along the Hourglass Twins' equator.</Page>
				<Page>No matter how long I've stayed here, that great column of sand has never once wandered across this camp.</Page>
				<Page>To that end, I would suggest starting your exploration at the poles of the Hourglass Twins. That should keep you safe from being pulled into space by the sand column, or crushed by falling sand!</Page>
			</Dialogue>
						<RevealFacts>
     						   <FactID>R_SLR R4</FactID>
     						   <FactID>SLR_T R2</FactID>
    					  </RevealFacts>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
				<DialogueOption>
					<Text>Do you know when the sand will stop flowing between the Twins?</Text>
					<DialogueTarget>Chert SW4</DialogueTarget>
				</DialogueOption>
				<DialogueOption>
					<Text>That sounds wise! Thanks for the advice, Chert.</Text>
					<DialogueTarget>Chert5</DialogueTarget>
				</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Chert SW4</Name>
		<SetPersistentCondition>Sandflow</SetPersistentCondition>
			<Dialogue>
				<Page>It will take.. Ah, I'm.. not too sure, since I didn't keep track when this interval began..</Page>
				<Page>I am sure the sandflow does not last longer than 20 minutes, though. If you feel impatient, feel free to take a nap by a campfire to pass the time!</Page>
				<Page>Time slips by during a good nap, after all.</Page>
				<Page>I intentionally set up this camp to be out of the sand column's path - so please, rest easy about the possibility of the sand column wandering this way while you rest.</Page>
			</Dialogue>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
				<DialogueOption>
					<Text>What do you think even causes sand to flow between the Twins, though?</Text>
					<DialogueTarget>Chert SW2.5</DialogueTarget>
				</DialogueOption>
				<DialogueOption>
					<Text>Good to know! Thanks, Chert.</Text>
					<DialogueTarget>Chert5</DialogueTarget>
				</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>


	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>FoundSomethingMenu</Name>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
			<RequiredLogCondition>SS Tower EX5</RequiredLogCondition>
					<Text>I found out what causes the sand to flow between the twins.</Text>
					<DialogueTarget>ChertSW5</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>ChertSW5</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>How fascinating..</Page>
				<Page>So if I understand correctly.. Gravity from the sun and the twin closer to the sun cause a combined force that pulls sand to the other twin when the twins orbit into alignment?</Page>
				<Page>It sounds peculiar.. but it makes complete sense now that you've spelled it out!</Page>
				<Page>Surely, the gravitational centre of the solar system combining its pull with another planet would cause some interesting tidal effects. And you said the Nomai called this phenomenon the "sunless day"?</Page>
				<Page>Excellent work, hatchling. Solving a mystery that has puzzled me for ages on your first expedition is truly something else!</Page>
				<Page>After we gather more conclusive data on this phenomenon, we should mark your findings with a new exhibit in the village museum, then celebrate with some sap wine!</Page>
				</Dialogue>
</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Chert SW4</Name>
			<Dialogue>
				<Page>PLACEHOLDER FOR SHIPLOGS WHEN I MOVE THESE SHIPLOGS TO ANOTHER CLUE</Page>
			</Dialogue>
							<RevealFacts>
     						   <FactID>GD Tower R1.5</FactID>
    					  </RevealFacts>
						  <RevealFacts>
     						   <FactID>BH Tower R2</FactID>
    					  </RevealFacts>
						  <RevealFacts>
     						   <FactID>TH Tower R2</FactID>
    					  </RevealFacts>
						  <RevealFacts>
     						   <FactID>SS Tower R2</FactID>
    					  </RevealFacts> 
						  <RevealFacts>
     						   <FactID>HGT Tower R2</FactID>
    					  </RevealFacts>
	</DialogueNode>


</DialogueTree>

