<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	Clue should be guiding players towards rotating doors on warp towers activating on their own
	Actors should be
	Context should be Pye visiting the solar tower crew? One of the members warping from TH notices?
	
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		CLARY: Yarrow, the column of sand is roaming <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Ash Twin</color>]]> right now!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: I worry for your safety.. You should cease construction of the <![CDATA[<color=orange>solar tower</color>]]> until it subsides!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		YARROW: Worry not, Clary! The <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hourglass Twins'</color>]]> poles do not experience sunless days.. We are safe from the sand column here.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: Still, your concern is deeply appreciated, Clary. It is heartwarming that you came all this way to warn me about a sunless day!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: A sunless day..? Is that what causes sand to flow between the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hourglass Twins?</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: Oh, are you not aware what a sunless day is?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: I have never heard of this phenomenon! Would you kindly explain it to me, Yarrow?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: I would be happy to! Though, it may be a difficult concept to explain without some demonstration..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: Have you heard of the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Hourglass Observatory,</color>]]> Clary? It is a station in a stationary orbit behind the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hourglass Twins.</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: If you accompany me there, I could more clearly explain the mechanisms behind the sand transfer to you!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: I'd be thrilled if you would, Yarrow! However, there is some work I need to tend to first. Where should I meet you once I am ready?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>12</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>11</ParentID>
		<Text>
			YARROW: Let us meet at the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Hourglass Observatory's</color>]]> warp tower on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Ember Twin's</color>]]> equator when you are ready!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>13</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>12</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: You have my gratitude, Yarrow. I look forward to visiting the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Hourglass Observatory</color>]]> together with you!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SLR_T EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SLR_T EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>