<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		OENO: Daz, the construction of the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary</color>]]> has been going swimmingly thanks to your help! Your new voyager stones are truly a revolutionary piece of technology.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		OENO: However, during our time voyaging, I encountered some.. strange occurrences which I would like to inquire about.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		OENO: To start, working in shifts with Coleus, voyaging into the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary</color>]]> seemed to always transport me some distance outside of the projection pool.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		OENO: In the dark, this has caused me to stumble off the tiny island more times than I wish to admit! Is this an intended feature, or some strange quirk of the voyager stone?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		OENO: More distressingly: at some point, I began to hear.. <![CDATA[<i>thoughts that were not my own.</i>]]> It was like there was another person in my mind while I was voyaging!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		OENO: Assuming my mind has not become aberrant, I understand the voyager stones work using the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project's</color>]]> memory storage systems.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		OENO: Coleus posits perhaps there was some sort of mix-up between our memory masks from using the same voyager stone, but he had no such experience himself while voyaging.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		OENO: Coleus insisted I rest while he continued to work, so I decided to visit your workshop today to ask about these experiences. I would deeply appreciate if you could investigate their causes, Daz!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Workshop EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Workshop EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>