<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: Oeno, I have seen your scroll detailing the issues you encountered in your time using the voyager stones. (My thanks once again for helping to test this new technology!)
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: To start: your first observation is indeed an intended feature! The memory storage systems allow one voyager (per mask) to remain on standby when disconnected, returning them to that exact position when reconnected.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: This was done to facilitate a quick return to voyages far from the projection pool the voyage originally travels to!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: However: it appears this system currently fails to discriminate between the original host and any new users when a second Nomai voyages to the same destination, from the same projection pool.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		DAZ: As a result, any Nomai voyaging under these circumstances will be connected to any previous Nomai's outstanding voyagers, causing them to inherit its location.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: Furthermore, as the voyager stones use a paired Nomai's memory mask to allow them to receive transmissions from the voyager...
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: Voyaging to the same destination from the same projection pool causes connection to any standby voyagers connected to another memory mask, causing both memory masks to share the voyage.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	
<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>		
			OENO: I see! That must be why Coleus and I received visions from each other's voyages.. My deepest gratitude for your quick work in diagnosing these issues, Daz!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
			OENO: In this case: until these issues can be amended, we shall simply be mindful of disposing of our voyagers, so we may avoid unwittingly sharing our voyages with each other!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Workshop EX4</FactID>
			<Condition>2</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Workshop EX5</FactID>
			<Condition>7</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>