<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		OENO: Daz, your new voyager stones are truly revolutionary. The construction of the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary</color>]]> has already progressed swiftly thanks to you!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		OENO: However, after spending much time working with them, Coleus and I believe we may have already found a few quirks with the technology we require you to look into.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		OENO: To start: while working in shifts with Coleus, I noticed my voyage consistently beginning some distance outside of the projection pool. (Coleus corroborated this issue during his shifts too!)
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		OENO: In the dark, this has caused me to stumble off the tiny island more times than I wish to admit! Is this an intended feature of the voyager stone?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		OENO: More alarmingly: during Coleus' shift, as he used the voyager stone, I began to receive memories from his voyage, and even heard his thoughts! it was as if we had some sort of telepathic connection!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		OENO: I understand the voyager stones function using the memory storage system crafted for the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project.</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		OENO: Could there perhaps have been some sort of mix-up between our memory masks, caused by us sharing the same voyager stone?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		OENO: We have decided to pause our work with the voyager stones until these issues can be amended. We would deeply appreciate if you could investigate them soon, Daz!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Workshop EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>7</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>