<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange> we are clowns in a circus </color>]]>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: Oeno, I saw your scroll today regarding the issues you and Coleus encountered during the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary's</color>]]> construction. (My thanks to both of you for your help testing the voyager stones!)
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: To your first observation: what you described is indeed an intended feature! The memory storage systems allow one voyager per system to remain on standby while disconnected.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: When reengaged, the voyager continues from that exact position - allowing Nomai to quickly return to their voyages, no matter how far they traveled from the projection pool!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: I find your hypothesis highly compelling - the memory storage systems must be confused somehow to cause the telepathic link you described. However, it is not to do with the voyager stone itself..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: The problem seems to arise when multiple Nomai share the same projection pool, as you and Coleus likely did while working in shifts.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: It appears the voyager system currently fails to discern between the first voyager, and any subsequent Nomai voyaging from that projection pool to the same destination.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: Instead of creating a new voyager, they inhabit the inactive voyager - causing both memory storage systems to be connected to the same voyager, and creating a stream of shared consciousness!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	
<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>		
			OENO: Goodness, what an illuminating and expedient assessment, Daz! I suppose such a major issue should be fixed.. though I must admit it was fun sharing a consciousness with someone else!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
			OENO: But now that we know the issue, Coleus and I shall simply work from different projection pools until it is fixed - that should prevent the system from confusing our memory storage systems again!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Workshop EX4</FactID>
			<Condition>2</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Workshop EX5</FactID>
			<Condition>7</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>