<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange> we are clowns in a circus </color>]]>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		OENO: Daz, the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary's</color>]]> construction has been completed already, thanks to your voyager stones! I hope you will voyage to visit it soon to see our work.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: What terrific news! Cassava, you should join me with a voyager stone - I am sure you will be impressed by our friends' work!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: I would love to! I have no doubt that
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: Whose thoughts are these? Cassava, is that you..? Are we.. Are we sharing the same voyage?!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: I-I am unsure! I only stepped into the projection pool you were using.. Quickly, disengage the projection stone from the pedestal at once!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		OENO: What happened? Are you both alright?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: I.. I believe I may have accidentally connected to Daz's voyager, after stepping into the projection pool he was using.. I was unaware the voyager stones were capable of such a thing!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	
<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>		
			DAZ: Our thoughts and experiences were being streamed to each other through the voyager's connection to our memory masks... For the briefest of moments, we were one, Cassava!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
			CASSAVA: Daz, that was incredible.. I can only imagine what we may be able to do with this incredible discovery!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>WorkshopTop EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>3</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>WorkshopTop EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>7</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>