<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		MALLOW: Daz: I have been trying to retrieve a conversation I wrote using a projection stone, with little progress.. Might you be able to access the data stored on it?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: Mallow, I'm afraid you misunderstand.. Conversations shared across projection stones are not recorded on the stone itself (like scrolls are) - they are recorded on the projection walls!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: The information is recorded onto the projection walls at both ends of the conversation, allowing Nomai at both ends to view the shared conversation using the corresponding projection stones.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: Think of each projection stone as a key, and each recorded conversation as unique locks - information that can only be retrieved with the corresponding projection stones.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		MALLOW: In other words, I must locate the corresponding projection stones to access the information I seek.. No wonder I could not find so many conversations I had written before!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		MALLOW: Your projection walls are far more sophisticated than I had imagined.. You have my gratitude for teaching me about them, my dear brother-by-proxy!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	


<ShipLogConditions>
	
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>WorkshopTop EX5</FactID>
			<Condition>3</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>WorkshopTop EX6</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>