<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Daz, I have been trying to access a conversation I wrote back on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow,</color>]]> but this projection stone seems to lack any record of that conversation! Could there be an issue with the data stored on it?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: My love, I fear you may have misundersood how projection stones and recorded conversations work!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: Conversations shared across projection stones are recorded into the projection walls they are written on, <![CDATA[<i>not</i>]]> the projection stones themselves.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: A single projection stone only grants access to any conversation with the respective wall; Think of each projection stone as a unique key, and the projection walls as having locks for each key.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: To give an example: you could only see this conversation by using a projection stone to the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Scroll and Stone Workshop</color>]]> from the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Construction Yard's</color>]]> projection wall, or vice versa - and no others!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Goodness, that makes so much more sense now! No wonder I could never seem to find my conversations on a different wall than I'd written it on.. Gratitude, my love.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	


<ShipLogConditions>
	
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Workshop EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>3</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>