<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
Clue to convey: Warp transmitters require a warp receiver (context: wait, the warp receiver isnt installed yet!)

	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CLARY: Friends, the <![CDATA[<color=orange>White Hole Station's</color>]]> construction was completed today!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: I shall be jumping into the black hole shortly to test the <![CDATA[<color=orange>White Hole Station.</color>]]> Oh, I cannot wait to jump into the black hole at last soon!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		FILIX: How exciting, Clary! Once the <![CDATA[<color=orange>White Hole Station</color>]]> is operational, we will finally be able to live without constant fear of falling into the black hole.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		POKE: Wait, Clary! <![CDATA[<i>Do not</i>]]> jump into the black hole!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		POKE: Filix, did she hear my warning?! Oh, Clary!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		FILIX: Your warning appears to have been in time, Poke! Your sister was able to catch the Belaying Beam before the black hole swallowed her. But what happened, Poke?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		POKE: I'll explain later, Filix! For now, Clary still needs our help: her maneuver landed her on the ledge right below the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Belaying Beam!</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		POKE: For some reason, she hasn't come back up using the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Belaying Beam..</color>]]> Is she injured..? Oh.. Filix, we should hurry to her!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<ShipLogConditions>

		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>BH_H EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>BH_H EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>6</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>BH_H EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>