<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		YARROW: Friends on the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Hourglass Observatory:</color>]]> I am happy to report that we are almost ready to launch the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project!</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: To allow everyone to prepare for this momentous event, we will be launching the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project</color>]]> at the conclusion of the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hourglass Twins'</color>]]> current sand transfer cycle!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: Wait, Yarrow! Sand is flowing from <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Ember Twin</color>]]> to <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Ash Twin</color>]]> during this current sand transfer cycle!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		OENO: The <![CDATA[<color=orange>solar towers</color>]]> on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Ash Twin</color>]]> are already buried by oceans of sand.. Should we not delay the launch, so they will not be impeded from powering the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project?</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: Worry not, Oeno.. No amount of sand will be able to stand up to the might of a supernova! 
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: As the sun collapses, the supernova will engulf the star system with immense heat.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: As the <![CDATA[<color=orange>solar towers</color>]]> have been reinforced, we are confident any sand will be melted away by this heat as the supernova occurs, allowing our towers to function unimpeded.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>	
	<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: I see.. I am impressed by your foresight, Yarrow! I shall look forwards greatly to the success of the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project,</color>]]> with my worries put to rest.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<ShipLogConditions>

		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>HOB EX4</FactID>
			<Condition>6</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>HOB EX5</FactID>
			<Condition>7</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>HOB R3</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	</ShipLogConditions>
	
</NomaiObject>