<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		YARROW: Be welcomed in the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Hourglass Observatory,</color>]]> Clary!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: If you are visiting today to learn about the cause of the sand transfer between the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hourglass Twins,</color>]]> we invite you to look through the observation deck above.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		YARROW: As the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hourglass Twins</color>]]> orbit around each other, they become aligned along a straight line with the sun at regular intervals, casting a sunless day on the twin farther from the sun.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: The twin farther from the sun feels not only gravity from the other twin - but also gravity from the sun, pulling it in the same direction.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: It is this combined gravitational force that causes sand to be pulled towards the other twin at the alignment point, creating the striking funnel of sand between the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hourglass Twins.</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: This force wanes as the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hourglass Twins</color>]]> orbit out of alignment. It is only when they complete a full revolution around their barycenter that the flow of sand begins once more, flowing back towards the other twin.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: You have my deepest gratitude for your thorough explanation, Yarrow. I feel much more at ease now, knowing when and why the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hourglass Twins'</color>]]> sand transfer occurs!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: Orbiting around each other like moons, the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hourglass Twins</color>]]> feel a constant pull of gravity from each other. However, this force alone is not strong enough to cause sand transfer.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
<ShipLogConditions>

		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SS Tower R1</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SS Tower EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>


		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SS Tower EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SS Tower EX2.5</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SS Tower EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SS Tower EX4</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SS Tower EX5</FactID>
			<Condition>6</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>