<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PHLOX: Spire, I had not heard you were constructing a new model here at the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Crossroads!</color>]]> Could I ask what this fascinating new model is for?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		SPIRE: Greetings, Phlox! This is a simulation of future meteor impacts from <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hollow's Lantern</color>]]> (our dreaded volcanic moon) on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow,</color>]]> but..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: What? That sounds like incredible, Spire!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: With forecasts from this model, we would be able to know precisely where any meteor impacts occur.. It would allow Nomai to safely traverse <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow's</color>]]> surface without fear!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		SPIRE: Yes, it <![CDATA[<i>would</i>]]> be a lovely idea! The only issue is... The model appears to be <![CDATA[<i>flawed.</i>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		SPIRE: Even with data from the negative time interval, a meteor impact calculated using the model was off by orders of magnitudes.. And I simply cannot figure out why.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: How odd.. Have you brought this issue to our friends in the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Hanging City?</color>]]> Perhaps they have ideas to improve the model's calculations.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: I look forward to the day you perfect this model, my friend. Your models of <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Giant's Deep</color>]]> have already been so revolutionary for our clan!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		SPIRE: How you flatter me, Phlox. You have my gratitude for your advice, my friend!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<Text>
		SPIRE: As I do not appear to be making progress on my own, I shall break from my fruitless work to seek advice from our friends at the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Hanging City.</color>]]> Perhaps they will notice something I have overlooked!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Workshop R3</FactID>
			<Condition>8</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>