<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PHLOX: Friends, may I ask who built this intriguing model of <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow</color>]]> at the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Crossroads?</color>]]> I am quite curious about its purpose!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		SPIRE: Ah, that would be me, Phlox. My apologies for my lack of clarity in this new model's purpose!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		SPIRE: This is a simulation of where future meteor impacts from <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hollow's Lantern</color>]]> (our dreaded volcanic moon) will occur on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow.</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		SPIRE: With forecasts from this model, Nomai will be able to know precisely when and where any meteor impacts occur - allowing them to safely traverse <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow's</color>]]> surface without fear!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: I see.. What a brilliant idea, Spire! I should have known you were the one behind this project, after seeing your work at the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Southern Observatory.</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: An update: Spire, I fear there may be a flaw in this model.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>	

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: A meteor approached and crashed near me just now - on a path where the model had said there would be none!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: Could there be some flaw in this model's calculations of where meteors fall - or was that harrowing encounter simply an unfortunate anomaly?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		SPIRE: My gratitude for reporting this error, Phlox. I am deeply relief you were not harmed!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<Text>
		SPIRE: How strange.. There indeed appears to be periods of inaccuracy, where meteors do not land where the model has predicted. Yet, without any modification, it returns to predicting impacts with perfect accuracy!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: An update: While studying meteor impacts during the negative time interval to improve Spire's model, we noticed a disturbing issue.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>12</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>11</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: Spire, I must return to Giant's Deep to ask Daz about this issue at once. Could you bring this matter to our friends at the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Hanging City?</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>13</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>12</ParentID>
		<Text>
		SPIRE: Of course, my friend. I only hope that somebody at the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Hanging City</color>]]> will have an answer to this mystery!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Workshop R3</FactID>
			<Condition>8</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>