<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		PHLOX: Spire, I fear there may be a flaw in this simulation of where meteor impacts from <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hollow's Lantern</color>]]> (our dreaded volcanic moon) will occur on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow!</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>	

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: A meteor approached and crashed near me just now.. on a path where the model had said there would be none!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: Could there be some flaw in this model's calculations of where meteors fall, or was that harrowing encounter simply an unfortunate anomaly?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		SPIRE: My gratitude for reporting this error, Phlox. I am deeply relief you were not harmed!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		SPIRE: How strange.. There appears to be periods of inaccuracy where meteors do not land as predicted. Yet, without any modification, it resumes predicting impacts with perfect accuracy!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: An update: Spire and I have noticed something rather disturbing.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: Spire, I must return to <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Giant's Deep</color>]]> to ask Daz about this issue at once. Could you bring this matter to our friends at the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Hanging City?</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		SPIRE: Of course, Phlox. I only hope that someone at the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Hanging City</color>]]> will have an answer to this mystery!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Workshop R3</FactID>
			<Condition>8</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>