<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		THATCH: Kousa, we deeply thank you for your incredible invention! The storm shelters have done a wonderful job protecting us from the cyclones on Giant's Deep.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		THATCH: However, Cassava and I both have witnessed the storm shelters activating erroneously, in the absence of any cyclones. I have come today to inquire your thoughts on this strange quirk!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		KOUSA: I am glad to hear of such news! It warms my heart to hear all of you safe and thriving on such a wild planet.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		KOUSA: Young Thatch, I recall explaining to you how the storm shelters function when you last visited! The storm shelters are not powered by cyclones - they are powered by solar panels!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		KOUSA: As an island is sent into orbit, the solar panels installed on them detect sunlight unimpeded by the planet's thick clouds. This is what powers the storm shelters to protect any Nomai within them.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		KOUSA: However, if a storm shelter powered down immediately upon reentry, they would rest too prematurely, and do little to protect a Nomai against the planet's intense gravity.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		KOUSA: That is why the solar panels are tuned to detect the faintest sunlight, allowing them to power the storm shelter slightly before and after a cyclone encounter, keeping its guests safely protected.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		KOUSA: However, as the sun passes directly over an island, more sunlight penetrates the clouds and reaches the solar panel. Sensitivity to this increase in sunlight is what causes the storm shelters to power on.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		THATCH: I see... My deepest gratitude for your thorough explanation, Kousa. But.. of note: it was Plume who last visited your workshop, not me!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
<ShipLogConditions>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>GSHOP EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>GSHOP EX4</FactID>
			<Condition>8</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>