<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		KOUSA: To my friends returning from the expedition to the stormy planet: I hope that you have been well!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		KOUSA: I have heard many tales of your hardships during your stay, and could not help but wonder if there was not something I could do to help..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		KOUSA: This is why I have engineered a new invention to offer protection from these storms, with great help from our friends in the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sunless City</color>]]>  - the storm shelter!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		KOUSA: The storm shelter is a device that generates a gravity field designed to hold Nomai in place, perfect for protecting Nomai in zero-gravity.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		KOUSA: Thanks to the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sunless City's</color>]]> contributions, the device is able to autonomously power itself when islands are launched into orbit, and even deactivates on its own afterwards to conserve power.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		KOUSA: I humbly invite you to visit my workshop soon so I may share this invention with you, and send it with you on your next expedition!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PLUME: How incredible, Kousa! I must thank our friends from the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sunless City</color>]]> when we next set off for our an expedition together.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PLUME: And of course, you have my deepest gratitude for your hard work, Kousa. I shall visit the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Gravity Crystal Workshop</color>]]> as soon as I can after my rest.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>BH_H EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>BH_H EX4</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>BH_H EX5</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		
	</ShipLogConditions>
	
</NomaiObject>