<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		KOUSA: Plume, my old friend! You have returned from your expedition safely!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: It is good to see you well as ever, Kousa! I see you have been working hard to keep the shelves in the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Gravity Crystal Workshop's</color>]]> stocked full of gravity crystals.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		KOUSA: Your eye is keen! A recent meteor from <![CDATA[<color=orange>Hollow's Lantern</color>]]> broke off some tiny pieces of the planet's crust, providing an abundance of material to carve new gravity crystals.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		KOUSA: But what brings you here to my humble workshop today, my friend?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PLUME: Kousa, do you not recall? You asked me to come to your workshop today to show me an invention of yours.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PLUME: If I recall correctly, you described it as an invention that would help our expedition team weather the terrible storms on the ocean planet?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		KOUSA: Oh... Yes, yes, of course. I wanted to show you my newest invention! How could I have forgotten? It is right outside!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		KOUSA: The storm shelter generates a gravity field designed to hold Nomai in place, perfect for protecting Nomai when islands are lifted into space.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		KOUSA: This is our first collaboration with the..... The...
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PLUME: The <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sunless City?</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		KOUSA: Yes, yes! The <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sunless City!</color>]]> They kindly shared their technology with us to power this invention.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>12</ID>
		<ParentID>11</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		KOUSA: Thanks to their contributions, the device can autonomously power itself when the island is launched into orbit, and even deactivates on its own afterwards, conserving power!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>13</ID>
		<ParentID>12</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PLUME: How incredible! I must thank our friends from the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sunless City</color>]]> when we next set off for our an expedition together.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>14</ID>
		<ParentID>13</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PLUME: And of course, you have my deepest gratitude for your wisdom and hard work engineering this device, Kousa! This device shall make our stay on such a turbulent planet much safer.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>15</ID>
		<ParentID>14</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		KOUSA: I am proud to do what I can to protect all of you on your journey, my friend.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>16</ID>
		<ParentID>15</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		KOUSA: Now, why were you here again?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>GSHOP EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>3</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>GSHOP EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>11</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		
	</ShipLogConditions>
	
</NomaiObject>