<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		THATCH: Kousa, I am pleased to report that the storm shelters have done a wonderful job protecting us from the cyclones on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Giant's Deep</color>]]> thus far!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		THATCH: However, we do have one small question.. Is there any reason why storm shelters sometimes power on, even in the absence of cyclones?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		KOUSA: I am glad to hear of such news! It warms my heart to hear all of you safe and thriving on such a wild planet.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		KOUSA: Ah, Thatch, did I not explain this to you when you last visited? The storm shelters are not powered by cyclones.. They are powered by solar panels!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		KOUSA: When an island is sent into orbit, the solar panels installed on the island are able to receive sunlight unimpeded by the planet's thick clouds.. This is what allows the storm shelters to autonomously activate.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		KOUSA: However, if a storm shelter powered down immediately upon reentry into the planet, they would rest too prematurely, and do little to protect a Nomai against the planet's intense gravity.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		KOUSA: To keep guests safely protected, the solar panels are tuned to detect the faintest sunlight, allowing them to power the storm shelter slightly before and after a cyclone encounter.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		KOUSA: As the sun passes directly over an island, more sunlight is able to penetrate the clouds and reach the solar panel. That is the most likely cause of the issue you have encountered!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		THATCH: I see... My deepest gratitude for your thorough explanation, Kousa. But.. Of note: it was Plume who last visited your workshop, not me!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
<ShipLogConditions>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>GSHOP R4</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>GSHOP EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>GSHOP EX4</FactID>
			<Condition>8</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>