<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		KOUSA: Plume, my old friend! You have returned from your expedition safely!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: I am glad to see you well too, Kousa! I see you have been working hard to keep the shelves in the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Gravity Crystal Workshop's</color>]]> fully stocked with gravity crystals.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		KOUSA: Your eye is keen, friend. A recent meteor has provided an abundance of material from the crust for me to carve new gravity crystals!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		KOUSA: But what brings you here to my humble workshop today, my friend?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PLUME: Kousa, do you not recall? You urged me to visit your workshop today to show me a new invention of yours!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PLUME: You mentioned a device engineered with help from the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sunless City,</color>]]> that would help our expedition team weather the terrible storms we have faced on our expedition?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		KOUSA: Ah, yes, I recall now.. I wished to show you the storm shelter!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		KOUSA: The storm shelter uses gravity crystals to powers a gravitational field to hold Nomai in place when islands are ejected into orbit.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		KOUSA: Thanks to the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sunless City's</color>]]> contributions, the device is able to autonomously power itself upon entering orbit, and even deactivates on its own afterwards to conserve power!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		KOUSA: I believe it would be easier to demonstrate than explain..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		KOUSA: There is a storm shelter right outside the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Gravity Crystal Workshop,</color>]]> my friend. If you follow me outside, I would love to show you how it works!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>GSHOP EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>3</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>GSHOP EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>7</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>BH_H R1</FactID>
			<Condition>7</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		
	</ShipLogConditions>
	
</NomaiObject>