<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PHLOX: How Projection Walls Work
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: Projection walls allow Nomai to talk to each other without being in the same place. It's a wonderful technology for talking to friends from far away!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: To use a projection wall, a projection stone must be placed into its pedestal. This connects the projection wall to the stone's corresponding projection wall, sharing anything written on both walls!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: Incoming messages from the other projection wall are written in an orange color! This makes it easy to always tell which side is talking.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		FILIX: Well done, Phlox! But did you know the projection walls are a newer version of the way our Vessel communications used to work?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: Really? My father has never told me about that!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		FILIX: It's true! Though we are unable to connect to the Vessels' communication network, our projection walls were an iteration of their design, which separated incoming and outgoing messages into different walls.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: New projection stones are crafted at the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Scroll and Stone Workshop</color>]]> every day, allowing us to talk and project from more and more places!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Workshop R5</FactID>
			<Condition>8</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>