<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
Clue: Supernova generate lots of heat

	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CLARY: <![CDATA[<i>Pye, you're safe!</i>]]> Oh, thank goodness, thank goodness.. Everybody! Pye is safe!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PYE: <![CDATA[<i>Oh, Clary!</i>]]> At long last, I am free from this dreadful <![CDATA[<color=orange>diving bell!</color>]]>  Though it was mostly insulated from the heat, the cramped interior was quite unkind on my cervical spine!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: You have our deepest apologies, Pye.. But, with this success, we can now be certain that a protective shell crafted from this ore is capable of withstanding even the might of a supernova!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PYE: But, Root.. The <![CDATA[<color=orange>diving bell</color>]]> was only tested by the heat of this volcanic lava pool, was it not?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PYE: A supernova radiates immense amounts of heat, enough to melt away the toughest of materials.. How can we be sure that the temperatures within this lava pool will be comparable?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: Your concern is not at all surprising, Pye! But fear not: our clan's elders have travelled countless galaxies, and even more knowledge was learned from their sibling clans.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: It is they who have given us precise measurements of a supernova's temperatures, equal to that of the lava pool's deepest point. We would never dare to work in theory for such crucial data!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PYE: I see.. That is an immense relief to hear.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PYE: But if that is so... There is nothing holding us back from fulfilling our elders' mission now.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PYE: I must leave at once to share the results of this test with Idaea! I will speak with you later, my friends.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: Your eyes are filled with such determination, Pye! You have our deepest gratitude for your bravery today again.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LV EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LV EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>6</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LV EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>7</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>