<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
Clue: Supernova generate lots of heat

	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PYE: My friends, I apologize for my tardiness! It is quite difficult to reach this site.. Please, how has the test of the <![CDATA[<color=orange>diving bell</color>]]> fared?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: Pye! You have arrived just in time - the <![CDATA[<color=orange>diving bell</color>]]> has just finished cooling down from its journey into the lava pool's deepest point.. Now, it is finally time to learn the results!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: Hypothesis confirmed! Hypothesis confirmed! The ice has remained completely solid, even after the <![CDATA[<color=orange>diving bell</color>]]> was submerged in the deepest point of the lava pool!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: What terrific news, friends! With this success, we can now be certain that a protective shell crafted from this ore will be capable of withstanding even the might of a supernova!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PYE: I am overjoyed to hear of this success! But, my friends.. The <![CDATA[<color=orange>diving bell</color>]]> was only tested by the heat of this volcanic lava, was it not?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PYE: A supernova radiates immense amounts of heat, enough to melt away the toughest of materials.. How can we be sure that the temperatures within this lava pool are comparable enough to trust this ore's durability?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: That is a wise question, Pye.. Perhaps we should test the <![CDATA[<color=orange>diving bell</color>]]> once more with a supernova, and see if the ice within remains solid.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: Clary, we should not make light of these concerns.. But Pye, have no fear; Our elders have travelled countless galaxies, and more knowledge was shared to them by their many sibling clans.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		ROOT: It is they who have passed down to us precise measurements of a supernova's temperatures, equal to that of this lava pool's deepest point.. We would never dare to work in theory for such crucial data!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PYE: I see.. That is an immense relief to hear.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PYE: Still, I would be happy to test Clary's craftsmanship.. We should to return to check if the ice within the <![CDATA[<color=orange>diving bell</color>]]> remains intact, once we are able to test it against a supernova!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>12</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>11</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: I was merely joking, Pye! A proper test would require us to carefully seal the <![CDATA[<color=orange>diving bell</color>]]> again once more.. With its structure compromised, the supernova would no doubt melt the ice within it!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>13</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>12</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PYE: Ha! If only your patience could gain a higher melting point as well, my friend!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LV EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LV EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>6</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LV EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>7</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>