<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Oeno, thank goodness you have voyaged here! One of the native lifeforms has escaped the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary!</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: I disconnected from my voyager briefly before realizing I had allowed the quantum shard to slip from my sight, along with one of the native species slumbering on it... When I returned, it was no longer on the quantum shard!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CYCAD: I wished to leave the Sanctuary to search for it, but I found myself unable to travel to Timber Hearth's surface! Please, how does one use the rule of quantum entanglement as a voyager?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: Leave this task to me, Cycad! I shall locate our runaway friend and deliver it back into the Sanctuary.
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Oeno, how did you do that?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: The surface of the planet is never dark enough for conscious beings to use the rule of quantum entanglement - and the quantum shard is surely too small to safely carry our unconscious bodies, unlike these lifeforms!
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: It is quite simple, Cycad. Simply recall how you caused the quantum shard to move earlier!
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: I see! A voyager is unable to observe its surroundings on its own...
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>		
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: You have my gratitude for this lesson, Oeno!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	

<ShipLogConditions>
			<RevealFact>
				<FactID>SY EX1</FactID>
				<Condition>3</Condition>
			</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
				<FactID>SY EX3</FactID>
				<Condition>8</Condition>
			</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
				<FactID>SY EX4</FactID>
				<Condition>8</Condition>
			</RevealFact>
</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>