<DialogueTree xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/dialogue_schema.xsd">

<NameField>RECORDING</NameField>

<DialogueNode>
    <Name>Feldspar_Destroyer</Name>
    <EntryCondition>DEFAULT</EntryCondition>
    <Dialogue>
      <Page>Trip 2, entry #1</Page>
      <Page>Crashes: 30 (All on purpose!)</Page>
      <Page>Alright! Looks like this chunk of Brittle Hollow is as stable as it gets.</Page>
      <Page>Like I'd have found that out if I'd just used the scout's integrity reading like Hornfels always nags about..</Page>
       <Page><![CDATA[<i>All</i>]]> the chunks read 100% integrity! It's how much that 100% decreases if you stomp too hard or whatever that matters!</Page>
      <Page>But uh, hm, wow. Brittle Hollow.. seriously lives up to that first part of its name.</Page>
      <Page>You're telling me just a light crash into a piece of its crust... with one of Slate's rickety ships... damages the crust <![CDATA[<i>that much?</i>]]> <![CDATA[<Pause=2>]]> ..That's just horrifying.</Page>
       <Page>I probably shouldn't keep trying to test surface integrity by crashing my ship into it then...</Page>
       <Page>Repairs aside, might not be much of a planet left by the time I'm done.</Page>
         <Page>Anyway... What are these weird lil' crystals? They're making me stick to the wall.</Page>
          <Page>Guess they must play with gravity somehow? That's neat.</Page>
             <Page>I should try bring one home to Timber Hearth. Bet it'd make a pretty neat exhibit in Hornfels' new museum!</Page>
             <Page>If Slate could install one in the ship, maybe it'd do something getting spacesick driving that rickety ship, too.</Page>
             <Page>And if the ship has some localized gravity, maybe I can finally fly that lil' hatchling who's afraid of space to see the ruins on this planet at last!</Page>
    </Dialogue>
  </DialogueNode>

</DialogueTree>