<DialogueTree xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/dialogue_schema.xsd">

	
	<NameField>Gabbro</NameField>
	

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>GabbroMenu</Name>

		<DialogueOptionsList>
	<DialogueOption>
				<RequiredLogCondition>ARK EX2</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>Gabbro, did you tell Arkose something about ghost matter disappearing?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>GM_Talk</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
				<DialogueOption>
				<Text>What's with the campfire right outside the cove there?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>CampfireWave</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>GM_Talk</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Hm? Oh yea, I noticed that on my last trip here.</Page>
			<Page>That smart lil' cookie noticed the same thing back on Timber Hearth, and asked me about it last time I visited the village.</Page>
			<Page>You know the Little Scout has a feature that tells you if there's danger where you shoot it, right?</Page>
				<Page>It works great for scouting out ghost matter. Lights up a warning when you shoot it into a patch of the deadly stuff - which is sweet if you tend to forget the invisible deadly stuff is there.</Page>
				<Page>Well, one time, I was using it to scout a big patch of ghost matter on one of the other islands. Just left it down in case I forgot it was there.</Page>
				<Page>But suddenly, the scout suddenly starts saying it's safe!</Page>
				<Page>That's weird, right? Must be some quirk with the sensors, I thought.</Page>
				<Page>But I took some photos with the scout camera too, and lo and behold - the ghost matter really was gone!</Page>
				<Page>Weirder, a moment later, the scout says there's danger again.. And the ghost matter was back in the photos, too.</Page>
				<Page>Wasn't a one-off, either - though I've noticed it seems to happen on this island more than any of the other islands with ghost matter I've come across, for whatever reason.</Page>
				<Page>I haven't actually like.. stuck a limb into the ghost matter to know for sure if the ghost matter really vanishes when that happens. <![CDATA[<Pause=1>]]> I don't know if I trust Slate's tech more than my common sense, y'know?</Page>
				<Page>I made Arkose seriously promise me not to do anything dumb trying to learn about this stuff. I hope they've listened.</Page>
				<Page>I know ghost matter evaporates away with time, but isn't that supposed to take ages? The few patches I've found all look like they've got a long way to go.</Page>
					<Page>But hey, there's some ghost matter right in the cove back there. Feel free to check it out with your scout if you're feeling curious.</Page>
						<Page>Just be careful, alright? There's a campfire up the hill you can patch up by if you happen to get hurt messing with the stuff.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		 				  <RevealFacts>
     						   <FactID>Cove R1</FactID>
    					  </RevealFacts>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
		<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Can't I use the campfire outside the cove there?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>WillDo</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Will do.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>WillDo</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>CampfireWave</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Oh, you can light that one back up if you want. Just uh, don't use it for napping.</Page>
			<Page>I've woken up wet and groggy literally every time I slept at that campfire.. Well, wetter and groggier than usual, sleeping on Giant's Deep.</Page>
			<Page>Just a bad spot for a campfire, I guess.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>WillDo</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Sweet. Stay safe out there, time buddy.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>



</DialogueTree>