<DialogueTree xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/dialogue_schema.xsd">

	
	<NameField>Gabbro</NameField>
	

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>GabbroMenu</Name>

		<DialogueOptionsList>
	<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Gabbro, did you tell Arkose something about ghost matter disappearing?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>GM_Talk</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>GM_Talk</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Hm? Oh yea, I noticed that on my last trip here.</Page>
			<Page>That smart lil' cookie noticed the same thing back on Timber Hearth too, and asked me about it last time I visited the village.</Page>
			<Page>You know the Little Scout has a feature that tells you if there's danger where you shoot it?</Page>
				<Page>It works great for scouting out ghost matter. Lights up a warning when you shoot it into a patch of the deadly stuff - which is sweet if you're lazy to snap photos everywhere like me.</Page>
				<Page>Well, one time, I was using it to scout a big patch of ghost matter on one of the other islands. Just left it down in-case I forget the invisible deadly stuff is there.</Page>
				<Page>But suddenly, the scout suddenly starts saying it's safe!</Page>
				<Page>That's weird, right? Must be some quirk with the sensors, I thought.</Page>
				<Page>But I took some photos with the scout camera too, and lo and behold - the ghost matter really was gone!</Page>
				<Page>Weirder, right after the scout says there's danger again.. and the ghost matter was back in the photos, too!</Page>
				<Page>Wasn't a one-off, though I've noticed it seems to happen on this island more than any of the other islands with ghost matter I've come across, for whatever reason.</Page>
				<Page>I haven't actually like.. stuck a limb into the ghost matter to know for sure if the ghost matter really vanishes when that happens. I don't know if I trust Slate's tech more than my instincts, y'know?</Page>
				<Page>I made Arkose seriously promise me not to do anything dumb too, so I hope they listened.</Page>
					<Page>But hey, there's some ghost matter right in the cove back there. Feel free to check it out with your scout and see the weird stuff for yourself, if you don't believe me!</Page>
						<Page>Just be careful, alright? There's a campfire I set up up the hill you can patch up by if you happen to get hurt messing with the stuff.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Can't I just use the campfire right outside the cove there?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>CampfireWave</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Will do!</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>WillDo</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>CampfireWave</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>I mean.. sure? You could light that one back up if you really want to.</Page>
			<Page>But I'm just saying! There's a better fire up the hill I made for a reason...</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>WillDo</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Man, now I wanna get up and go roast a can of marshmallows.</Page>
			<Page>When you roast it just right, it just melts in your mouth and melts away any bad thoughts and bruises, y'know?</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>



</DialogueTree>