<DialogueTree xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/dialogue_schema.xsd">

	<NameField>Mica</NameField>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>ModelRocketKid1</Name>
	
		<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<RequiredLogCondition>MICA R1</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>Hey, Mica. Got any questions about the universe for me?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>ModelRocketKid_Sand1</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<RequiredLogCondition>MICA EX1</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>Hey Mica, the sand column's flowing right now!</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>ModelRocketKid_RightNow</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
			<RequiredLogCondition>SS Tower EX5</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>I figured out what causes sand to flow between the Hourglass Twins!</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>ModelRocketKid_Sand2</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
	</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>ModelRocketKid_Sand1</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Questions about the universe? Uh, wow, you're putting me on the spot, astronaut! Uhh, lemme think a sec...</Page>
			<Page>How about.. No, I figured that one out... Um, what about... Oh, OH! I got one!</Page>
			<Page>Um, when does sand start flowing between the Hourglass Twins again, astronaut?</Page>
		</Dialogue>
			 <DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Pretty soon..?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>ModelRocketKid_SW_Intro_2</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Wait.. Sand stops flowing between the Hourglass Twins?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>ModelRocketKid_SW_Intro</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
			<RequiredLogCondition>SS Tower EX5</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>The sand starts flowing when the Hourglass Twins orbit into alignment with the sun.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>ModelRocketKid_Sand</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
	</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>ModelRocketKid_SW_Intro</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Yeah, haven't you noticed? Try looking at the Hourglass Twins with your signalscope right now, astronaut!</Page>
			<Page>Without sand flowing between them, the "Hourglass Twins" don't really live up to their name, do they? We should just call them "The Twins" the rest of the time, heh.</Page>
			<Page>Chert told me sand should start flowing back to Ember Twin again really soon.. <![CDATA[<Pause=2>]]> But that's SO vague!</Page>
			<Page>I wanna be ready to watch when sand starts flowing between the Twins again, but since Chert took off into space without telling me how much longer it'll take, I have no idea when it's gonna happen..</Page>
			 </Dialogue>
			  				<RevealFacts>
     						   <FactID>MICA EX1</FactID>
     						   <FactID>MICA EX2</FactID>
     						   <FactID>MICA EX3</FactID>
    					  </RevealFacts>
			<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Maybe I'll go ask Chert what they know, then.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>ModelRocketKid_SW_End</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
	</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>ModelRocketKid_SW_Intro_2</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Uugh, I know that already..</Page>
			<Page>Chert told me it'd happen again really soon - but I've been waiting and waiting, and nothing! It feels like one of those things that won't happen until you stop waiting for it.</Page>
			<Page>Without sand flowing between them, the "Hourglass Twins" don't even live up to their name! We should just call them "The Twins" until sand finally flows between them again.</Page>
			<Page>If you see Chert out there, could you help me ask how much longer it'll take? I wanna be ready to watch when sand starts flowing to the other Twin again!</Page>
			  </Dialogue>
			  				<RevealFacts>
     						   <FactID>MICA EX1</FactID>
     						   <FactID>MICA EX2</FactID>
     						   <FactID>MICA EX3</FactID>
    					  </RevealFacts>
			<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Maybe I'll go ask Chert what they know, then.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>ModelRocketKid_SW_End</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
	</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>ModelRocketKid_SW_End</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Sounds like a plan.</Page>
			<Page>Hey, astronaut, if you learn anything about why sand flows between the Hourglass Twins..</Page>
			<Page>..Promise you'll come back and tell me all about it? I wanna learn more about this weird phenomenon too!</Page>
			 </Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>ModelRocketKid_RightNow</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>W-what? Right now.. Really?!</Page>
			<Page>Aww.. Moraine's still using the signalscope, and I can't borrow yours when you're about to go into space.. ARGH! I had the signalscope all day the other day, waiting for the sand to start flowing! Why's it only starting now?!</Page>
			<Page>Space is the worst...</Page>
			 </Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>
	

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>ModelRocketKid_Sand2</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Wha? Are you still half-awake from your nap, astronaut? You musta had some crazy dreams!</Page>
			<Page>Eh, whatever. Let's hear your ideas for what causes the twins' weird shifting sands, astronaut!</Page>
			 </Dialogue>
				 <DialogueOptionsList>
					<DialogueOption>
					<RequiredPersistentCondition>Chert_Natural</RequiredPersistentCondition>
						<Text>Chert says it's just some sort of natural phenomenon.</Text>
							<DialogueTarget>ModelRocketKid_Sand_No</DialogueTarget>
					</DialogueOption>
					<DialogueOption>
								<Text>It's caused by gravity from the sun and the twin closer to the sun combining during alignment.</Text>
						<DialogueTarget>ModelRocketKid_Sand</DialogueTarget>
						</DialogueOption>
				</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<SetPersistentCondition>Mica_Q</SetPersistentCondition>
		<Name>ModelRocketKid_Sand_No</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Pfff. I've heard that before too, astronaut!</Page>
			<Page>Slate says that's just Chert's fancy way of saying they don't know what causes it.</Page>
			<Page>I'd never say that to Chert's face.. but I feel like there's gotta just be more we haven't figured out there!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>ModelRocketKid_Sand</Name>
		<SetCondition>Question_Answered</SetCondition>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Huh.. So it's gravity from the sun... and gravity from the twin closer to the sun combining, that causes sand to flow between the twins...</Page>
			<Page>Huh.. That makes sense! The sun's gotta have some insane gravitational pull, after all.</Page>
			<Page>So.. If that's true, that means sand should stop flowing between the Twins once they orbit out of alignment, right?</Page>
			<Page>Haha, that sounds like a fun theory to test! It shouldn't take too long for the Hourglass Twins to orbit around each other again. Let's see if the sand stops flowing when they orbit out of alignment, astronaut!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>



</DialogueTree>
