<DialogueTree xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/dialogue_schema.xsd">

	<!--
	IF IT’S NIGHT, change SignalScopeKid2 dialogue to this:
	I’m waiting for nightfall so I can pick up sounds from distant planets using my signalscope.
-->

	<NameField>Moraine</NameField>
	
	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>SignalscopeKid1</Name>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
		<DialogueOption>
			<RequiredPersistentCondition>Shutup_Moraine</RequiredPersistentCondition>
			<RequiredLogCondition>TH_NOMAI_MINE_X3</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>I dived into the waterways and found a Nomai mural depicting Hearthian ancestors on land.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>SignalscopeKidNew4</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
				<DialogueOption>
				<RequiredLogCondition>MOR R1</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>Hey Moraine, did you hear anything about ghost matter disappearing?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>SignalscopeKidNew1</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>SignalscopeKidNew1</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Yeah, I thought everyone knew that. Ghost matter evaporates slowly, doesn't it?</Page>
			<Page>Still, it's a little scary how long it's taken just that little patch in the village to evaporate..</Page>
			<Page>The fact that there are skeletons of early Hearthians in there, tells us that little patch must have been around even when our Hearthian ancestors were learning to walk on land!</Page>
			</Dialogue>
			<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Wait, there are Hearthian skeletons in there?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>SignalscopeKidNew2</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
	</DialogueOptionsList>
		</DialogueNode>

		<DialogueNode>
		<Name>SignalscopeKidNew2</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Yeah! You didn't notice them before?</Page>
			<Page>We haven't been able to remove them because of the ghost matter to put them in the museum, but Riebeck says they're definitely Hearthian!</Page>
			<Page>Riebeck says they must have been some ancestors of ours, unlucky enough to stumble upon that patch of ghost matter while exploring the surface of Timber Hearth.</Page>
			<Page>Our species used to be aquatic before our ancestors learned to walk on land, you know.</Page>
			<Page>Riebeck thinks Hearthians had to learn how to live on land because if they didn't, we'd have died instantly whenever we got launched out of the water by geysers!</Page>
			<Page>Even though they could go on land, Riebeck says our ancestors still mainly lived in the huge underground cave system inside the geysers.</Page>
			<Page>Apparently, there's a whole interconnected underwater cave system inside the geysers that our ancestors swam around in!</Page>
			<Page>That part's a recent discovery, though. Nobody's even explored the waterways yet, since Riebeck <![CDATA[<i>"wasn't going to get eaten by an underwater monster",</i>]]> and the other astronauts were uh, busy, lazy, or missing.</Page>
				<Page>Oh, I can't even imagine what's down there, in the waterways our ancestors lived in for millennia.. Would you ever be interested in jumping into a geyser to explore Timber Hearth's spooky depths, astronaut?</Page>
		</Dialogue>
							<RevealFacts>
     						  	 <FactID>MOR EX1</FactID>
    					 	 </RevealFacts>
	 <DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>I could dive down there to look around sometime.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>SignalscopeKidNew3</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
			<RequiredLogCondition>TH_NOMAI_MINE_X3</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>I swam around the waterways already! I found a Nomai mural of our Hearthian ancestors down there.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>SignalscopeKidNew4</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
	</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>



<DialogueNode>
		<Name>SignalscopeKidNew3</Name>
		<SetPersistentCondition>Shutup_Moraine</SetPersistentCondition>
		<Dialogue>
				<Page>Really? Wow, you're so cool, astronaut!</Page>
				<Page>I'd love to jump down a geyser to explore myself.. But Mayor Rutile says I'll drown, since we can't breathe underwater like early Hearthians did, and I'm bad at holding my breath..</Page>
				<Page>If you do find anything down there, I wanna hear all about it, okay?</Page>
				<Page>Oooh, it's like revisiting the place where our ancestors came from! This is gonna be an incredible day for Hearthian history, astronaut!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>SignalscopeKidNew4</Name>
		<Dialogue>
				<Page>Woah.. What? A Nomai mural of.. our ancestors on land? That’s.. That's <![CDATA[<i>awesome!</i>]]></Page>
				<Page>It’s not a huge underwater monster like I was hoping.. But it’s still really awesome!</Page>
				<Page>But wait... Doesn’t that mean Hearthians must have already existed when the Nomai were around?</Page>
					<Page>And it sounds like we were still able to live on both water AND land back then! </Page>
					<Page>Aw, when did Hearthians stop being able to breathe underwater completely then?</Page>
					<Page>If we were still able to breathe underwater nowadays, I'd be able to swim around the waterways all day..</Page>
				<Page>But wow.. Isn't this discovery gonna totally upend our knowledge of Hearthian history?</Page>
					<Page>I think you’d better fly to Brittle Hollow as soon as you can to tell Riebeck about this huge discovery, astronaut. They'll probably lose their marbles revising the Hearthian history books!</Page>
					<Page>Don’t forget, you can use your signalscope to track down the other travelers more easily!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
							<RevealFacts>
     						  	 <FactID>MOR EX2</FactID>	 
     						  	 <FactID>MOR EX3</FactID>	 
     						  	 <FactID>MOR R2</FactID>
    					 	 </RevealFacts>
		
		<SetCondition>SHOW_SIGNALSCOPE_PROMPT</SetCondition>
	</DialogueNode>





		<DialogueNode>
		<Name>SignalscopeKid5</Name>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
				<DialogueOption>
				<RequiredPersistentCondition>Shutup_Moraine</RequiredPersistentCondition>
			<RequiredLogCondition>TH_NOMAI_MINE_X3</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>I dived into the waterways and found a Nomai mural depicting Hearthian ancestors on land.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>SignalscopeKidNew4</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
				<DialogueOption>
				<RequiredLogCondition>MOR R1</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>Hey Moraine, did you hear anything about ghost matter disappearing?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>SignalscopeKidNew1</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>


</DialogueTree>