<DialogueTree xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/dialogue_schema.xsd">

	<!--
	IF IT’S NIGHT, change SignalScopeKid2 dialogue to this:
	I’m waiting for nightfall so I can pick up sounds from distant planets using my signalscope.
-->

	<NameField>Moraine</NameField>
	
	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>SignalscopeKid1</Name>
			<DialogueOptionsList>
		<DialogueOption>
			<RequiredLogCondition>MOR R3</RequiredLogCondition>
			<RequiredLogCondition>TH_NOMAI_MINE_X3</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>I dived into the waterways and found a Nomai mural of ancient Hearthians on land.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>SignalscopeKidNew4</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
				<DialogueOption>
				<RequiredLogCondition>MOR R1</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>Hey Moraine. Have you.. heard anything about stuff that disappears sometimes?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>SignalscopeKidNew1</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<RequiredLogCondition>MOR EX3</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>Hang on, why did you think there was more than one comet?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>SignalscopeKidNewC1</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<RequiredLogCondition>INSP R0</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>I think I found the comet you saw!</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>SignalscopeKidNewC2</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>


<DialogueNode>
		<Name>SignalscopeKidNewC1</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>O-oh, um.. Sorry, I think I probably just saw wrong..</Page>
			<Page>You know how busted my signalscope is, with how much Tephra and Galena play with it.. Just look at how much shinier your brand new signalscope is, astronaut!</Page>
			<Page>But, if you really wanna know.. I thought I saw two comets in the sky a few nights ago.</Page>
			<Page>I've been trying to catch this second comet again ever since, just to see if it's real.. But I haven't been able to see it again since.</Page>
			<Page>So.. I think it really was just a smudge on my signalscope.</Page>
			<Page>But ahh, I really wanna hope.. Imagine if I'd discovered a new celestial body, astronaut! That'd be a dream come true.</Page>
			</Dialogue>
							<RevealFacts>
     						  	 <FactID>MOR R4</FactID>
    					 	 </RevealFacts>
		</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>SignalscopeKidNewC2</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>R-really?! Please, tell me more about it!</Page>
			<Page>What was this comet like? Where was it hiding?</Page>
			</Dialogue>
			<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>It's hidden in Giant's Deep's shadow.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>SignalscopeKidNewC3</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<RequiredLogCondition>INSP EX4</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>It's made of gravity crystals, and the Nomai made it.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>SignalscopeKidNewC4</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<RequiredLogCondition>INSP EX2</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>It's a Nomai superweapon.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>SignalscopeKidNewC5</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
	</DialogueOptionsList>
		</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>SignalscopeKidNewC3</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Ohh.. So that's why it's so hard to see it.. I guess Giant's Deep must have kept it hidden from us pretty well!</Page>
			<Page>But.. that's weird, isn't it?</Page>
			<Page>Hornfels told me comets can have weird orbits.. But comets aren't supposed to stay still like that, are they? The Interloper sure doesn't do that!</Page>
			<Page>Why is this comet hiding itself inside a planet's shadow like that? It's kinda creepy..</Page>
			</Dialogue>
		</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>SignalscopeKidNewC4</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Woah, wha? The Nomai MADE the comet.. And the whole thing's made of gravity crystals..? That's. NUTS, astronaut!!</Page>
			<Page>Where'd the Nomai even get so many gravity crystals?!</Page>
			<Page>Also, isn't a whole comet-sized chunk of gravity crystals kinda much? What could they possibly need that much for?</Page>
			<Page>Were the Nomai trying to make a little artificial moon?</Page>
			<Page>Haha, that's such a cute idea.. I could totally see the Nomai doing that!</Page>
			</Dialogue>
		</DialogueNode>

		<DialogueNode>
		<Name>SignalscopeKidNewC5</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Huh? A.. weapon?</Page>
			<Page>But.. Weren't the Nomai really peaceful and friendly? Why.. What'd they need a weapon like that for?</Page>
			<Page>That's.. really weird.</Page>
			<Page>Um...If it really is a weapon.. I'm sure they must have had a good reason to make something like that.</Page>
			</Dialogue>
		</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>SignalscopeKidNew1</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Huh? What a strange question, astronaut!</Page>
			<Page>Um.. Does our ability to breathe underwater count?</Page>
			</Dialogue>
			<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Wait.. We used to be able to breathe underwater?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>SignalscopeKidNew2</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
	</DialogueOptionsList>
		</DialogueNode>

		<DialogueNode>
		<Name>SignalscopeKidNew2</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Yeah! Isn't that cool? We used to be able to breathe underwater like the little fishies do!</Page>
			<Page>You know our species was totally aquatic a long, long time ago, right?</Page>
			<Page>According to Riebeck, our ancestors had to learn to live on land because if they didn't, they'd have died instantly whenever the geysers launched them out of the waterways where we lived.</Page>
			<Page>But even after learning to live on land, for some reason, our ancestors continued to live inside the waterways inside the geysers.</Page>
			<Page>Apparently, there's even a massive underwater cave system inside the geysers that our ancestors swam around in!</Page>
			<Page>That part's a recent discovery, though.. Nobody's properly explored them yet, since Riebeck "wasn't going to get eaten by an underwater monster", and the other astronauts were uh, busy, lazy, or missing.</Page>
				<Page>I'd hate to get your spacesuit wet, but.. Would <![CDATA[<i>you</i>]]> be interested in jumping into one of those geysers to explore Timber Hearth's spooky depths, astronaut?</Page>
				<Page>I'd dive into a geyser to explore those ancient waterways myself - but Riebeck says since we stopped being able to breathe underwater, I'd probably just drown..</Page>
		</Dialogue>
							<RevealFacts>
     						  	 <FactID>MOR R3</FactID>
    					 	 </RevealFacts>
	 <DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Sure, I could dive down there to look around sometime.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>SignalscopeKidNew3</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
			<RequiredLogCondition>TH_NOMAI_MINE_X3</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>I swam around the waterways already! I found a Nomai mural of our Hearthian ancestors down there.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>SignalscopeKidNew4</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
	</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>



<DialogueNode>
		<Name>SignalscopeKidNew3</Name>
		<Dialogue>
				<Page>Really? Wow, you're so cool, astronaut!</Page>
				<Page>If you do find anything down there, I wanna hear all about it, okay?</Page>
				<Page>Oooh, it's like revisiting the place where we all came from! This is gonna be an incredible day for Hearthian history, astronaut!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>SignalscopeKidNew4</Name>
		<SetCondition>morc1</SetCondition>
		<Dialogue>
				<Page>Woah, what..? A Nomai mural of our ancestors on land..? That’s.. That's <![CDATA[<i>awesome!</i>]]></Page>
				<Page>It’s not a huge underwater monster like I was hoping.. But it’s still really awesome!</Page>
				<Page>But wait... Doesn’t that mean our ancestors were already alive when the Nomai were around?</Page>
					<Page>What's more, it sounds like we were still able to live on both water AND land back then..</Page>
					<Page>Aw, when did Hearthians stop being able to breathe underwater completely then? If we were still able to breathe underwater nowadays, I'd be able to swim around the waterways all day!</Page>
					<Page>But wow.. Isn't this discovery gonna totally upend our knowledge of Hearthian history, astronaut?</Page>
					<Page>If Riebeck heard about this discovery, they'd probably lose their marbles revising the Hearthian history books!</Page>
					<Page>Oooh, I bet Riebeck's gonna kick themself for turning down the chance to be the first to explore those waterways.. I can't imagine the look on their face when they hear about this!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
							<RevealFacts>
     						  	 <FactID>MOR EX1</FactID>	 
     						  	 <FactID>MOR EX2</FactID>	 
     						  	 <FactID>MOR R2</FactID>
    					 	 </RevealFacts>
	</DialogueNode>





		<DialogueNode>
		<Name>SignalscopeKid5</Name>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
		<DialogueOption>
			<RequiredLogCondition>MOR R3</RequiredLogCondition>
			<RequiredLogCondition>TH_NOMAI_MINE_X3</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>I dived into the waterways and found a Nomai mural of ancient Hearthians on land.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>SignalscopeKidNew4</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
				<DialogueOption>
				<RequiredLogCondition>MOR R1</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>Hey Moraine. Have you.. heard anything about stuff that disappears sometimes?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>SignalscopeKidNew1</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<RequiredLogCondition>MOR EX3</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>Hang on, why did you think there was more than one comet?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>SignalscopeKidNewC1</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<RequiredLogCondition>INSP R0</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>I think I found the comet you saw!</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>SignalscopeKidNewC2</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>


</DialogueTree>