<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PHLOX: The cyclone appears to have passed. We are safe now, my friends.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		DAZ: What a relief.. Thank goodness the specimen was not swept away by the winds as well.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		DAZ: But how strange! The jellyfish of <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Giant's Deep</color>]]> typically dwell near the planet's core... How did this specimen travel so far away from its dwelling, to end up on the surface of the ocean?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Perhaps it was a frozen jellyfish recently released from Bramble Island's glaciers? That is the first hypothesis that comes to my mind.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: I would not think it would be possible for most species to survive such long-term preservation, but it is a possibility.. Is there any way we could test this hypothesis?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		DAZ: Perhaps we should visit the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Deep Storm Station.</color>]]> We should be able to survey the native population of jellyfish under the ocean current from aboard the station.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: That is a wise idea, Daz! If there is any change in the total population, we will know that this specimen was from the native population.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: The warp pad to the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Deep Storm Station</color>]]> is located on the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Construction Yard.</color>]]> Let us travel there at once, my friends!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Cove EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Cove R4</FactID>
			<Condition>2</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>DSS R7</FactID>
			<Condition>6</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>