<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		COLEUS: The projection pool has been installed, Oeno! Now, we will be able to project to this site for further inspections in the future.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: This space seems rather small, Coleus.. Will there be enough room for the warp receiver into the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary?</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		OENO: We won't be constructing a warp receiver for this structure, Cycad. It would be too costly - we plan on entering using different means.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		CYCAD: A warp transmitter requires a connected warp receiver to function, does it not?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Surely there must be a different route of entry other than the one Coleus used.. I have never been comfortable trusting a quantum entity with my life, you see.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: Worry not, Cycad: have you heard of Daz's latest invention? It should provide you with the most convenient entry into the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary!</color>]]>
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: Daz has asked all of us to use his invention during the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary's</color>]]> construction.. We will be the first to test it thoroughly!
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: How exciting! Cycad, you must visit the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Scroll and Stone Workshop</color>]]> on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Giant's Deep</color>]]> to learn more about Daz's invention when you can!
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	

<ShipLogConditions>

			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Campsite EX1.5</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SY R4</FactID>
			<Condition>6</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SY R3</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
				<RevealFact>
				<FactID>SY R4</FactID>
				<Condition>6</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Workshop R1</FactID>
			<Condition>11</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>