<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		COLEUS: Friends, the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary's</color>]]> projection pool has been successfully installed! You should be able to peer through the pool to see our progress now.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Looking through the projection pool, this space seems rather small, Coleus.. Are we sure there is enough space for a warp receiver?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		OENO: Haven't you heard, Cycad? We won't be constructing a warp receiver to enter the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary.</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		OENO: For this project, we will be using the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Scroll and Stone Workshop's</color>]]> latest invention to journey to this space instead!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		COLEUS: According to Daz, the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Scroll and Stone Workshop's</color>]]> new invention will allow Nomai to explore outside the radius of a projection pool, not just peer through it.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: With such technology, we will be able to travel anywhere without the restrictions of a warp pad!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: I cannot wait, Coleus.. I am sure this technology will be truly revolutionary for our clan!
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: Cycad, if you wish to learn more about Daz's invention, you should visit the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Scroll and Stone Workshop</color>]]> on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Giant's Deep</color>]]> to see it in motion!
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	

<ShipLogConditions>

			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Campsite EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>8</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SY R4</FactID>
			<Condition>8</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Workshop R1</FactID>
			<Condition>8</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>