<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		COLEUS: Friends, the forge has asked for one more shipment of ore to be delivered to <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hollow's Lantern</color>]]>. Let us work quickly to complete this last shipment!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Isn't the construction of <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Ash Twin's</color>]]> protective shell complete? What will this new shipment of ore be used for?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		COLEUS: Why, in the construction of the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary,</color>]]> of course!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		COLEUS: Even though it was formed here, the ore still requires treatment at <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Hollow's Lantern</color>]]> to reach its full capabilities.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CYCAD: That is sooner than I'd thought! Has a suitable site for the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary</color>]]> been chosen already?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: Indeed! We have chosen a site in the planet's underground pools, where one of the quantum shard travels.
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: In that case, we will need to put extra eyes into carefully reinforcing the walls of the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary</color>]]> to protect it from groundwater.
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Has the need for a new warp receiver been communicated to Poke yet? The warp receiver must be installed before the structure can be sealed!
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: That won't be necessary, Cycad! The new type of projection stone invented by Daz should allow us to work without a warp receiver.
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>

		<ID>10</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: What? But warp transmitters require a connected warp receiver to function! How will anyone enter the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary,</color>]]> without a warp receiver to warp them inside?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: You should visit the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Scroll and Stone Workshop</color>]]> on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Giant's Deep</color>]]> to learn about Daz's invention, Cycad - it will allow us to access the sealed space without a warp system entirely!
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>12</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>11</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: If it means the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary's</color>]]> construction will be more expedient, I have absolutely no qualms! When shall we begin our work?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>13</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>12</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: I am glad to hear your enthusiasm as always, my young apprentice.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>14</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>13</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: Is everyone rested up? Then we shall begin our work shortly!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	

<ShipLogConditions>

				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Campsite EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>14</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Campsite EX1.5</FactID>
			<Condition>10</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SY R2</FactID>
			<Condition>9</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SY R3</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
				<RevealFact>
				<FactID>SY R4</FactID>
				<Condition>6</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Workshop R1</FactID>
			<Condition>11</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>