<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Oeno, I write to you from my voyager within the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary:</color>]]> I request urgent assistance in locating a native lifeform that has escaped my watch!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: I disconnected from my voyager briefly by accident, allowing the quantum shard to slip from my sight, along with one of the native lifeforms resting on it. When the shard returned, its passenger was gone!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		OENO: We must locate this runaway before the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project</color>]]> begins; the Sanctuary is their only lifeline in the event that all other safety measures fail!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: I have located and delivered the slumbering runaway back into the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary,</color>]]> Cycad! Please watch over them with great care.
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: But Cycad, you should be able to entangle with and travel using the quantum shard yourself as a voyager! If any more escapes occur, I implore you to take matters into your own hands.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: But the surface of the planet is never completely dark enough for one to allow a conscious individual to travel to it using the quantum shard.. I do not see how... Oh!
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: I see now! A voyager lacks sentience, and so lacks the ability to observe its surroundings on its own!
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: However, it is rather slow waiting from within the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary</color>]]> for the quantum shard to return.. I wish it didn't require a cover of darkness inside the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary</color>]]> to visit!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	

<ShipLogConditions>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Nomai Mine Entry 2</FactID>
			<Condition>8</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>