<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Oeno, I write to you from my voyager within the Sanctuary: if you read this scroll, I request urgent assistance in locating and returning one of the native lifeforms into the Sanctuary!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: I disengaged my voyager stone by accident for a moment, allowing the quantum shard to slip from my sight back into superposition, along with one of the native lifeforms resting on it!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		OENO: When the shard returned, the lifeform was gone! We must locate and return it to safety. The Sanctuary is their only lifeline in the event that the Ash Twin Project fails!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: I have located and delivered our four-eyed friend back into the Sanctuary, Cycad! Thank goodness I saw your scroll on the quantum shard before the runaway traveled any farther.
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: But Cycad, you should be able to entangle with and travel using the quantum shard, even as a voyager. If any more escapes occur, I implore you to take matters into your own hands!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: But how? The surface of the planet is never dark enough for one to entangle with the shard to travel to the surface without observing their surroundings. I do not see how..
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Ah, I understand now.. A voyager lacks sentience, and so lacks the ability to observe its surroundings on its own!
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: That said, it is rather tiresome waiting within the Sanctuary for the quantum shard to return, once it travels outside.. I wish it didn't have to only travel inside under the cover of darkness!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	

<ShipLogConditions>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Nomai Mine Entry 2</FactID>
			<Condition>8</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>