<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Oeno, I write to you from my voyager within the Sanctuary: I request urgent assistance in locating a native lifeform that  escaped from the Sanctuary!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: I disengaged the voyager stone briefly by accident - allowing the quantum shard to slip from my sight, along with one of the native lifeforms resting on it!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		OENO: When the shard returned, its passenger was gone! We must locate and rescue this runaway before the Ash Twin Project begins to spare it from a terrible fate!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: I have located and delivered our four-eyed friend back into the Sanctuary, Cycad!
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: But Cycad, you should be able to entangle with and travel using the quantum shard, even as a voyager. If any more escapes occur, I implore you to take matters into your own hands!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: But the surface of the planet is never dark enough for one to travel to using the quantum shard. I do not see how..
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Ah, I see! A voyager lacks sentience, and so lacks the ability to observe its surroundings on its own..
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: That said, it is rather tiresome waiting within the Sanctuary for the quantum shard to return.. I wish it wasn't only able to travel inside under the cover of darkness!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	

<ShipLogConditions>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Nomai Mine Entry 2</FactID>
			<Condition>8</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>