<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Oeno, I request urgent assistance in locating a native lifeform that has escaped the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary!</color>]]>!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: The quantum shard slipped from my sight when I disengaged my voyager stone by accident earlier.. When the shard returned, the lifeform that was resting on it was gone!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		OENO: We must locate this missing lifeform before the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project</color>]]> begins; the Sanctuary is their only protection from the supernova if the project fails!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: I have located and delivered the escaped lifeform back into the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary,</color>]]> Cycad! Please watch over them with great care.
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: But Cycad, you should be able to travel using the quantum shard too, even as a voyager! If any more escapes occur, I implore you to take matters into your own hands.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: But the surface of the planet is never completely dark enough to allow a conscious individual to travel to it using the quantum shard! I do not see how...
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Oh, I see how I can travel outside now! A voyager lacks the ability to observe its surroundings on its own!
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: I only wish the quantum shard didn't require a cover of darkness to visit the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary!</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	

<ShipLogConditions>
			<RevealFact>
				<FactID>SY EX1</FactID>
				<Condition>3</Condition>
			</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
				<FactID>SY EX3</FactID>
				<Condition>7</Condition>
			</RevealFact>
				<RevealFact>
				<FactID>SY EX4</FactID>
				<Condition>8</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>