<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Oeno, I hope this scroll reaches you on the quantum shard: I request urgent assistance in locating a native lifeform that has escaped the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary!!</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: I disengaged my voyager stone by accident earlier, causing the quantum shard to slip from my sight - along with one of the native species resting on it!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CYCAD: When I regained connection to the voyager, the quantum shard was there, but the lifeform on it was gone!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: We must find it before the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project</color>]]> begins; the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary</color>]]> is their only protection during the operation of the project!
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: I have delivered the lifeform back to you, Cycad. But, Cycad.. Are you not aware the voyager is capable of using the rule of quantum entanglement as well?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: But Oeno, isn't the surface of the planet too bright for one to use the rule of quantum entanglement (unlike these slumbering species)?
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: Come now, Cycad. Did you not notice what caused the quantum shard to move earlier?
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: I see.. A voyager is unable to observe its surroundings on its own. You have my gratitude, Oeno!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	

<ShipLogConditions>
			<RevealFact>
				<FactID>SY EX1</FactID>
				<Condition>3</Condition>
			</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
				<FactID>SY EX3</FactID>
				<Condition>8</Condition>
			</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
				<FactID>SY EX4</FactID>
				<Condition>8</Condition>
			</RevealFact>
</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>