<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		DAZ: Phlox, when you have time to spare after toiling away at your statues, I would deeply appreciate if you could deliver more flat templates soon to the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Scroll and Stone Workshop</color>]]> upstairs!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: I would be happy to! I always enjoy the simplicity of sculpting these templates. But did I not already deliver you several stacks recently?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		DAZ: The voyager stone's development is nearing completion! I require more templates to craft and test more projection locations, before I can be confident in its use.
			</Text>
	</TextBlock>
			<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		DAZ: You should pair with a memory statue to test the voyager stones sometime as well, Phlox!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
				<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PHLOX: Oh! I was not aware I needed to be paired to a memory statue to use them. Is there a reason for this prerequisite?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		DAZ: The voyager stones are designed to work with our memory storage system for the memory statues, recording and transmitting experiences from the projection pool back to the individual.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		DAZ: That is how the voyager stone allows one to explore remotely beyond a projection pool!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		DAZ: Without the individual being first paired to a memory statue, I'm afraid the voyager stone would be little more than any ordinary projection stone in function.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Workshop R4</FactID>
			<Condition>6</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

	
</NomaiObject>