<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		DAZ: These new storm shelters are incredible, Thatch! I have never felt safer visiting <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Giant's Deep</color>]]> in their presence!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		THATCH: I feel the same way, Daz! We owe Kousa at the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Gravity Crystal Workshop</color>]]> much gratitude for engineering this incredible invention to keep us safe.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		DAZ: Hm..? Why has the storm shelter suddenly activated? There are no cyclones near the island at the moment.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		DAZ: How strange.. The storm shelters should only activate in the presence of cyclones, should they not? Could this storm shelter be defective?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		THATCH: No, the issue does not seem unique to this unit alone; all the storm shelters on the island seem to have activated for some erroneous reason!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		THATCH: Unfortunately, I do not know much about the mechanisms of this device.. It was not long ago we Nomai on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Giant's Deep</color>]]> were completely insulated from cyclones in the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Looming City,</color>]]> you see.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		THATCH: When I next travel home, I shall pay a visit to the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Gravity Crystal Workshop</color>]]> on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow</color>]]> to learn more about the storm shelter, and shed light on this issue!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
	
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC R1</FactID>
			<Condition>6</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>GSHOP R2</FactID>
			<Condition>7</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Pioneer EX3.5</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>