<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Friends, we have successfully completed the excavation of the core of Giant's Deep. With this, the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Deep Storm Station</color>]]> takes its first step towards realization!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		AVENS: I expected zero-g at the center of a planet to feel quite different from zero-g in space, but it does not feel dissimilar to working aboard the cannon! Wouldn't you agree, Mallow?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: I would appreciate if both of you would kindly focus on the task of reinforcing the station's walls! We are surrounded by <![CDATA[<i>oceans</i>]]> of pressure; we must fortify the station's integrity with great care!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: Daz, I'm almost done installing the new warp receiver within the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Deep Storm Station.</color>]]> Once it is ready, it should connect us with the warp transmitter on the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Construction Yard!</color>]]>
</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: Of note: as we have sealed ourselves in this space, we will require somebody to warp to our warp receiver to charge a return warp that will allow us to return to the surface!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		DAZ: Have no fear, Clary; I am already waiting on the warp transmitter, eager to see my Cassava again!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationAB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: You have my gratitude, Daz! The return warp will be most useful in allowing me to excuse myself, before I become trapped in the station with <![CDATA[<i>two</i>]]> pairs of gelatinous Nomai.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>DSS CONV3</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>