<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: The Inspired has completed its orbit around the star system, collecting as much of the deadly matter as it is safely able to.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: When I give the order, all deadly matter collected by the Inspired will be warped to its sibling warp core here.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: If everything goes as planned, the deadly matter should be completely contained by the deep oceans surrounding the Deep Storm Station, sealing it away indefinitely.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: I have ordered the Inspired to remain in stationary orbit around Giant's Deep. Should containment fail in my absence, I pray that the Inspired will trap any ghost matter that leaks out.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: And finally, I have delivered the native species of Timber Hearth (kept safe within the Sanctuary) back to the decontaminated surface of the planet using my voyager.
</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: My dearest hope.. is that these species will be able to live on to learn from the universe in our stead.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: I only wish I could see all the amazing discoveries they might make..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: ...I am ready.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: My friends.. Daz.. I cannot wait to join all of you.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: The universe is... And we shall all become one within it!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>DSS EX4</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>DSS EX5</FactID>
			<Condition>3</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>DSS EX6</FactID>
			<Condition>11</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>INSP R4</FactID>
			<Condition>3</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>