<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: I have gathered as much of the deadly matter from across the star system as I am safely able to.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: When the order is given, the collected deadly matter will be warped into this space.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: If everything goes as planned, the deadly matter should be completely contained by the deep oceans surrounding the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Deep Storm Station,</color>]]> sealing it away indefinitely.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: I have ordered the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Inspired</color>]]> to remain in stationary orbit around <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Giant's Deep..</color>]]> Should this containment fail, I pray that it will catch any matter that leaks out.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: But before I give the order, I have released the species within the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary</color>]]> back to the surface using my voyager.
</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: It is my dearest hope that these species will continue to grow and learn from the universe in our stead.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: I only wish we could have been a part of their journey..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Now, all that remains is to collapse the innumerable possibilities before me.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: My friends.. Daz.. I cannot wait to be with you again.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: The universe is.. and we are now one with it.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>DSS EX5</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

<RevealFact>
			<FactID>INSP EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>INSP EX7</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>