<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	Clue: There is another QM locator on BH and you can learn to use the rule of imaging from afar there?

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		COLEUS: Melorae, are you ready? We are about to begin our first expedition to the Quantum Moon!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		MELORAE: Of course, Coleus. I have looked forward to this expedition ever since our reunion with our friends on Brittle Hollow, and learning of our shared passion for this wandering moon!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		MELORAE: But.. where is Thatch? He was supposed to travel here from Brittle Hollow to meet with us at the Quantum Moon Locator before we set off, was he not?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: We have waited for some time, but Thatch has still not arrived. Could your nephew have lost his way, Melorae? Or..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: Could he have confused our instructions for another <![CDATA[<color=orange>Quantum Moon Locator?</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		MELORAE: But Coleus, this is the only Quantum Moon Locator we know of! Unless..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		MELORAE: Could our friends on Brittle Hollow have built a second Quantum Moon Locator we were not aware of?  
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: That is likely.. Our friends on Brittle Hollow would have surely come up with a similar plan to track a wandering moon.. Though I am deeply curious how differently their locator might function from ours!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>	
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: Perhaps they might even have devised a way to track where the Quantum Moon goes when it disappears completely!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<Text>
		MELORAE: How you make my heart flutter with possibilities, Coleus!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<Text>
		MELORAE: Seeing as we cannot begin the expedition without him, we should travel to Brittle Hollow to try to find Thatch.. as well as to seek out this hypothetical second <![CDATA[<color=orange>Quantum Moon Locator!</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>BH_QML R1</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>R_SLR R3</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>BH_QML R3</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>