<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	Clue: There is another QM locator on BH and you can learn to use the rule of imaging from afar there?

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		COLEUS: Melorae, are you ready? We are finally ready to begin our first expedition to the Quantum Moon!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		MELORAE: Of course I am, Coleus! I have looked forward to this fateful expedition for so long!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		MELORAE: Where is Thatch? We agreed to meet here at the Quantum Moon Locator before we set off, did we not? He is running late!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: We have waited some time, but Thatch has still not arrived. Could he have lost his way? Or..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: Could he have confused our instructions for another <![CDATA[<color=orange>Quantum Moon Locator?</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		MELORAE: But Coleus, this is the only Quantum Moon Locator on the Hourglass Twins! Unless... Could our friends on Brittle Hollow have had the same idea to build a Quantum Moon Locator before our reunion?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: We cannot proceed with this expedition without Thatch. It would not be safe to conduct the expedition without  
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		SOLANUM: If time allows, I shall try to find this second <![CDATA[<color=orange>Quantum Moon Locator</color>]]> on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow</color>]]> to learn its secrets!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>BH_QML R1</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>R_SLR R3</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>BH_QML R3</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>