<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
    <ID>BRITTLE_HOLLOW</ID>


<Entry>
        <ID>BH_HIGHWAY</ID>
        <Name>Artificial Gravity Highway</Name>
        <Curiosity>None</Curiosity>
         
         <RumorFact>
            <ID>BH_H R1</ID>
            <RumorName>Storm Shelter Invitation</RumorName>
            <Text>A Nomai named Kousa left a scroll in the Hanging City that goes into more detail about the storm shelter.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>

        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>BH_H EX1</ID> 
            <Text>A pair of artificial gravity highways that allows one to ascend the Hanging City's districts.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>BH_H EX2</ID>
            <Text>I found a conversation detailing the incomplete construction of the White Hole Station. Its warp receiver was planned to be constructed on the surface above the Hanging City.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>BH_H EX3</ID>
            <Text>A warp transmitter requires a connected warp receiver to function.</Text> 
     </ExploreFact>

         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>BH_H EX4</ID> 
            <Text>Storm shelters were engineered to protect Nomai on an expedition to Giant's Deep, by generating a gravity field when islands are lifted into space.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
            <ExploreFact>
            <ID>BH_H EX5</ID> 
            <Text>The Sunless City contributed to the invention of the storm shelter, allowing the device to autonomously power on and off.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
      
</Entry>

<Entry>
        <ID>BH_WORKSHOP</ID>
        <Name>Gravity Crystal Workshop</Name>
        <Curiosity>None</Curiosity>
         
         <RumorFact>
            <ID>GSHOP R1</ID>
            <SourceID>CONSTRUCT_BAY</SourceID>
            <Text>Gravity crystals used to build the Orbital Probe Cannon were sourced from this workshop on Brittle Hollow.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
            <ID>GSHOP R2</ID>
            <Text>The Nomai on Giant's Deep visited this workshop on Brittle Hollow's equator to inquire about storm shelters activating in the absence of cyclones.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>

        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>GSHOP EX1</ID> 
            <Text>Gravity crystals were crafted from fragments of Brittle Hollow's crust and stored at this workshop.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>GSHOP EX2</ID> 
            <Text>An invention called the storm shelter was engineered at this workshop to help Nomai weather storms on their expedition.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
 <ExploreFact>
            <ID>GSHOP EX3</ID>
            <Text>Storm shelters are powered by solar panels, not cyclones.</Text> 
     </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>GSHOP EX4</ID> 
            <Text>Nomai on Giant's Deep reported some sort of issue with the storm shelter when the sun was directly overhead.</Text> 
             <AltText>
                         <Text>The solar panels powering the storm shelters are tuned to detect even faint amounts of sunlight, causing storm shelters to activate when the sun is directly overhead.</Text>
                         <Condition>GSHOP R2</Condition>
                    </AltText>
        </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>GSHOP EX5</ID> 
            <Text>Feldspar discovered gravity crystals here on their first expedition into space. They wanted to bring one home, but were unable to find any available crystals at this site.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
      
</Entry>


</AstroObjectEntry>