<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
    <ID>DARK_BRAMBLE</ID>


<Entry>
        <ID>DB_FROZENGUYS</ID>
        <Name>Bramble Expedition</Name>
        <Curiosity>None</Curiosity>
         
         <RumorFact>
            <ID>DBG R1</ID>
             <SourceID>LOOMINGCITY</SourceID>
            <Text>The Nomai planned to conduct a survey expedition to Dark Bramble's north pole in search of survivors.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
      <RumorFact>
            <ID>DBG R2</ID>
            <Text>The Nomai found frozen species inside this glacier on the underside of Dark Bramble's north pole.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
     
     
 <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DBG EX0</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai mourned their failure in locating their missing friends on an expedition to Dark Bramble's exterior. They debated whether or not to attempt more expeditions into the bramble.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DBG EX1</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Cassava made a discovery on this expedition. There are platforms on the side of the glacier leading to what he found.</Text>
             <AltText>
                         <Text>The Nomai found several species frozen inside the glacier on the underside of Dark Bramble's north pole.</Text>
                         <Condition>DBG R2</Condition>
                    </AltText> 
        </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DBG EX2</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai hypothesized that these species originated within the frozen planet, and were launched within shards of ice to the planets that became their new habitats.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
      
</Entry>



<Entry>
        <ID>DB_ANGLERNEST</ID>
        <Name>Anglerfish Nest</Name>
        <Curiosity>Vessel</Curiosity>
         
        <RumorFact>
            <ID>DBA R1</ID>
            <Text>A Nomai named Plume considered locating an anglerfish nest inside Dark Bramble to cull the countless hordes of anglerfish within the bramble, but was dissuaded from the idea.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
            <ID>DBA R2</ID>
             <SourceID>DB_VESSEL</SourceID>
            <Text>A Nomai named Keek discovered this anglerfish nest while trying to reach the Vessel.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>

        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DBA EX1</ID> 
            <Text>A cluster of anglerfish eggs guarded fiercely by anglerfish deep within Dark Bramble.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DBA EX2</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Keek discovered this nest on a desperate mission to reach the Vessel. Keek.. met a gruesome end.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DBA EX3</ID>
            <Text>Keek noted that the eggs were warm, gelatinous, and filled with liquid.</Text> 
     </ExploreFact>
     
      
</Entry>



</AstroObjectEntry>