<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
    <ID>DARK_BRAMBLE</ID>


<Entry>
        <ID>DB_FROZENGUYS</ID>
        <Name>Bramble Campsite</Name>
        <Curiosity>None</Curiosity>
         
         <RumorFact>
            <ID>DBG R1</ID>
             <SourceID>LOOMINGCITY</SourceID>
            <RumorName>Bramble Expedition</RumorName>
             <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <Text>The Nomai planned to conduct a survey expedition to Dark Bramble's north pole in search of survivors.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
     
 <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DBG EX0</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai were unable to locate any survivors on Dark Bramble's exterior. They decided against further expeditions into the bramble due to their limited methods of travel.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
           <ID>DBG EX0.5</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai reported seeing countless hordes of anglerfish inside the bramble.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
           <ID>DBG EX1</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Plume proposed locating an anglerfish nest inside Dark Bramble to cull the anglerfish's population, but was strongly dissuaded from this plan as it would endanger the native species.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>

        <Entry>      
              <ID>DB_FROZENGUYS_2</ID>
               <Name>Ancient Glacier</Name>
              <Curiosity>None</Curiosity>

        <RumorFact>
            <ID>DBF R1</ID>
            <RumorName>Glacier Discovery</RumorName>
            <Text>The Nomai discovered something during their final expedition of Dark Bramble's exterior. They constructed platforms on the side of the northern glacier to guide each other to this discovery.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DBF EX1</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai found several species frozen inside this glacier on the underside of Dark Bramble's north pole.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DBF EX2</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai hypothesized that these species must have originated within the frozen planet, and were launched within shards of ice to the planets that would become their new habitats.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
      </Entry>
</Entry>




<Entry>
        <ID>DB_ANGLERNEST</ID>
        <Name>Anglerfish Nest</Name>
        <Curiosity>Vessel</Curiosity>
         
       <RumorFact>
            <ID>DBA R1</ID>
            <Text>A Nomai named Plume speculated about the existence of an anglerfish nest inside Dark Bramble.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
            <ID>DBA R2</ID>
             <SourceID>DB_VESSEL</SourceID>
            <Text>A Nomai named Keek discovered this anglerfish nest while trying to reach the Vessel.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>

        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DBA EX1</ID> 
            <Text>A cluster of anglerfish eggs guarded fiercely by anglerfish deep within Dark Bramble.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DBA EX2</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Keek discovered this nest on a desperate mission to reach the Vessel before they were cornered by anglerfish. They met a gruesome end.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DBA EX3</ID>
            <Text>Keek noted that the anglerfish eggs were warm, gelatinous, and filled with liquid.</Text> 
     </ExploreFact>
     
      
</Entry>

</AstroObjectEntry>