<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
    <ID>GIANTS_DEEP</ID>



<Entry>


       <ID>SCROLL_WORKSHOP</ID>
        <Name>Scroll and Stone Workshop</Name>
        <Curiosity>STOWAWAYS</Curiosity>
 
        <RumorFact>
            <ID>Workshop R1</ID>
             <SourceID>TH_CAMPSITE</SourceID>
            <Text>A new invention from the Scroll and Stone Workshop on Giant's Deep provides convenient entry into the Sanctuary.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
              <SourceID>GD_STATUE_ISLAND</SourceID>
            <ID>Workshop R2</ID>
            <Text>Projection stones for the Orbital Probe Cannon were crafted at a workshop on Statue Island.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
              <SourceID>GD_STATUE_ISLAND</SourceID>
            <ID>Workshop R3</ID>
            <Text>Nomai scrolls and projection stones were crafted at this workshop on Statue Island.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
             <RumorFact>
            <ID>Workshop R4</ID>
            <Text>A new type of projection stone used the memory storage systems to allow paired Nomai to explore remotely beyond projection pools.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
            <RumorFact>
            <ID>Workshop R5</ID>
            <Text>Projection stones were crafted at the Scroll and Stone Workshop.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Workshop EX1</ID> 
            <Text>Nomai scrolls and projection stones were crafted at this workshop on Statue Island.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Workshop EX1.5</ID> 
            <Text>A new type of projection stone called the voyager stone was developed at this workshop.</Text>
            <AltText>
                      <Text>A new type of projection stone called the voyager stone was developed at this workshop. This new type of projection stone would use memory storage systems to allow Nomai to explore remotely beyond projection pools.</Text>
                      <Condition>Workshop R4</Condition>
            </AltText>
        </ExploreFact>
           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Workshop EX2.5</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Daz used a voyager stone to rescue a jellyfish beached on the shore without being shocked.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Workshop EX3</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Oeno noticed her voyages beginning outside the projection pool while using a voyager stone, and experienced a strange telepathic connection with another Nomai using a voyager stone.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>

    <Entry>
       <ID>SCROLL_WORKSHOP_TOP</ID>
        <Name>Workshop Loft</Name>
        <Curiosity>STOWAWAYS</Curiosity>
          <RumorFact>
            <ID>WorkshopTop R1</ID>
            <Text>There is a second floor of the Scroll and Stone Workshop, but it seems too high to reach. A Nomai elevator blocks the doorway.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
            <RumorFact>
            <ID>WorkshopTop R2</ID>
            <Text>A voyager stone to the Sanctuary may be found at the Scroll and Stone Workshop.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>

         
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>WorkshopTop EX1</ID> 
            <Text>When disconnected, the memory storage system allows a voyager to remain on standby, returning a voyage to that position once reengaged.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>WorkshopTop EX2</ID> 
            <Text>Voyaging to the same destination from the same projection pool causes multiple memory storage systems to be connected to the same voyager, creating a stream of shared consciousness.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>WorkshopTop EX3</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Daz was cut off while writing to the Deep Storm Station from the Scroll and Stone Workshop.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>WorkshopTop EX4</ID> 
            <Text>Conversations shared across projection stones are not stored on the stones themselves, but on the projection walls they were written on.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
             <ExploreFact>
            <ID>WorkshopTop EX5</ID> 
            <Text>A single projection stone can unlock many conversations across different projection walls.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        </Entry>
</Entry>

///


<Entry>
       <ID>BISLE_STUDY</ID>
        <Name>Backshore Study Site</Name>
        <Curiosity>None</Curiosity>
 
           <RumorFact>
            <ID>Study R1</ID>
            <RumorName>Jellyfish Study Site</RumorName>
            <Text>A group of Nomai discovered frozen jellyfish on this island. They decided to find higher elevation to be safe from the waves while studying them.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        <RumorFact>
            <ID>Study R2</ID>
            <RumorName>Jellyfish Study Site</RumorName>
            <Text>The Nomai transported a frozen jellyfish from this island to the Looming City.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Study EX1</ID> 
            <Text>A high shore on Bramble Island safe from waves, where the Nomai studied frozen jellyfish.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Study EX2</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai transported a frozen jellyfish from this island back to the Looming City to investigate why they had stopped coming to the surface of the ocean.</Text> 
         </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Study EX3</ID> 
            <Text>Nomai at this site noticed Giant's Deep becoming completely dark, before what appeared to be a giant column of water launched the island into space.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>
</Entry>
      


///





<Entry>
        <ID>PIONEER_BEACH</ID>
        <Name>Pioneers' Beach</Name>
       <Curiosity>None</Curiosity>

       

         
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Pioneer EX1</ID> 
            <Text>This camp sheltered Nomai during their first survey expedition to Giant's Deep.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Pioneer EX2</ID> 
            <Text>The expedition team moved their supplies into the island's interior for shelter.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
             <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Pioneer EX3B</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai recorded their first encounter with a cyclone here. A Nomai named Thatch complained about becoming soaked when the island plunged back into the ocean.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Pioneer EX3</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Melorae stressed the importance of protecting themselves from cyclones, or seeking a landmass clear of the cyclones' path entirely.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
           <ID>Pioneer EX3.5</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Daz noticed storm shelters powering on by themselves, even in the absence of cyclones.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Pioneer EX4</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai discovered jellyfish on the surface of Giant's Deep.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
</Entry>




///



 <Entry>
       <ID>CONSTRUCT_BAY</ID>
        <Name>Construction Bay</Name>
        <Curiosity>STOWAWAYS</Curiosity>

        <ExploreFact>
           <ID>CB_EX1</ID> 
            <Text>A bay on one side of the Construction Yard flooded with ghost matter.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
               <ExploreFact>
            <ID>CB_EX2A</ID> 
            <Text>I found schematics for something called the Orbital Probe Cannon.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
               <ExploreFact>
            <ID>CB_EX2</ID> 
            <Text>I found schematics for something called the Inspired.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>CB_EX4</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Cassava observed ghost matter being temporarily neutralized by water. He traveled to Timber Hearth to study another property of ghost matter he noticed.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>

             <ExploreFact>
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>CB_EX5</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai excavated the core of Giant's Deep to construct the Deep Storm Station. They asked Nomai at the Construction Yard to use the warp pad there to warp in, to charge a return warp that would allow them to return to the surface.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
</Entry>

///



<Entry>
        <ID>LOVERSCOVE</ID>
        <Name>Lovers' Cove</Name>
        <Curiosity>STOWAWAYS</Curiosity>
        <RumorFact>
            <ID>Cove R1</ID> 
             <RumorName>Ghost Matter Cove</RumorName>
            <Text>There is a small cove on Gabbro's Island guarded by ghost matter.</Text>
        </RumorFact>
        <RumorFact>
            <ID>Cove R2</ID> 
             <RumorName>Ghost Matter Cove</RumorName>
            <Text>Gabbro made a second campfire outside this cove, but abandoned it after finding the waves were washing high enough to extinguish it.</Text>
        </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
            <ID>Cove R3</ID>
             <RumorName>Ghost Matter Cove</RumorName>
            <Text>A Nomai named Daz tested a new type of projection stone with a Nomai named Cassava on this island. During this test, his voyager disappeared without warning, to Cassava’s alarm.</Text>
        </RumorFact>

         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Cove EX1</ID> 
            <Text>A small cove inside Gabbro's Island filled with ghost matter.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Cove EX2</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Daz proposed to a Nomai named Cassava in this cove! Strangely, Daz appeared to celebrate Cassava's acceptance before receiving an answer.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>Cove EX3</ID> 
            <Text>While sharing joyous news of his engagement, Daz revealed that he had proposed to Cassava during a 6-second negative time interval.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Cove EX4</ID> 
            <Text>According to a Nomai named Cassava, days last shorter on Gabbro's Island and Statue Island.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
             <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Cove EX5</ID> 
            <Text>As the sun orbits overhead, its gravity causes waves to wash higher on the island, washing high enough to dissolve voyagers.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
 </Entry>





<Entry>
        <ID>LOOMINGCITY</ID>
        <Name>Looming City</Name>
        <Curiosity>None</Curiosity>

            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>

         <RumorFact>
            <ID>LC R1</ID> 
            <SourceID>CONSTRUCT_BAY</SourceID>
            <Text>The Nomai on Giant's Deep used to be completely insulated from cyclones in the Looming City.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
          <RumorFact>
            <ID>LC R2</ID> 
            <SourceID>BISLE_STUDY</SourceID>
            <Text>The Nomai transported a frozen jellyfish from Bramble Island to a habitat in the Looming City for research.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
          <RumorFact>
            <ID>LC R3</ID> 
            <SourceID>BISLE_STUDY</SourceID>
            <Text>The Nomai were curious about how the jellyfish would interact with the quantum shard in the Looming City.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
          <RumorFact>
            <ID>LC R4</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai abandoned this tower after a quantum shard caused its interior to become inhospitably quantum.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>


        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LC EX1</ID>
                  <Text>A great tower that once served as a Nomai settlement, built on an island within the eye of the hurricane.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LC EX4</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai abandoned this tower due to extenuating circumstances, chronicled in scrolls within the tower.</Text> 
                 <AltText>
                      <Text>The Nomai abandoned this tower after a quantum shard made it inhospitable. They moved to the island they found on their first expedition, and noted another island as a potential construction site.</Text>
                     <Condition>LC R4</Condition>
                 </AltText>
        </ExploreFact>
           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LC EX4.5</ID> 
            <Text>This second island was noted to sail in the opposite direction, making its days three times longer than the first island.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>

          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LC EX2</ID> 
            <Text>Objects left on a quantum shard will travel with the shard.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LC EX3</ID> 
            <Text>Giant's Deep's thick clouds completely obscure sight of anything outside the planet.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LC EX5</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai transported a frozen jellyfish here from Bramble Island in hopes of studying jellyfish behavior.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>

    <Entry>
           <ID>LOOMINGCITY_JELLY</ID>
        <Name>Cerberus' Pool</Name>
        <Curiosity>None</Curiosity>

          <RumorFact>
            <RumorName>Jellyfish Habitat</RumorName>
                        <RumorNamePriority>1</RumorNamePriority>
            <ID>LCJ R1</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai constructed a jellyfish habitat at the Looming City to conduct further research into them.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        <RumorFact>
            <ID>LCJ R2</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Solanum lost a scroll from the tower in this pool. A jellyfish at the bottom of the pool is blocking the scroll with electrifying tentacles.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LCJ EX1</ID> 
            <Text>A pool under the Looming City that houses a jellyfish the Nomai studied. A scroll sits at the bottom of the pool, guarded by the jellyfish.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LCJ EX2</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai discovered that jellyfish are drawn to the surface of the ocean by the Quantum Moon's gravity.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LCJ EX3</ID> 
            <Text>Leaving a pair of eyes at the Quantum Moon Locator allows one to consistently know where the Quantum Moon is.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
    </Entry>
</Entry>




<Entry>
   <ID>DEEP_STORM_STATION</ID>
        <Name>Deep Storm Station</Name>

        <Curiosity>STOWAWAYS</Curiosity>
		<IsCuriosity/>

      <RumorFact>
            <RumorName>Deepest Space</RumorName>
            <ID>DSS Probe</ID> 
            <Text>My scout was warped somewhere into a space with glowing masks and wires. It appears to be flooded with ghost matter.</Text>
    </RumorFact>
    <RumorFact>
            <ID>DSS R2</ID>
             <RumorName>Deep Storm Station</RumorName>
             <RumorNamePriority>1</RumorNamePriority>
            <Text>I was able to enter the Deep Storm Station using a voyager stone. The gravity on this part of the station is too strong for me to jump to the other side.</Text> 
    </RumorFact>
    <RumorFact>
             <ID>DSS R3</ID> 
            <RumorName>Deep Storm Station</RumorName>
             <RumorNamePriority>1</RumorNamePriority>
            <Text>Two Nomai named Pye and Idaea tried to warp to the Deep Storm Station, but arrived on Statue Island instead. They returned to Ash Twin, seeking guidance.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        
     <RumorFact>
                  <ID>CONV R1</ID> 
                     <SourceID>TT_TIME_LOOP_DEVICE</SourceID>
                 <Text>The Deep Storm Station powered a 6-second negative time interval to test the mechanics of the Ash Twin Project.</Text> 
    </RumorFact>
    <RumorFact>
                 <ID>CONV R2</ID> 
               <SourceID>LOVERSCOVE</SourceID>
            <Text>While sharing joyous news of his engagement with the Deep Storm Station, Daz revealed that he had proposed to Cassava during a 6-second negative time interval.</Text> 
    </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
                 <ID>CONV R3</ID> 
               <SourceID>GD_CONSTRUCTION_YARD</SourceID>
            <Text>The Nomai excavated the core of Giant's Deep to construct the Deep Storm Station. They asked Nomai at the Construction Yard to warp in, to charge a return warp that would allow them to return to the surface.</Text> 
    </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
                 <ID>CONV R4</ID> 
               <SourceID>SCROLL_WORKSHOP</SourceID>
            <Text>A Nomai named Daz was cut off while writing to the Deep Storm Station from the Scroll and Stone Workshop.</Text> 
    </RumorFact>
   

   

        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS EX1</ID> 
            <Text>An underwater station built at the heart of Giant's Deep.</Text>
                  <AltText>
                        <Text>An underwater station at the heart of Giant's Deep, built to test the mechanics of the Ash Twin Project using energy from the planet's electric core.</Text>
                        <Condition>CONV R1</Condition>
                 </AltText>
        </ExploreFact>

           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS EX2</ID> 
            <Text>There are eight monoliths with Nomai masks attached. Two of the masks are lit up.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
  
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS EX3</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Cassava was protected from some sort of danger aboard the Deep Storm Station, and used voyager stones to travel outside the station safely.</Text>
            <AltText>
                <Text>A Nomai named Cassava survived the arrival of ghost matter in the star system aboard the Deep Storm Station, and used voyager stones to travel outside the station safely.</Text>
                <Condition>COMET_INTERIOR_X1</Condition>
            </AltText>
        </ExploreFact>
        
  <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS EX3.5</ID> 
            <Text>Cassava took great care to never keep the Quantum Moon locked in orbit around Giant's Deep for extended periods of time.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>

         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS EX4</ID> 
            <Text>Cassava released the species within the Sanctuary back to the surface using his voyager.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS EX5</ID> 
            <Text>Cassava gathered much of the ghost matter in the star system and warped it into the Deep Storm Station, to contain it at the cost of his own life.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>
    
             <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS EX6</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai known as Cassava met his end praying for the future of the native species, wishing the Nomai could have been part of their journey.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>

</Entry>




</AstroObjectEntry>