<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
    <ID>GIANTS_DEEP</ID>



<Entry>


       <ID>SCROLL_WORKSHOP</ID>
        <Name>Scroll and Stone Workshop</Name>
        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
 
        <RumorFact>
            <ID>Workshop R1</ID>
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
             <SourceID>TH_CAMPSITE</SourceID>
            <Text>A new invention from the Scroll and Stone Workshop on Giant's Deep provides convenient entry into the Sanctuary.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
            <ID>Workshop R2</ID>
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <Text>A Nomai named Daz was cut off while writing to the Deep Storm Station from the Scroll and Stone Workshop.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>Workshop R3</ID>
            <Text>Projection stones were crafted at this workshop.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
             <RumorFact>
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>Workshop R4</ID>
            <Text>A new invention from this workshop allowed Nomai to walk beyond a projection pool.</Text>
        </RumorFact>
           <RumorFact>
            <ID>Workshop R5</ID>
              <SourceID>GD_STATUE_ISLAND</SourceID>
            <Text>A new type of projection stone used the memory storage systems to allow paired Nomai to explore remotely beyond projection pools.</Text>
        </RumorFact>
        
        
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Workshop EX1</ID> 
            <Text>Nomai scrolls and projection stones were crafted at this workshop on Statue Island.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Workshop EX1.5</ID> 
            <Text>A new type of projection stone called the voyager stone was developed at this workshop.</Text>
            <AltText>
                      <Text>A new type of projection stone called the voyager stone was developed at this workshop. This new type of projection stone would use memory storage systems to allow Nomai to explore remotely beyond projection pools.</Text>
                      <Condition>Workshop R5</Condition>
            </AltText>
        </ExploreFact>
           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Workshop EX2.5</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Daz used a voyager stone to rescue a jellyfish beached on the shore without being shocked.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>

    <Entry>
       <ID>SCROLL_WORKSHOP_TOP</ID>
        <Name>Workshop Loft</Name>
        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
          <RumorFact>
            <ID>WorkshopTop R1</ID>
            <Text>There is a second floor of the Scroll and Stone Workshop, but it is too high to reach. The doorway is blocked by a downward-traveling Nomai elevator.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
            <RumorFact>
            <ID>WorkshopTop R2</ID>
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <Text>A voyager stone to the Sanctuary may be found in the loft of the Scroll and Stone Workshop.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>

         
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>WorkshopTop EX1</ID> 
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <Text>I spoke to the memory of a dead Nomai named Daz!</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>WorkshopTop EX1.5</ID> 
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <Text>Daz believes his essence has been preserved within his memory mask in the Deep Storm Station, but doubts he is fully alive.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>WorkshopTop EX2</ID> 
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <Text>Entering an active projection pool causes multiple memory storage systems to be connected to the same voyager, creating a stream of shared consciousness and thought.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>WorkshopTop EX2.5</ID> 
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <Text>Daz wishes he could have seen our village back home on Timber Hearth.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>WorkshopTop EX3</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Daz was cut off while writing to the Deep Storm Station from the Scroll and Stone Workshop.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>WorkshopTop EX4</ID> 
            <Text>Conversations shared across projection stones are not stored on the stones themselves, but on the projection walls they were written on.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
             <ExploreFact>
            <ID>WorkshopTop EX5</ID> 
            <Text>A single projection stone can unlock many conversations across different projection walls.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        </Entry>
</Entry>

///


<Entry>
       <ID>BISLE_STUDY</ID>
        <Name>Backshore Study Site</Name>
        <Curiosity>None</Curiosity>
 
           <RumorFact>
            <ID>Study R1</ID>
            <RumorName>Jellyfish Study Site</RumorName>
            <Text>The Nomai discovered frozen jellyfish on this island. They decided to seek higher elevation on the island safe from waves to study them.</Text>
        </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
            <ID>Study R2</ID>
            <Text>Nomai at this site noticed Giant's Deep becoming completely dark, before what appeared to be a giant column of water launched the island into space.</Text>
        </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
            <ID>Study R3</ID>
             <RumorName>Jellyfish Specimen Origins</RumorName>
            <Text>The jellyfish at the Looming City was transported there by the Nomai from Bramble Island.</Text>
        </RumorFact>
        
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Study EX1</ID> 
            <Text>A high shore on Bramble Island safe from waves, where the Nomai studied frozen jellyfish.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Study EX2</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai transported a frozen jellyfish from this island back to the Looming City to investigate why they had stopped coming to the surface of the ocean.</Text> 
         </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Study EX3</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Melorae was cut off after seeing the sky become dark.</Text>
             <AltText>
                         <Text>Nomai at this site noticed Giant's Deep becoming completely dark, before what appeared to be a giant column of water launched the island into space.</Text>
                         <Condition>Study R2</Condition> 
               </AltText>
        </ExploreFact>
</Entry>
      


///





<Entry>
        <ID>PIONEER_BEACH</ID>
        <Name>Pioneers' Beach</Name>
       <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>

       

         
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Pioneer EX1</ID> 
            <Text>This beach was where Nomai landed on their first survey expedition to Giant's Deep, before they moved their supplies into the island's interior for shelter.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Pioneer EX4</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai encountered jellyfish on the surface of Giant's Deep.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
             <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Pioneer EX3B</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai recorded their first encounter with a cyclone here. A Nomai named Thatch complained about becoming soaked when the island plunged back into the ocean.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Pioneer EX3</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai looked for ways to protect themselves from cyclones, as well as landmasses clear of the cyclones' path.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
           <ID>Pioneer EX3.5</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai noticed the island's storm shelters powering on by themselves, even in the absence of cyclones.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
</Entry>




///



 <Entry>
       <ID>CONSTRUCT_BAY</ID>
        <Name>Construction Bay</Name>
        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>

    <RumorFact>
    <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
                 <ID>CB_R1</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai working aboard the Deep Storm Station wrote to the Construction Yard, asking for help in charging a return warp that would allow them to return to the surface.</Text> 
    </RumorFact>

        <ExploreFact>
           <ID>CB_EX1</ID> 
            <Text>The lower bay of the Construction Yard. One side is flooded with ghost matter.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
               <ExploreFact>
            <ID>CB_EX2A</ID> 
            <Text>I found schematics for something called the Orbital Probe Cannon. A Nomai named Privet mistook the purpose of a new warp transmitter on Giant's Deep for travel to the Orbital Probe Cannon.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
               <ExploreFact>
            <ID>CB_EX2</ID> 
            <Text>I found schematics for something called the Inspired.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>CB_EX3</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Cassava observed ghost matter being temporarily neutralized when it was immersed by the waves washing onto the island. He posited that ghost matter was unable to penetrate water.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>CB_EX4</ID> 
            <Text>Cassava traveled to Timber Hearth to investigate a second property of ghost matter.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        

             <ExploreFact>
            <ID>CB_EX5</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Cassava decided to run more launches using an alternate power source. He asked Nomai seeking him to use the Construction Yard's projection wall.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        
</Entry>

///



<Entry>
        <ID>LOVERSCOVE</ID>
        <Name>Lovers' Cove</Name>
        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
        <RumorFact>
            <ID>Cove R1</ID> 
             <RumorName>Ghost Matter Cove</RumorName>
            <Text>There is a small cove on Gabbro's Island flooded by ghost matter.</Text>
        </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
                 <ID>Cove R2</ID> 
                 <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
               <SourceID>LOVERSCOVE</SourceID>
            <Text>A Nomai named Daz proposed to his lover during a negative time interval, allowing him to see 3 seconds into the future of his proposal.</Text> 
    </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
            <ID>Cove R3</ID>
             <RumorName>Ghost Matter Cove</RumorName>
            <Text>A new invention from the Scroll and Stone Workshop was tested here. During the test, something called the voyager disappeared without warning.</Text>
        </RumorFact>
          <RumorFact>
            <ID>Cove R4</ID>
             <RumorName>Ghost Matter Cove</RumorName>
            <Text>A new invention allowed Nomai to walk beyond projection pools.</Text>
        </RumorFact>

         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Cove EX1</ID> 
            <Text>A small cove inside Gabbro's Island filled with ghost matter.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Cove EX2</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Daz proposed to a Nomai named Cassava in this cove. Strangely, Daz appeared to celebrate Cassava's acceptance before receiving an answer.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Cove EX3</ID> 
            <Text>Daz and Cassava wrote to something called the Deep Storm Station through a projection wall, excited by the success of some sort of test.</Text> 
                    <AltText>
                         <Text>A Nomai named Daz proposed to his lover during a negative time interval, allowing him to see 3 seconds into the future of his proposal.</Text>
                         <Condition>CONV R2</Condition>
                    </AltText> 
        </ExploreFact>
           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Cove EX4</ID> 
            <Text>Days pass by much quicker on Gabbro's Island and Statue Island.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
             <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Cove EX5</ID> 
            <Text>As the sun orbits overhead, it causes waves to wash higher on the island, washing high enough to dissolve voyagers.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
 </Entry>





<Entry>
        <ID>LOOMINGCITY</ID>
        <Name>Looming City</Name>
        <Curiosity>None</Curiosity>

            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>

         <RumorFact>
            <ID>LC R1</ID> 
            <Text>Nomai living on Giant's Deep used to be completely insulated from cyclones in the Looming City.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
          <RumorFact>
            <ID>LC R2</ID> 
            <SourceID>BISLE_STUDY</SourceID>
            <Text>The Nomai transported a frozen jellyfish from Bramble Island to a habitat in the Looming City for research.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
          <RumorFact>
            <ID>LC R3</ID> 
            <SourceID>BISLE_STUDY</SourceID>
            <Text>The Nomai were curious about how the jellyfish would interact with the quantum shard in the Looming City.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
          <RumorFact>
            <ID>LC R4</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai abandoned this tower after a quantum shard caused its interior to become inhospitably quantum.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>


        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LC EX1</ID>
                  <Text>A great tower that once served as a Nomai settlement, built on an island within the eye of the hurricane.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LC EX5</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai abandoned this tower due to extenuating circumstances, chronicled in scrolls within the tower.</Text> 
                 <AltText>
                      <Text>The Nomai abandoned this tower after a quantum shard made it inhospitable. They moved to the island they found on their first expedition, and noted another island as a potential construction site.</Text>
                     <Condition>LC R4</Condition>
                 </AltText>
        </ExploreFact>
           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LC EX5.5</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai noted a smaller quantum shard that travels across each of the planet's outer islands.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>

          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LC EX2</ID> 
            <Text>Objects left on a quantum shard will travel with the shard.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LC EX3</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai discovered that quantum objects can be locked in superposition by observing an image of them.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LC EX4</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai were puzzled why the jellyfish had begun coming to the surface more frequently, and for longer durations of time.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>

    <Entry>
           <ID>LOOMINGCITY_JELLY</ID>
        <Name>Cerberus' Pool</Name>
        <Curiosity>None</Curiosity>

          <RumorFact>
            <RumorName>Jellyfish Habitat</RumorName>
                        <RumorNamePriority>1</RumorNamePriority>
            <ID>LCJ R1</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai constructed a jellyfish habitat at the Looming City to conduct further research into them.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        <RumorFact>
            <ID>LCJ R2</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Solanum lost a scroll from the tower in this pool. A jellyfish at the bottom of the pool has surrounded the scroll with its electrifying tentacles.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LCJ EX1</ID> 
            <Text>A pool under the Looming City that houses a jellyfish. A scroll sits at the bottom of the pool, guarded by the jellyfish.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LCJ EX2</ID> 
            <Text>The Quantum Moon exerts a gravitational pull on the objects around it.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LCJ EX3</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai discovered that the Quantum Moon's gravity causes the jellyfishes' water-composed bodies to rise to the surface as it orbits Giant's Deep.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
    </Entry>
</Entry>




<Entry>
   <ID>DEEP_STORM_STATION</ID>
        <Name>Deep Storm Station</Name>

        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
		<IsCuriosity/>

      <RumorFact>
            <RumorName>Irradiated Station</RumorName>
                 <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>DSS Probe</ID> 
            <Text>My scout was warped somewhere into a space flooded with ghost matter. I could see purple electricity outside the viewport.</Text>
    </RumorFact>
    <RumorFact>
            <ID>DSS R2</ID>
                 <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
             <RumorName>Deep Storm Station</RumorName>
             <RumorNamePriority>1</RumorNamePriority>
            <Text>I was able to enter the Deep Storm Station.</Text> 
    </RumorFact>
    <RumorFact>
             <ID>DSS R3</ID> 
            <RumorName>Deep Storm Station</RumorName>
                 <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
             <RumorNamePriority>1</RumorNamePriority>
            <Text>Two Nomai named Pye and Idaea tried to warp to the Deep Storm Station, but arrived on Statue Island instead. They returned to Ash Twin to await guidance.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        
     <RumorFact>
                  <ID>CONV R1</ID> 
                 <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
                     <SourceID>TT_TIME_LOOP_DEVICE</SourceID>
                 <Text>The Deep Storm Station used energy from Giant's Deep's electric core to test the mechanisms of the Ash Twin Project.</Text> 
    </RumorFact>
    <RumorFact>
                 <ID>CONV R2</ID> 
                 <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
               <SourceID>LOVERSCOVE</SourceID>
            <Text>A Nomai named Daz proposed to his lover during a negative time interval, allowing him to see 3 seconds into the future of his proposal.</Text> 
    </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
                 <ID>CONV R3</ID> 
                 <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
               <SourceID>GD_CONSTRUCTION_YARD</SourceID>
            <Text>The Nomai working aboard the Deep Storm Station wrote to the Construction Yard, asking for help in charging a return warp that would allow them to return to the surface.</Text> 
    </RumorFact>
     <RumorFact>
                 <ID>CONV R3.5</ID> 
                 <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
               <SourceID>GD_CONSTRUCTION_YARD</SourceID>
            <Text><Text>The Nomai ensured the Deep Storm Station's interior was perfectly sealed.</Text> </Text> 
    </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
                 <ID>CONV R4</ID> 
                 <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
               <SourceID>SCROLL_WORKSHOP</SourceID>
            <Text>A Nomai named Daz was cut off while writing to the Deep Storm Station from the Scroll and Stone Workshop.</Text> 
    </RumorFact>
   

   

        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS EX1</ID> 
            <Text>An underwater Nomai station deep within Giant's Deep.</Text>
                  <AltText>
                        <Text>An underwater Nomai station deep within Giant's Deep, built to test the mechanisms of the Ash Twin Project using energy from the planet's electric core.</Text>
                        <Condition>CONV R1</Condition>
                 </AltText>
        </ExploreFact>

           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS EX2</ID> 
            <Text>There are eight monoliths with Nomai masks attached. Two of the masks are lit up.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
  
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS EX3</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Cassava was protected from some sort of danger aboard the Deep Storm Station, and used voyager stones to travel outside the station safely.</Text>
            <AltText>
                <Text>A Nomai named Cassava survived the arrival of ghost matter in the star system aboard the Deep Storm Station, and used voyager stones to travel outside the station safely.</Text>
                <Condition>COMET_INTERIOR_X1</Condition>
            </AltText>
        </ExploreFact>
        
  <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS EXW</ID> 
            <Text>Several species in the star system were protected from some sort of danger by the property of immersion. Cassava feared what might happen if they ever returned to the planet's surface.</Text> 
            <AltText>
                <Text>Several species in the star system were protected from ghost matter by the property of immersion. Cassava feared what might happen if they ever returned to the planet's surface.</Text>
                <Condition>COMET_INTERIOR_X1</Condition>
            </AltText>
        </ExploreFact>

  <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS EX3.5</ID> 
            <Text>Giant's Deep's thick clouds obscured sight of anything outside the planet, protecting the native species from harm.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>

          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS EXG</ID> 
            <Text>The Inspired used a lattice of gravity crystals to exploit the property of attraction.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>

        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS EX5</ID> 
            <Text>After releasing the species within the Sanctuary with his voyager, Cassava gathered ghost matter that had engulfed the other planets and warped it into the Deep Storm Station, containing it indefinitely.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>

</Entry>




</AstroObjectEntry>