<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
    <ID>GIANTS_DEEP</ID>



<Entry>


       <ID>SCROLL_WORKSHOP</ID>
        <Name>Scroll and Stone Workshop</Name>
        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
 
        <RumorFact>
            <ID>Workshop R1</ID>
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <Text>A new invention from the Scroll and Stone Workshop on Giant's Deep was used to enter the Sanctuary, in place of a warp receiver.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
            <RumorFact>
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>Workshop R2</ID>
            <Text>A new invention from this workshop allowed Nomai to walk beyond any projection pools they peered through.</Text>
        </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>Workshop R3</ID>
            <Text>Projection stones were crafted at this workshop on Giant's Deep.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>Workshop R4</ID>
            <SourceID>GD_STATUE_ISLAND</SourceID>
            <Text>Nomai scrolls and projection stones were crafted at this workshop on Statue Island.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        
        
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Workshop EX1</ID> 
            <Text>Nomai scrolls and projection stones were crafted at this workshop.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Workshop EX2</ID> 
            <Text>Voyager stones use memory statues to record experiences from the projection pool.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>
           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Workshop EX3</ID> 
            <Text>Memories recorded by memory statues are sent back in time at the end of each loop.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>
           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Workshop EX4</ID> 
            <Text>Memories past the end-of-cycle transmission cannot be sent back. This is indicated by a static vision at the end of the loop.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>
           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Workshop EX5</ID> 
            <Text>Conversations written using projection stones are recorded on projection walls at both ends of the conversation, not the stone itself.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>
           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Workshop EX6</ID> 
            <Text>Information stored within projection walls can only be retrieved using the corresponding projection stones.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>

    <Entry>
       <ID>SCROLL_WORKSHOP_TOP</ID>
        <Name>Workshop Loft</Name>
        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
          <RumorFact>
            <ID>WorkshopTop R1</ID>
            <Text>There is a second floor of the Scroll and Stone Workshop that is too high to reach. The doorway is blocked by a downward-traveling Nomai elevator.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
         
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>WorkshopTop EX1</ID> 
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <Text>A Nomai named Daz was cut off while writing to the Deep Storm Station about the failure of the Ash Twin Project.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>WorkshopTop EX2</ID> 
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <Text>Daz feared that the lifeforms sheltered within the Sanctuary had escaped using the quantum shard.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>WorkshopTop EX3</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai were unable to completely evacuate the species within the Sanctuary due to the species' amphibious nature, which allowed them to evade Nomai voyagers by staying underwater.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>

        </Entry>
</Entry>




///





<Entry>
        <ID>PIONEER_BEACH</ID>
        <Name>Statue Island Beach</Name>
       <Curiosity>None</Curiosity>

         
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Pioneer EX1</ID> 
            <Text>This beach was where Nomai landed on their first survey expedition to Giant's Deep.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
             <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Pioneer EX2</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai moved their camp into the island's interior to seek shelter from the planet's storms.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>

        <Entry>

            <ID>PIONEER_CAMP_INTERIOR</ID>
            <Name>Pioneer Interior Camp</Name>
            <Curiosity>None</Curiosity>

            <RumorFact>
            <ID>Pioneer_Int R1</ID>
            <Text>The Nomai moved their camp into the island's interior to seek shelter from the planet's storms.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Pioneer_Int EX1</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai exploring Giant's Deep discovered an island which remains entirely clear of the cyclones' path.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Pioneer_Int EX2</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai decided to relocate to and settle on the stormless island, until they could find other ways to protect themselves from cyclones.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
           <ID>Pioneer_Int EX3</ID> 
            <Text>A new invention called the storm shelter protected Nomai on Giant's Deep from cyclones.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
           <ID>Pioneer_Int EX4</ID>
            <Text>Nomai noticed storm shelters powering on by themselves in the absence of cyclones, though they were supposed to only activate in the presence of cyclones.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>

        </Entry>

</Entry>



///



 <Entry>
       <ID>CONSTRUCT_BAY</ID>
        <Name>Construction Bay</Name>
        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>

    <RumorFact>
    <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
                 <ID>CB_R1</ID> 
            <Text>The Deep Storm Station's warp pad is located on the Construction Yard.</Text> 
    </RumorFact>
    <RumorFact>
    <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
                 <ID>CB_R2</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Cassava noticed ghost matter at this site disappearing at times. They decided to study and record their findings on the other side of the Construction Bay.</Text> 
    </RumorFact>
    <RumorFact>
    <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
                 <ID>CB_R3</ID> 
            <SourceID>DEEP_STORM_STATION</SourceID>
            <Text>A Nomai named Cassava was protected by the property of immersion aboard the Deep Storm Station.</Text> 
    </RumorFact>
    <RumorFact>
    <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
                 <ID>CB_R4</ID> 
            <SourceID>GD_CONSTRUCTION_YARD</SourceID>
            <Text>A bay on the lower part of the Construction Yard.</Text> 
    </RumorFact>

        <ExploreFact>
           <ID>CB_EX1</ID> 
            <Text>The lower bay of the Construction Yard. One side is flooded by ghost matter.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>CB_EX2</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Cassava observed ghost matter being temporarily neutralized when immersed by waves washing onto the island. This property was named the 'property of immersion'.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>CB_EX3</ID> 
            <Text>Cassava was protected by the property of immersion aboard the Deep Storm Station. He vowed to learn more about ghost matter and its source in the time he had left.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        
        
</Entry>

///



<Entry>
        <ID>LOVERSCOVE</ID>
        <Name>Jellyfish Study Cove</Name>
        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
        <RumorFact>
            <ID>Cove R1</ID> 
             <RumorName>Ghost Matter Cove</RumorName>
            <Text>There is a small cove on Gabbro's Island flooded by ghost matter.</Text>
        </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
                 <ID>Cove R2</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai were discovered a beached jellyfish on this island. They took shelter from a cyclone inside the nearby cove, before continuing their research.</Text> 
    </RumorFact> 

         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Cove EX1</ID> 
            <Text>A small cove inside Gabbro's Island filled with ghost matter.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Cove EX2</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai were intrigued how a jellyfish reached the surface of Giant's Deep.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Cove EX3</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai decided to visit the Deep Storm Station to survey the population of jellyfish from below Giant's Deep's ocean current.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>
           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Cove EX4</ID> 
            <Text>The warp pad to the Deep Storm Station is located on the Construction Yard.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>

 </Entry>





<Entry>
        <ID>LOOMINGCITY</ID>
        <Name>Looming City</Name>
        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>

            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>

         <RumorFact>
            <ID>LC R1</ID> 
             <SourceID>PIONEER_CAMP_INTERIOR</SourceID>
            <Text>Nomai living on Giant's Deep used to be completely insulated from cyclones in the Looming City.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
          <RumorFact>
            <ID>LC R2</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai abandoned this tower after a quantum shard caused its interior to become inhospitably quantum.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>


        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LC EX1</ID>
                  <Text>A great tower that once served as a Nomai settlement.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LC EX2</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai abandoned this tower due to extenuating circumstances, chronicled in scrolls within the tower.</Text> 
                 <AltText>
                      <Text>The Nomai abandoned this tower after its interior became quantum. They relocated to the island they first arrived on for its high cliffs.</Text>
                     <Condition>LC R2</Condition>
                 </AltText>
        </ExploreFact>

          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LC EX3</ID> 
            <Text>"Objects left on a quantum shard will travel with the shard."</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LC EX4</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai discovered that observing an image of a quantum object locks the quantum object in superposition.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>LC EX5</ID> 
            <Text>Days last three times longer on islands in the northern hemisphere, as they sail against the rotation of Giant's Deep.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>

</Entry>









<Entry>
   <ID>DEEP_STORM_STATION</ID>
        <Name>Deep Storm Station</Name>

        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
		<IsCuriosity/>

      <RumorFact>
            <RumorName>Irradiated Station</RumorName>
                 <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>DSS Probe</ID> 
            <Text>My scout was warped into some sort of underwater Nomai station flooded with ghost matter. I could see purple electricity outside the viewport.</Text>
    </RumorFact>
    <RumorFact>
            <ID>DSS R2</ID>
                 <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
             <RumorName>Irradiated Station</RumorName>
            <Text>I was warped into some sort of underwater Nomai station flooded with ghost matter. I could see purple electricity outside the viewport.</Text> 
    </RumorFact>
    <RumorFact>
                 <ID>DSS R6</ID>
            <Text>A Nomai mural depicts the Deep Storm Station as being comprised of a lower and upper module.</Text> 
    </RumorFact>
    <RumorFact>
            <ID>DSS R3</ID>
                 <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
             <RumorName>Deep Storm Station</RumorName>
             <RumorNamePriority>1</RumorNamePriority>
            <Text>A Nomai described the Deep Storm Station as "a project concerning the safety of their clan and the star system."</Text> 
    </RumorFact>
    <RumorFact>
            <ID>DSS R4</ID>
                 <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
             <RumorName>Deep Storm Station</RumorName>
             <RumorNamePriority>1</RumorNamePriority>
            <Text>The Deep Storm Station used energy from Giant's Deep's electric core to test the mechanisms of the negative time interval.</Text> 
    </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
                 <ID>DSS R5</ID>
                 <RumorName>Deep Storm Station</RumorName>
                 <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
             <RumorNamePriority>1</RumorNamePriority>
               <SourceID>SCROLL_WORKSHOP</SourceID>
            <Text>A Nomai named Daz was cut off while writing to the Deep Storm Station from the Scroll and Stone Workshop.</Text> 
    </RumorFact> 
          <RumorFact>
            <ID>DSS R8</ID> 
            <SourceID>INSPIRED</SourceID>
            <Text>The Inspired's construction used a whitehole warp core from the Deep Storm Station's paired warp cores.</Text> 
         </RumorFact> 
         <RumorFact>
                 <ID>DSS R7</ID> 
            <SourceID>LOVERSCOVE</SourceID>
            <Text>The Nomai decided to visit the Deep Storm Station to survey the population of jellyfish from below Giant's Deep's ocean current.</Text> 
    </RumorFact> 
         <RumorFact>
            <ID>DSS R9</ID> 
            <SourceID>TT_TIME_LOOP_DEVICE</SourceID>
            <Text>The Nomai used the Deep Storm Station to see 6 seconds into the future after the Ash Twin Project was launched.</Text> 
    </RumorFact> 
   

        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS EX1</ID> 
            <Text>An underwater Nomai station deep within Giant's Deep.</Text>
                  <AltText>
                        <Text>An underwater Nomai station built to test the mechanisms of the Ash Twin Project, using energy from Giant's Deep's electric core.</Text>
                        <Condition>DSS R4</Condition>
                 </AltText>
        </ExploreFact>

           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS EX2</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Cassava located the source of ghost matter and became curious about recreating it, using a comet as a model.</Text>
                  <AltText>
                        <Text>A Nomai named Cassava explored the Interloper and became curious about recreating it, using the Interloper as a model.</Text>
                        <Condition>COMET_INTERIOR_X3</Condition>
                 </AltText> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS EX6</ID> 
            <Text>Cassava learned that a hostile comet came from a barren asteroid belt far outside any star system. He resolved to launch the Inspired regardless, to protect the surviving species of the star system.</Text> 
                  <AltText>
                        <Text>Cassava learned that the Interloper came from a barren asteroid belt far outside any star system. He resolved to launch the Inspired regardless, to protect the surviving species of the star system.</Text>
                        <Condition>COMET_INTERIOR_X3</Condition>
                 </AltText> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS EX7</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai used the Deep Storm Station to see 6 seconds into the future after the Ash Twin Project was launched. They were disappointed to learn that the Ash Twin Project had failed to launch.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
    

        <Entry>
             <ID>COMET_MURAL</ID>
               <Name>Comet Mural</Name>

              <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity> 

          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS EX3</ID> 
            <Text>The Inspired was a superweapon built to exact vengeance on the true source of ghost matter. Using gravity crystals, it powered a highly localized gravity field to exploit the property of attraction.</Text> 
                  <AltText>
                        <Text>The Inspired was a superweapon built to exact vengeance on the source of the Interloper. Using gravity crystals, it powered a highly localized gravity field to exploit the property of attraction.</Text>
                        <Condition>COMET_INTERIOR_X3</Condition>
                 </AltText> 
        </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS EX4</ID> 
            <Text>The Inspired used a white-hole warp core from the Deep Storm Station's paired warp cores, disabling the station indefinitely.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS EX5</ID> 
            <Text>There were entry points left at the front of the Inspired due to an insufficient amount of gravity crystals.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>

        </Entry>

        <Entry>
             <ID>DSS_BASEMENT</ID>
               <Name>Power Module</Name>

              <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity> 

           <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS_B EX0</ID> 
            <Text>The lower module of the Deep Storm Station. The energy cables from the exterior appear to be powering a white hole at the center of the station.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>

        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS_B EX1</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Cassava was protected from some sort of danger aboard the Deep Storm Station. He used voyager stones to travel outside the station safely.</Text>
            <AltText>
                <Text>A Nomai named Cassava survived the arrival of ghost matter aboard the Deep Storm Station. He used voyager stones to travel outside the station safely.</Text>
                <Condition>COMET_INTERIOR_X3</Condition>
            </AltText>
        </ExploreFact>

     <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS_B EX2</ID> 
            <Text>Several aquatic species were protected from some sort of danger by the property of immersion. Cassava feared what might happen if they ever returned to the planet's surface.</Text> 
            <AltText>
                <Text>Several aquatic species were protected from ghost matter by the property of immersion. Cassava feared what might happen if they ever returned to the planet's surface.</Text>
                <Condition>COMET_INTERIOR_X3</Condition>
            </AltText>
        </ExploreFact>

        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>DSS_B EX3</ID> 
            <Text>Cassava was relieved that Giant's Deep's thick clouds had protected the native species from harm.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>

        </Entry>
</Entry>






</AstroObjectEntry>