<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
    <ID>Inspired</ID>


<Entry>
        <ID>INSPIRED</ID>
        <Name>The Inspired</Name>
        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
         <AltPhotoCondition>INSP R0</AltPhotoCondition>

     <RumorFact>
             <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>INSP R0</ID>
            <Text>I found a frozen comet hidden in the shadow of Giant's Deep.</Text>
         </RumorFact>
  <RumorFact>
             <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>INSP R1</ID>
            <Text>Gravity crystals from the Gravity Crystal Workshop were used in the construction of something called the Inspired.</Text>
         </RumorFact>
        <RumorFact>
             <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>INSP R1.5</ID>
            <Text>The Inspired used a lattice of gravity crystals to exploit something called the property of attraction.</Text>
         </RumorFact>
          <RumorFact>
             <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>INSP R2</ID>
            <SourceID>COMET_INTERIOR</SourceID>
            <Text>The Interloper was used as the model for the Inspired.</Text>
         </RumorFact>
        <RumorFact>
             <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>INSP R3</ID>
            <SourceID>DEEP_STORM_STATION</SourceID>
            <Text>A scroll in the Deep Storm Station reveals that the Inspired was built to bring destruction to the source of ghost matter.</Text>
               <AltText>
                        <Text>A scroll in the Deep Storm Station reveals that the Inspired was built to bring destruction to the source of the Interloper.</Text>
                        <Condition>COMET_INTERIOR_X1</Condition>
                 </AltText>
         </RumorFact>


         <ExploreFact>
          <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>INSP EX1</ID>
                        <Text>An artificial comet hidden in the shadow of Giant's Deep.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>

  <ExploreFact>
             <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>INSP EX2</ID>
            <Text>A Nomai named Cassava built the Inspired to bring great destruction to the source of ghost matter.</Text>
               <AltText>
                        <Text>A Nomai named Cassava built the Inspired to bring great destruction to the source of the Interloper.</Text>
                        <Condition>COMET_INTERIOR_X3</Condition>
                 </AltText>
        </ExploreFact>
        
           <ExploreFact>
        <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>INSP EX4</ID>
            <Text>The Inspired's construction used all available gravity crystals, and a white hole warp core powering the Deep Storm Station.</Text>
             <AltText>
                        <Text>The Inspired's construction used all available gravity crystals, and a white hole warp core powering the Deep Storm Station. Using a lattice of gravity crystals, it would exploit the property of attraction.</Text>
                        <Condition>INSP R1.5</Condition>
                 </AltText>
        </ExploreFact>

        <ExploreFact>
        <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>INSP EX5</ID>
            <Text>The Inspired's lattice is incomplete, with entry points at the front of the structure.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>

         <ExploreFact>
          <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>INSP EX6</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Cassava sent the Inspired towards Timber Hearth after making adjustments to it. He was determined to protect the native species.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>

           <ExploreFact>
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>INSP EX7</ID>
            <Text>The Inspired was kept in stationary orbit around Giant's Deep in case containment of ghost matter was breached.</Text>
       </ExploreFact>

          
      
</Entry>






</AstroObjectEntry>