<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
    <ID>Inspired</ID>


<Entry>
        <ID>INSPIRED</ID>
        <Name>The Inspired</Name>
        <Curiosity>STOWAWAYS</Curiosity>
        
  <RumorFact>
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>INSP R1</ID>
               <SourceID>DEEP_STORM_STATION</SourceID>
            <Text>The Inspired's construction required all available gravity crystals, and a white hole warp core obtained from the Deep Storm Station's paired warp cores.</Text>
        </RumorFact>

 <RumorFact>
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>INSP R2</ID>
               <SourceID>DEEP_STORM_STATION</SourceID>
            <Text>The ghost matter collected by the Inspired was warped into the Deep Storm Station for containment.</Text>
        </RumorFact>

         <ExploreFact>
          <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>INSP EX1</ID>
            <Text>I found a frozen comet hidden in the shadow of Giant's Deep.</Text>
                 <AltText>
                        <Text>An artificial comet made of gravity crystals hidden in the shadow of Giant's Deep.</Text>
                        <Condition>INSP R1</Condition>
                 </AltText>
        </ExploreFact>

  <ExploreFact>
             <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>INSP EX2</ID>
               <SourceID>COMET_INTERIOR</SourceID>
            <Text>The Inspired was a superweapon made to bring massive destruction to the source of ghost matter.</Text>
               <AltText>
                        <Text>The Inspired was a superweapon made to bring massive destruction to the source of the Interloper.</Text>
                        <Condition>COMET_INTERIOR_X1</Condition>
                 </AltText>
        </ExploreFact>
        
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>INSP EX3</ID>
            <Text>I found a mural detailing the construction of something called the Inspired.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>

         <ExploreFact>
          <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>INSP EX3.5</ID> 
            <Text>After realizing the Hearthians were on the verge of extinction, a Nomai named Cassava decided to exchange the Inspired's warp core before launching it towards Timber Hearth.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>

           <ExploreFact>
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <ID>INSP EX4</ID>
            <Text>The ghost matter collected by the Inspired was warped into the Deep Storm Station for containment, and kept in stationary orbit around Giant's Deep in case this containment was breached.</Text>
       </ExploreFact>

          
      
</Entry>






</AstroObjectEntry>