<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
    <ID>TIMBER_HEARTH</ID>

<Entry>
        <ID>TH_MICA</ID>
        <Name>Mica</Name>

        <Curiosity>NONE</Curiosity>
  <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_VILLAGE</SourceID>
            <ID>MICA R1</ID> 
            <Text>Slate says I should go talk to the hatchlings in the village before I take off.</Text> 
  </RumorFact>
  <RumorFact>
            <ID>MICA R2</ID> 
            <Text>I told Mica about the warp towers on Ash Twin.</Text> 
  </RumorFact>

       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>MICA EX1</ID> 
            <Text>Mica says that the sand has been going back and forth between the twins at precise intervals for a long time.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>MICA EX2</ID> 
            <Text>I told Mica about towers I found on Ash Twin. They wondered why there were windows on the top of each tower.</Text>
                <AltText>
                <Text>I told Mica about the warp towers on Ash Twin. They wondered if there were any warp towers that traveled to Timber Hearth.</Text>
                <Condition>MICA R2</Condition>
            </AltText>
       </ExploreFact>

</Entry>

<Entry>
        <ID>TH_TEPHRA</ID>
        <Name>Tephra</Name>

        <Curiosity>NONE</Curiosity>
  <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_VILLAGE</SourceID>
            <ID>TEPH R1</ID> 
            <Text>Slate says I should go talk to the hatchlings in the village before I take off.</Text> 
  </RumorFact>
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>TEPH EX1</ID> 
            <Text>Tephra and Galena noticed the quantum shard in the museum disappearing completely sometimes.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>TEPH EX2</ID> 
            <Text>Tephra asked me to find out where the museum's quantum shard goes when it disappears.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
</Entry>

<Entry>
        <ID>TH_GALENA</ID>
        <Name>Galena</Name>

        <Curiosity>NONE</Curiosity>
  <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_VILLAGE</SourceID>
            <ID>GAL R1</ID> 
            <Text>Slate says I should go talk to the hatchlings in the village before I take off.</Text> 
  </RumorFact>
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>GAL EX1</ID> 
            <Text>Galena wanted to show me something they made for me. They asked me to shoot my Little Scout up from the Outer Wilds Ventures exhibit to see what they made.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>GAL EX2</ID> 
            <Text>I found a heartwarming sign made by Galena using the Little Scout!</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
</Entry>

<Entry>
        <ID>TH_ARKOSE</ID>
        <Name>Arkose</Name>

        <Curiosity>NONE</Curiosity>
  <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_VILLAGE</SourceID>
            <ID>ARK R1</ID> 
            <Text>Slate says I should go talk to the hatchlings in the village before I take off.</Text> 
  </RumorFact>
  <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>GD_GABBRO_ISLAND</SourceID>
            <ID>ARK R2</ID> 
            <Text>Arkose says Gabbro noticed ghost matter disappearing as well.</Text> 
  </RumorFact>

       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>ARK EX1</ID> 
            <Text>Arkose noticed the patch of ghost matter in the village disappearing sometimes.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>ARK EX2</ID> 
            <Text>Arkose says that Gabbro noticed something about ghost matter disappearing as well.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
</Entry>


<Entry>
        <ID>TH_MORAINE</ID>
        <Name>Moraine</Name>

        <Curiosity>STOWAWAYS</Curiosity>
  <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_VILLAGE</SourceID>
            <ID>MOR R1</ID> 
            <Text>Slate says I should go talk to the hatchlings in the village before I take off.</Text> 
  </RumorFact>
    <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>BH_RIEBECK</SourceID>
            <ID>MOR R2</ID> 
            <Text>Moraine says I should tell Riebeck about the Nomai mural I found in the waterways as soon as I can.</Text> 
  </RumorFact>
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>MOR EX1</ID> 
            <Text>Moraine asked if I could dive into a geyser to find anything hidden in the waterways of Timber Hearth.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>MOR EX2</ID> 
            <Text>Moraine says I should tell Riebeck about the Nomai mural I found in the waterways as soon as I can.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
</Entry>


<Entry>
        <ID>TH_SANCTUARY</ID>
        <Name>Sanctuary</Name>

        <Curiosity>STOWAWAYS</Curiosity>
        <RumorFact>
            <RumorName>Glittering Cave</RumorName>
            <RumorNamePriority>1</RumorNamePriority>
            <ID>SY R1</ID> 
            <Text>My Little Scout traveled with the museum’s quantum shard into a glittering cave somewhere within Timber Hearth.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_CAMPSITE</SourceID>
            <RumorName>Sanctuary</RumorName>
            <RumorNamePriority>2</RumorNamePriority>
            <ID>SY R2</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai discussed the excavation and sealing of a Sanctuary within Timber Hearth. They planned to use a new type of projection stone to enter this space.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>VM_VOLCANO</SourceID>
            <ID>SY R3</ID> 
            <Text>Ore mined on Timber Hearth was treated at a forge on Hollow's Lantern before being used to reinforce the Sanctuary.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
            <ID>SY R4</ID> 
            <Text>The Sanctuary was built in a groundwater pool to make use of a quantum shard that traveled inside it.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
          <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>DEEP_STORM_STATION</SourceID>
            <ID>SY R5</ID> 
            <Text>The Hearthians that survived the arrival of ghost matter within the Sanctuary were quarantined inside by a Nomai named Cassava.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SY EX1</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai built this Sanctuary to protect the native lifeforms of Timber Hearth from a supernova.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SY EX2</ID> 
            <Text>The Hearthians within the Sanctuary were protected from ghost matter. A Nomai named Cassava quarantined these survivors inside this space.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SY EX3</ID> 
            <Text>A voyager can travel with a quantum shard, as it is unable to observe its surroundings on its own.</Text> 
         </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SY EX4</ID> 
            <Text>The quantum shard visits the Sanctuary under the cover of darkness.</Text> 
         </ExploreFact>
</Entry>






<Entry>
             <ID>TH_CAMPSITE</ID>
        <Name>Nomai Campsite</Name>

        <Curiosity>STOWAWAYS</Curiosity>



         <RumorFact>
                 <ID>Campsite R2</ID>
            <SourceID>TH_WARPTOWER</SourceID>
            <Text>A Nomai named Cycad delivered news about rotating doors on Ash Twin activating on their own to Timber Hearth.</Text>
      </RumorFact>

       
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX0</ID> 
            <Text>This campsite belonged to the Nomai working on Timber Hearth.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX1</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai on Timber Hearth were careful not to leave the warp receiver unattended to protect the amphibious native lifeforms from being warped to Ash Twin.</Text> 
      </ExploreFact>
            <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX2</ID> 
            <Text>A warp receiver’s return warp only activates once it is clear of any objects.</Text> 
      </ExploreFact>
                <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX3</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Oeno modified vision orbs to acommodate Timber Hearth's native lifeforms. She was disappointed to learn the vision orb had not been raised by them, but by the Attlerock’s gravity as it orbited overhead.</Text> 
      </ExploreFact>
              <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX4</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Yarrow sought help from the Nomai on Timber Hearth regarding an issue on Ash Twin.</Text> 
             <AltText>
                <Text>A Nomai named Yarrow reported the rotating doors on the Sun Station and Timber Hearth warp towers opening and closing without input from time to time.</Text>
                <Condition>Campsite R2</Condition>
            </AltText>
      </ExploreFact>
              <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX5</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Cassava observed ghost matter in this site being pulled up by the Attlerock’s gravity as it orbited overhead.</Text> 
      </ExploreFact>
</Entry>



</AstroObjectEntry>