<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
    <ID>TIMBER_HEARTH</ID>

<Entry>
        <ID>TH_MICA</ID>
        <Name>Mica</Name>

        <Curiosity>None</Curiosity>
  <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_VILLAGE</SourceID>
            <ID>MICA R1</ID> 
            <Text>Slate asked me to find out which hatchling started a rumor that ghost matter disappears sometimes.</Text> 
  </RumorFact>
 <ExploreFact>
            <ID>MICA EX1</ID> 
            <Text>Chert told Mica that sand would start flowing between the Hourglass Twins again soon. According to Mica, not even Chert knows what causes sand to flow between the twins.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>MICA EX2</ID> 
            <Text>Mica wants me to ask Chert why it takes so long for sand to flow between the twins.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
</Entry>

<Entry>
        <ID>TH_TEPHRA</ID>
        <Name>Tephra</Name>

        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
  <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_VILLAGE</SourceID>
            <ID>TEPH R1</ID> 
            <Text>Slate asked me to find out which hatchling started a rumor that ghost matter disappears sometimes.</Text> 
  </RumorFact>
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>TEPH EX1</ID> 
            <Text>Tephra and Galena noticed the quantum shard in the museum disappearing completely sometimes.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>TEPH EX3</ID> 
            <Text>Tephra and Galena looked all over Timber Hearth to find where the quantum shard goes. The only part of Timber Hearth they couldn't look was the Nomai Ruins outside the village, because of the ghost matter in that area.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
</Entry>

<Entry>
        <ID>TH_GALENA</ID>
        <Name>Galena</Name>

        <Curiosity>None</Curiosity>
  <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_VILLAGE</SourceID>
            <ID>GAL R1</ID> 
            <Text>Slate asked me to find out which hatchling started a rumor that ghost matter disappears sometimes.</Text> 
  </RumorFact>
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>GAL EX1</ID> 
            <Text>Galena says they found a skeleton in the drain behind the village waterwheel. They asked me to use my Little Scout to check if the skeleton was still there.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
       
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>GAL EX3</ID> 
            <Text>I used my Little Scout to see the skeleton in the drain.. I think I might be haunted now.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
</Entry>

<Entry>
        <ID>TH_ARKOSE</ID>
        <Name>Arkose</Name>

        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
  <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_VILLAGE</SourceID>
            <ID>ARK R1</ID> 
            <Text>Slate asked me to find out which hatchling started a rumor that ghost matter disappears sometimes.</Text> 
  </RumorFact>
  <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>GD_GABBRO_ISLAND</SourceID>
            <ID>ARK R2</ID> 
            <Text>Arkose says that Gabbro told them that ghost matter disappears.</Text> 
  </RumorFact>

       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>ARK EX1</ID> 
            <Text>Arkose says that Gabbro told them that that ghost matter disappears the last time they returned from Giant's Deep.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>ARK EX2</ID> 
            <Text>Gabbro doesn't know why it happens, but they were the one that told Arkose that ghost matter disappears sometimes.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
</Entry>


<Entry>
        <ID>TH_MORAINE</ID>
        <Name>Moraine</Name>

        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
  <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_VILLAGE</SourceID>
            <ID>MOR R1</ID> 
            <Text>Slate asked me to find out which hatchling started a rumor that ghost matter disappears sometimes.</Text> 
  </RumorFact>
    <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>BH_RIEBECK</SourceID>
            <ID>MOR R2</ID> 
            <Text>Moraine says I should tell Riebeck about the Nomai mural I found in the waterways.</Text> 
  </RumorFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>MOR EX1</ID> 
            <Text>There's an unexplored interconnected underwater cave system inside the geysers. Moraine wonders what might be down there.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>MOR EX2</ID> 
            <Text>Moraine says the Nomai mural I found in the waterways will upend our knowledge of Hearthian history!</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>MOR EX3</ID> 
            <Text>Moraine says I should fly to Brittle Hollow to tell Riebeck about the Nomai mural as soon as I can.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
</Entry>


<Entry>
        <ID>TH_SANCTUARY</ID>
        <Name>Sanctuary</Name>

        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
        <RumorFact>
            <RumorName>Glittering Cave</RumorName>
            <RumorNamePriority>1</RumorNamePriority>
            <ID>SY R1</ID> 
            <Text>My Little Scout traveled with the museum’s quantum shard into a glittering cave somewhere within Timber Hearth.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        
         <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_CAMPSITE</SourceID>
            <RumorName>Sanctuary</RumorName>
            <RumorNamePriority>2</RumorNamePriority>
            <ID>SY R2</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai built the Sanctuary in a cave within Timber Hearth's underground pools where a quantum shard traveled.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>VM_SIDE</SourceID>
                 <RumorName>Sanctuary</RumorName>
            <RumorNamePriority>2</RumorNamePriority>
            <ID>SY R3</ID> 
            <Text>Ore mined on Timber Hearth was treated at a forge on Hollow's Lantern before being used to reinforce the Sanctuary.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
               <RumorName>Sanctuary</RumorName>
            <RumorNamePriority>2</RumorNamePriority>
            <ID>SY R4</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai planned to use a new invention from the Scroll and Stone Workshop to enter the Sanctuary.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        
         <RumorFact>
               <RumorName>Sanctuary</RumorName>
            <RumorNamePriority>2</RumorNamePriority>
            <ID>SY R4.5</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai reported trouble of some kind at the Sanctuary.</Text> 
            <AltText>
                         <Text>Several of the native species inside the Sanctuary eluded the Nomai's attempts to release them back to the surface.</Text>
                         <Condition>CONV R4</Condition>
                    </AltText>
        </RumorFact>

          <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>DEEP_STORM_STATION</SourceID>
            <ID>SY R5</ID> 
            <Text>The Hearthians that survived the arrival of ghost matter within the Sanctuary were quarantined inside by a Nomai named Cassava.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SY EX1</ID> 
            <Text>A Sanctuary built to protect the native lifeforms of Timber Hearth during the operation of the Ash Twin Project.</Text> 
             <AltText>
                <Text>A Sanctuary built in Timber Hearth's underground pools to protect the native lifeforms of Timber Hearth during the operation of the Ash Twin Project.</Text>
                <Condition>Campsite EX2</Condition>
            </AltText>
       </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SY EX2</ID> 
            <Text>The native species of Timber Hearth were endangered by some sort of danger because of their amphibious nature. A Nomai named Cassava quarantined the surviving species left inside the Sanctuary.</Text> 
            <AltText>
                <Text>The native species of Timber Hearth were endangered by ghost matter because of their amphibious nature. A Nomai named Cassava quarantined the surviving species left inside the Sanctuary.</Text>
                <Condition>COMET_INTERIOR_X1</Condition>
            </AltText>
        </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SY EX3</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Cycad was concerned after a quantum shard escaped his sight after accidentally disconnecting from his voyager. Another Nomai reminded him that voyagers are able to use the rule of quantum entanglement.</Text> 
         </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SY EX4</ID> 
            <Text>"A voyager is unable to observe its surroundings on its own."</Text> 
         </ExploreFact>
</Entry>






<Entry>
             <ID>TH_CAMPSITE</ID>
        <Name>Nomai Campsite</Name>

        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>

          <RumorFact>
            <ID>Campsite R1</ID> 
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <RumorName>Nomai Ruins</RumorName>
            <Text>Tephra asked me to explore the Nomai Ruins outside the village for undiscovered caves the quantum shard might travel to.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>

          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX1</ID> 
            <Text>This campsite belonged to the Nomai working on Timber Hearth.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
                <ID>Campsite EX1.5</ID> 
                <Text>The Nomai discovered a new native species during an expedition to Timber Hearth, and followed it deeper into the mountain.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
           
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX2</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai constructed something called the Sanctuary within Timber Hearth's underground pools, in a cave visited by a quantum shard.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX3</ID>
            <Text>The Nomai used a new invention from the Scroll and Stone Workshop on Giant's Deep to enter and exit the Sanctuary. This new invention allowed the Nomai to freely use the rule of quantum entanglement.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX5</ID>
            <Text>I found Nomai text warning of danger invisible to the naked eye beyond a barricade.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>


             <Entry>

                <ID>TH_WARPPOINT</ID>
                  <Name>Nomai Ruins</Name>

                <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
             
               <RumorFact>
            <ID>TH_WR R1</ID> 
            <RumorName>Timber Hearth Ghost Matter</RumorName>
            <Text>A Nomai named Cassava traveled to Timber Hearth to study another property of ghost matter he noticed.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
          <ExploreFact>
                    <ID>TH_WR EX3</ID> 
                   <Text>A Nomai named Cassava observed ghost matter in this site being pulled up by the Attlerock’s gravity as it orbited overhead. He posited that ghost matter could be competitively manipulated by sources of gravity.</Text> 
               </ExploreFact>
                 <ExploreFact>
                    <ID>TH_WR EX3.5</ID> 
                   <Text>This discovery was named the property of attraction, and spurred Cassava to return to Giant's Deep.</Text> 
               </ExploreFact>
               <ExploreFact>
                     <ID>TH_WR EX1</ID> 
                     <Text>The Nomai on Timber Hearth were careful not to leave this warp receiver unattended, to protect the planet's amphibious native lifeforms from being warped to Ash Twin.</Text> 
              </ExploreFact>
                 <ExploreFact>
                     <ID>TH_WR EX2</ID> 
                     <Text>After a Nomai has warped to it and the warp pad is clear of any entities, a warp receiver powers a return warp that allows travel to its paired warp transmitter once.</Text> 
              </ExploreFact>
              
              
             </Entry>


         
</Entry>



</AstroObjectEntry>