<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
    <ID>TIMBER_HEARTH</ID>

<Entry>
        <ID>TH_MICA</ID>
        <Name>Mica</Name>

        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
  <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_VILLAGE</SourceID>
            <ID>MICA R1</ID> 
            <Text>Slate asked me to hear out what questions the kids in the village have about the universe.</Text> 
  </RumorFact>
  
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>MICA EX1</ID> 
            <Text>Mica says that sand hasn't been flowing between the Hourglass Twins for some time.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>MICA EX2</ID> 
            <Text>According to Chert, sand would start flowing between the Hourglass Twins again on the morning of my launch day, right as the sun rises over the horizon in the village.</Text>
       </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>MICA EX3</ID> 
            <Text>Somehow, Chert knows exactly when sand flows between the Hourglass Twins.</Text>
       </ExploreFact>
</Entry>

<Entry>
        <ID>TH_TEPHRA</ID>
        <Name>Tephra</Name>

        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
           <RumorFact>
              <SourceID>TH_VILLAGE</SourceID>
                   <ID>TEPH R1</ID> 
                 <Text>Slate asked me to hear out what questions the kids in the village have about the universe.</Text> 
          </RumorFact>
          <RumorFact>
             <ID>TEPH R2</ID> 
             <Text>I used my Little Scout to look inside the drain behind the waterwheel, but the museum shard wasn't in there.</Text> 
          </RumorFact>
          <RumorFact>
               <ID>TEPH R3</ID> 
               <Text>I jumped down a geyser into the underwater caves of Timber Hearth, but the museum shard wasn't in there.</Text> 
          </RumorFact>
          <RumorFact>
              <ID>TEPH R4</ID> 
             <Text>Tephra asked me to explore the Nomai Ruins outside the village to see if the museum shard was traveling there. They warned me about ghost matter in that area.</Text> 
          </RumorFact>

       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>TEPH EX1</ID> 
            <Text>Tephra and Galena noticed the quantum shard in the museum disappearing completely sometimes. They wondered where it went when it disappeared completely.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
     <ExploreFact>
            <ID>TEPH EX2</ID> 
            <Text>Tephra asked me to use my Little Scout to check if the museum shard was inside the drain behind the village waterwheel.</Text> 
                 <AltText>
                 <Text>I used my Little Scout to look inside the drain behind the waterwheel, but the museum shard wasn't in there.</Text>
                    <Condition>TEPH R2</Condition>
                    </AltText> 
       </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>TEPH EX3</ID> 
            <Text>Tephra asked me to dive into a geyser to see if the museum shard was inside the underwater caves of Timber Hearth.</Text> 
                 <AltText>
                 <Text>I jumped down a geyser into the underwater caves of Timber Hearth, but the museum shard wasn't in there.</Text>
                    <Condition>TEPH R3</Condition>
                    </AltText> 
       </ExploreFact>
     <ExploreFact>
            <ID>TEPH EX4</ID> 
            <Text>According to Riebeck, our ancestors once lived in the ancient waterways inside Timber Hearth's geysers.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>TEPH EX5</ID> 
            <Text>Arkose thinks Riebeck would lose their marbles if they heard about the Nomai mural I found in the waterways.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>

         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>TEPH EX6</ID> 
            <Text>Tephra says that until we figure out another way to see where the museum shard goes, we've hit a dead end.</Text> 
                 <AltText>
                 <Text>Tephra asked me to explore the Nomai Ruins outside the village to see if the museum shard was traveling there. They asked me to be careful of ghost matter in that area.</Text>
                    <Condition>TEPH R4</Condition>
                    </AltText> 
       </ExploreFact>
</Entry>

<Entry>
        <ID>TH_GALENA</ID>
        <Name>Galena</Name>

        <Curiosity>None</Curiosity>
  <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_VILLAGE</SourceID>
            <ID>GAL R1</ID> 
            <Text>Slate asked me to hear out what questions the kids in the village have about the universe.</Text> 
  </RumorFact>
       <RumorFact>
            <ID>GAL R2</ID> 
            <Text>Galena says Feldspar told them about tentacled monsters on the surface of Giant's Deep.</Text> 
       </RumorFact>
       
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>GAL EX1</ID> 
            <Text>Galena says Feldspar told them about monsters on Giant's Deep.</Text>
       </ExploreFact>
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>GAL EX2</ID> 
            <Text>According to Feldspar, the monsters on Giant's Deep would come to the surface of the ocean sometimes.</Text>
       </ExploreFact>
</Entry>

<Entry>
        <ID>TH_ARKOSE</ID>
        <Name>Arkose</Name>

        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
  <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_VILLAGE</SourceID>
            <ID>ARK R1</ID> 
            <Text>Slate asked me to hear out what questions the kids in the village have about the universe.</Text>  
  </RumorFact>
  <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>GD_GABBRO_ISLAND</SourceID>
            <ID>ARK R2</ID> 
            <Text>Arkose says that Gabbro was the one who told them that ghost matter disappears.</Text> 
  </RumorFact>

       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>ARK EX1</ID> 
            <Text>Arkose noticed that the patch of ghost matter in the village wouldn't leave a glowing trail sometimes when a rock was thrown into it.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>ARK EX2</ID> 
            <Text>According to Gabbro, ghost matter disappears sometimes.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact> 
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>ARK EX3</ID> 
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <Text>Gabbro asked me to tell Arkose about how water neutralizes ghost matter.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
     
</Entry>


<Entry>
        <ID>TH_MORAINE</ID>
        <Name>Moraine</Name>

        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
  <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_VILLAGE</SourceID>
            <ID>MOR R1</ID> 
            <Text>Slate asked me to hear out what questions the kids in the village have about the universe.</Text>  
  </RumorFact>

       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>MOR EX1</ID> 
            <Text>For some reason, Moraine asked me how many comets there were in the star system.</Text>
       </ExploreFact>
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>MOR EX2</ID> 
            <Text>Moraine says they saw two comets in the sky one night. They were sure it was a second comet, but they haven't been able to find it again since.</Text>
       </ExploreFact>
</Entry>


<Entry>
        <ID>TH_SANCTUARY</ID>
        <Name>Sanctuary</Name>

        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
        <RumorFact>
            <RumorName>Glittering Cave</RumorName>
            <RumorNamePriority>1</RumorNamePriority>
            <ID>SY R1</ID> 
            <Text>My Little Scout traveled with the museum’s quantum shard into a glittering cave somewhere within Timber Hearth.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        
         <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_CAMPSITE</SourceID>
            <RumorName>Sanctuary</RumorName>
            <RumorNamePriority>2</RumorNamePriority>
            <ID>SY R2</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai built the Sanctuary in a cave within Timber Hearth's underground pools where a quantum shard traveled.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>VM_SIDE</SourceID>
                 <RumorName>Sanctuary</RumorName>
            <RumorNamePriority>2</RumorNamePriority>
            <ID>SY R3</ID> 
            <Text>Ore mined on Timber Hearth was treated at a forge on Hollow's Lantern before being used to reinforce the Sanctuary.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
               <RumorName>Sanctuary</RumorName>
            <RumorNamePriority>2</RumorNamePriority>
            <ID>SY R4</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai planned to use a new invention from the Scroll and Stone Workshop to enter the Sanctuary.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        
         <RumorFact>
               <RumorName>Sanctuary</RumorName>
            <RumorNamePriority>2</RumorNamePriority>
            <ID>SY R4.5</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai reported trouble of some kind at the Sanctuary.</Text> 
            <AltText>
                         <Text>Several of the native species inside the Sanctuary eluded the Nomai's attempts to release them back to the surface.</Text>
                         <Condition>CONV R4</Condition>
                    </AltText>
        </RumorFact>

          <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>DEEP_STORM_STATION</SourceID>
            <ID>SY R5</ID> 
            <Text>The Hearthians that survived the arrival of ghost matter within the Sanctuary were quarantined inside by a Nomai named Cassava.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SY EX1</ID> 
            <Text>A Sanctuary built to protect the native lifeforms of Timber Hearth during the operation of the Ash Twin Project.</Text> 
             <AltText>
                <Text>A Sanctuary built in Timber Hearth's underground pools to protect the native lifeforms of Timber Hearth during the operation of the Ash Twin Project.</Text>
                <Condition>Campsite EX2</Condition>
            </AltText>
       </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SY EX2</ID> 
            <Text>The native species of Timber Hearth were endangered by some sort of danger because of their amphibious nature. A Nomai named Cassava quarantined the surviving species left inside the Sanctuary.</Text> 
            <AltText>
                <Text>The native species of Timber Hearth were endangered by ghost matter because of their amphibious nature. A Nomai named Cassava quarantined the surviving species left inside the Sanctuary.</Text>
                <Condition>COMET_INTERIOR_X3</Condition>
            </AltText>
        </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SY EX3</ID> 
            <Text>A quantum shard escaped a Nomai's sight when the Nomai accidentally disconnected from his voyager. Another Nomai reminded him that voyagers were able to use the rule of quantum entanglement.</Text> 
         </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SY EX4</ID> 
            <Text>"A voyager is unable to observe its surroundings on its own."</Text> 
         </ExploreFact>
</Entry>






<Entry>
             <ID>TH_CAMPSITE</ID>
        <Name>Nomai Campsite</Name>

        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>

         
           <RumorFact>
            <ID>Campsite R2</ID> 
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <Text>There is a Nomai campsite on the path from the Nomai Ruins into the geyser mountain.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>

          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX1</ID> 
            <Text>This campsite belonged to the Nomai working on Timber Hearth.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
           
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX2</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai constructed something called the Sanctuary within Timber Hearth's underground pools, in a cave visited by a quantum shard.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX3</ID>
            <Text>A new invention from the Scroll and Stone Workshop allowed Nomai to freely use the rule of quantum entanglement.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
                <ID>Campsite EX1.5</ID> 
                <Text>The Nomai discovered a new species during an expedition to Timber Hearth, and followed it deeper into the mountain.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX5</ID>
            <Text>I found Nomai text warning of danger invisible to the naked eye beyond a thorny barricade.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>


             <Entry>

                <ID>TH_WARPPOINT</ID>
                  <Name>Nomai Ruins</Name>

                <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
             
               <RumorFact>
            <ID>TH_WR R1</ID> 
            <RumorName>Timber Hearth Ghost Matter Research</RumorName>
            <Text>A Nomai named Cassava traveled to Timber Hearth to study another property of ghost matter he noticed.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        <RumorFact>
            <ID>TH_WR R2</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Cassava observed ghost matter in this site being pulled up by the Attlerock’s gravity as it orbited overhead.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>

          <ExploreFact>
                    <ID>TH_WR EX3</ID> 
                   <Text>There is a scroll in a toppled shelf here, but it is surrounded by ghost matter.</Text> 
                   <AltText><Text>A Nomai named Cassava observed ghost matter in this site being pulled up by the Attlerock’s gravity as it orbited overhead. He posited that ghost matter could be competitively manipulated by sources of gravity.</Text>
                         <Condition>TH_WR R2</Condition>
                         </AltText>
               </ExploreFact>
                 <ExploreFact>
                    <ID>TH_WR EX3.5</ID> 
                   <Text>This discovery was named the property of attraction.</Text> 
               </ExploreFact>
               <ExploreFact>
                     <ID>TH_WR EX1</ID> 
                     <Text>The Nomai on Timber Hearth were careful not to leave this warp receiver unattended, to protect the planet's native life from being warped to Ash Twin.</Text> 
              </ExploreFact>
                 <ExploreFact>
                     <ID>TH_WR EX2</ID> 
                     <Text>After a Nomai has warped to it and the warp pad is clear of any entities, a warp receiver powers a return warp that allows travel to its paired warp transmitter once.</Text> 
              </ExploreFact>
              
              
             </Entry>


         
</Entry>



</AstroObjectEntry>