<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
    <ID>TIMBER_HEARTH</ID>

<Entry>
        <ID>TH_MICA</ID>
        <Name>Mica</Name>

        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
  <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_VILLAGE</SourceID>
            <ID>MICA R1</ID> 
            <Text>Slate asked me to hear out what questions the kids in the village have about the universe.</Text> 
  </RumorFact>
  
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>MICA EX1</ID> 
            <Text>Mica says that sand hasn't been flowing between the Hourglass Twins for some time.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>MICA EX2</ID> 
            <Text>According to Chert, sand would start flowing between the Hourglass Twins again on the morning of my launch day.</Text>
       </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>MICA EX3</ID> 
            <Text>Mica isn't sure how Chert knows when sand flows between the Hourglass Twins.</Text>
       </ExploreFact>
</Entry>

<Entry>
        <ID>TH_TEPHRA</ID>
        <Name>Tephra</Name>

        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
           <RumorFact>
              <SourceID>TH_VILLAGE</SourceID>
                   <ID>TEPH R1</ID> 
                 <Text>Slate asked me to hear out what questions the kids in the village have about the universe.</Text> 
          </RumorFact>
          <RumorFact>
             <ID>TEPH R2</ID> 
             <Text>I used my Little Scout to look inside the drain behind the waterwheel, but the museum shard wasn't in there.</Text> 
          </RumorFact>
          <RumorFact>
              <ID>TEPH R4</ID> 
             <Text>Tephra asked me to explore the Nomai Ruins outside the village to see if the museum shard was traveling there. They warned me about ghost matter in that area.</Text> 
          </RumorFact>

       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>TEPH EX1</ID> 
            <Text>Tephra and Galena noticed the quantum shard in the museum disappearing completely sometimes. They wondered where it went when it disappeared completely.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
     <ExploreFact>
            <ID>TEPH EX2</ID> 
            <Text>Tephra asked me to use my Little Scout to check if the museum shard was inside the drain behind the village waterwheel.</Text> 
                 <AltText>
                 <Text>I used my Little Scout to look for the museum shard inside the drain behind the waterwheel.</Text>
                    <Condition>TEPH R2</Condition>
                    </AltText> 
       </ExploreFact>

         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>TEPH EX3</ID> 
            <Text>Tephra says that until we figure out another way to see where the museum shard goes, we've hit a dead end.</Text> 
                 <AltText>
                 <Text>Tephra asked me to explore the Nomai Ruins outside the village to see if the museum shard was traveling there. They warned me about ghost matter in that area.</Text>
                    <Condition>TEPH R4</Condition>
                    </AltText> 
       </ExploreFact>
</Entry>

<Entry>
        <ID>TH_GALENA</ID>
        <Name>Galena</Name>

        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
  <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_VILLAGE</SourceID>
            <ID>GAL R1</ID> 
            <Text>Slate asked me to hear out what questions the kids in the village have about the universe.</Text> 
  </RumorFact>
       <RumorFact>
            <ID>GAL R2</ID> 
            <Text>Galena wonders how much of Brittle Hollow left after the meteor storm ends.</Text> 
       </RumorFact>
       
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>GAL EX1</ID> 
            <Text>Galena wonders how much of Brittle Hollow left after the meteor storm ends.</Text>
       </ExploreFact>
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>GAL EX2</ID> 
            <Text>According to Riebeck, the meteor storm has lasted for weeks, and might start to break apart Brittle Hollow.</Text>
       </ExploreFact>
</Entry>


<Entry>
        <ID>TH_ARKOSE</ID>
        <Name>Arkose</Name>

        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
  <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_VILLAGE</SourceID>
            <ID>ARK R1</ID> 
            <Text>Slate asked me to hear out what questions the kids in the village have about the universe.</Text>  
  </RumorFact>
  <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>GD_GABBRO_ISLAND</SourceID>
            <ID>ARK R2</ID> 
            <Text>Arkose says that Gabbro was the one who told them that ghost matter disappears.</Text> 
  </RumorFact>

       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>ARK EX1</ID> 
            <Text>Arkose says that the ghost matter in the village sometimes doesn't leave a glowing trail when something was thrown into it.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>ARK EX2</ID> 
            <Text>According to Gabbro, ghost matter disappears sometimes.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact> 
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>ARK EX3</ID> 
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <Text>Gabbro asked me to tell Arkose about how water neutralizes ghost matter.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
     
</Entry>


<Entry>
        <ID>TH_MORAINE</ID>
        <Name>Moraine</Name>

        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
  <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_VILLAGE</SourceID>
            <ID>MOR R1</ID> 
            <Text>Slate asked me to hear out what questions the kids in the village have about the universe.</Text>  
  </RumorFact>

       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>MOR EX1</ID> 
            <Text>For some reason, Moraine asked me how many comets there were in the star system.</Text>
       </ExploreFact>
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>MOR EX2</ID> 
            <Text>Moraine says they saw two comets in the sky one night. They were sure it was a second comet, but they haven't been able to find it again since.</Text>
       </ExploreFact>
</Entry>


<Entry>
        <ID>TH_SANCTUARY</ID>
        <Name>Sanctuary</Name>

        <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
        <RumorFact>
            <RumorName>Glittering Cave</RumorName>
            <RumorNamePriority>1</RumorNamePriority>
            <ID>SY R1</ID> 
            <Text>My Little Scout traveled with the museum’s quantum shard into a glittering cave somewhere within Timber Hearth.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        
         <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_CAMPSITE</SourceID>
            <RumorName>Sanctuary</RumorName>
            <RumorNamePriority>2</RumorNamePriority>
            <ID>SY R2</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai built the Sanctuary using ore mined on Timber Hearth.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_CAMPSITE</SourceID>
               <RumorName>Sanctuary</RumorName>
            <RumorNamePriority>2</RumorNamePriority>
            <ID>SY R3</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai used a new invention from the Scroll and Stone Workshop to enter the Sanctuary.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
          <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>DEEP_STORM_STATION</SourceID>
            <ID>SY R5</ID> 
            <Text>The Hearthians that survived the arrival of ghost matter within the Sanctuary were quarantined inside by a Nomai named Cassava.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
          <RumorFact>
            <ID>SY R6</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Yarrow wrote to the Sanctuary about the failure of the Ash Twin Project.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        
        
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SY EX1</ID> 
            <Text>A Sanctuary built to protect Timber Hearth's native life during the operation of the Ash Twin Project.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SY EX3</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Cassava was horrified to discover that the native species of Timber Hearth had been gravely endangered by ghost matter due to their amphibious nature.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SY EX3.5</ID> 
            <Text>Cassava quarantined the species within the Sanctuary. He resolved to launch the Inspired towards Timber Hearth (after necessary adjustments) to protect them.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SY EX4</ID> 
            <Text>I found an Ash Twin projection stone inside the Sanctuary, but was unable to read the text on the projection wall.</Text> 
                   <AltText><Text>A Nomai named Yarrow wrote to the Sanctuary about the failure of the Ash Twin Project.</Text>
                         <Condition>SY R6</Condition>
                         </AltText>
         </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SY EX5</ID> 
            <Text>A memory statue aboard the Ash Twin Project erroneously paired with Yarrow. This was later learned to be caused by some sort of safeguard.</Text> 
         </ExploreFact>
</Entry>




 <Entry>

          <ID>TH_WARPPOINT</ID>
          <Name>Timber Hearth Warp Ruins</Name>

          <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>
             
               <RumorFact>
            <ID>TH_WR R1</ID> 
            <RumorName>Timber Hearth Matter Research</RumorName>
            <Text>A Nomai named Cassava traveled to Timber Hearth to study a second property of ghost matter.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        <RumorFact>
            <ID>TH_WR R2</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Cassava observed ghost matter in this site being pulled up by the Attlerock’s gravity as it orbited overhead.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>


                 <ExploreFact>
                     <ID>TH_WR EX1</ID> 
                     <Text>The Nomai ruins at this site were known as a warp receiver.</Text> 
              </ExploreFact>
                 <ExploreFact>
                     <ID>TH_WR EX2</ID> 
                     <Text>After a Nomai has warped to it and the warp pad is clear of any entities, a warp receiver powers a return warp that allows travel to its paired warp transmitter once.</Text> 
              </ExploreFact>
               <ExploreFact>
                     <ID>TH_WR EX3</ID> 
                     <Text>The Nomai on Timber Hearth were careful not to leave this warp receiver powered to protect the planet's native life from being warped to Ash Twin.</Text> 
              </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
                    <ID>TH_WR EX4</ID> 
                   <Text>There is a scroll in a toppled shelf here, but it is surrounded by ghost matter.</Text> 
                   <AltText><Text>A Nomai named Cassava observed ghost matter rising as the Attlerock orbited overhead.</Text>
                         <Condition>TH_WR R2</Condition>
                         </AltText>
               </ExploreFact>
                 <ExploreFact>
                    <ID>TH_WR EX5</ID> 
                   <Text>Cassava posited that ghost matter could be competitively manipulated by sources of gravity. This discovery was named the 'property of attraction'.</Text> 
               </ExploreFact>
              

     <Entry>

            <ID>TH_CAMPSITE</ID>
            <Name>Nomai Campsite</Name>

            <Curiosity>Stowaway</Curiosity>

         
           <RumorFact>
            <ID>Campsite R1</ID> 
            <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
            <Text>There is a Nomai campsite on the path from the Nomai Ruins into the geyser mountain.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>

          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX1</ID> 
            <Text>This campsite belonged to the Nomai working on Timber Hearth.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
           
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX2</ID> 
            <Text>Ore mined on Timber Hearth was used in the construction of the Sanctuary and the Ash Twin Project.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX3</ID>
            <Text>A new invention from the Scroll and Stone Workshop was used to enter the Sanctuary, in place of a warp receiver.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
                <ID>Campsite EX1.5</ID> 
                <Text>The Nomai visited the pools outside mining site 2b to study a native species of Timber Hearth.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX5</ID>
            <Text>I found Nomai text warning of danger invisible to the naked eye beyond a barricade.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>

         
             </Entry>
</Entry>



</AstroObjectEntry>