<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
    <ID>TIMBER_HEARTH</ID>

<Entry>
        <ID>TH_SANCTUARY</ID>
        <Name>Sanctuary</Name>

        <Curiosity>STOWAWAYS</Curiosity>
        <RumorFact>
            <RumorName>Glittering Cave</RumorName>
            <RumorNamePriority>1</RumorNamePriority>
            <ID>SY R1</ID> 
            <Text>My Little Scout traveled with the museum’s quantum shard into a glittering cave somewhere within Timber Hearth.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
         <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>TH_CAMPSITE</SourceID>
            <RumorName>Sanctuary</RumorName>
            <RumorNamePriority>2</RumorNamePriority>
            <ID>SY R2</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai discussed the excavation and sealing of a Sacntuary within Timber Hearth. They planned to use a new type of projection stone to enter this space.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        <RumorFact>
           <SourceID>VM_VOLCANO</SourceID>
            <ID>SY R3</ID> 
            <Text>Ore mined on Timber Hearth was treated at a forge on Hollow's Lantern before being used to reinforce the Sanctuary.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
        
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SY EX1</ID> 
            <Text>The Nomai built this Sanctuary to protect the native lifeforms of Timber Hearth from supernovas induced during the operation of the Ash Twin Project.</Text> 
       </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SY EX2</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Cassava quarantined the Hearthians’ ancestors in this Sanctuary, after realizing that they were gravely endangered by ghost matter.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SY EX3</ID> 
            <Text>A voyager can entangle with the quantum shard as it is unable to observe its surroundings on its own.</Text> 
         </ExploreFact>







        <Entry>
             <ID>TH_CAMPSITE</ID>
        <Name>Nomai Campsite</Name>

        <Curiosity>STOWAWAYS</Curiosity>


     <RumorFact>
                 <ID>Campsite R1</ID>
            <RumorName>Timber Hearth Warp Destination</RumorName>
            <Text>My scout traveled to somewhere on Timber Hearth after it was warped from a tower on Ash Twin.</Text>
      </RumorFact>
      

       
          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX1</ID> 
            <Text>This campsite belonged to the Nomai working on Timber Hearth.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
            <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX2</ID> 
            <Text>A warp receiver’s return warp only activates once it is clear of any objects.</Text> 
      </ExploreFact>
                <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX3</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Oeno modified vision orbs to acommodate Timber Hearth's native lifeforms. She was disappointed to learn the vision orb had not been raised by them, but by the Attlerock’s gravity as it orbited overhead.</Text> 
      </ExploreFact>
              <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX4</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Yarrow reported the rotating doors on the Sun Station and Timber Hearth warp towers opening and closing without input from time to time.</Text> 
      </ExploreFact>
              <ExploreFact>
            <ID>Campsite EX5</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Cassava observed ghost matter in this site being pulled up by the Attlerock’s gravity as it orbited overhead.</Text> 
      </ExploreFact>
        </Entry>
</Entry>



</AstroObjectEntry>