<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
    <ID>TOWER_TWIN</ID>

 

<Entry>
        <ID>TH_WARPTOWER</ID>
        <Name>Mountain Tower</Name>
        <Curiosity>TimeLoop</Curiosity>

          <RumorFact>
            <ID>TH Tower R1</ID>
            <SourceID>TT_WARP_TOWERS</SourceID>
             <Text>A tower on Ash Twin in the shape of a mountain.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>

       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>TH Tower EX1</ID>
             <Text>The Nomai kept the rotating doors of this tower closed to keep native life from Timber Hearth from wandering any farther without protection and oxygen.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
       <ExploreFact>
            <ID>TH Tower EX2</ID> 
            <Text>A Nomai named Oeno noticed this tower's rotating doors opening and closing by themself, even in the absence of any Nomai.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>TH Tower EX3</ID> 
            <Text>Oeno investigated this issue at the other tower on Ash Twin with rotating doors.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
 </Entry>


 
<Entry>
              <ID>SS_WARPTOWER</ID>
              <Name>Star Tower</Name>
            <Curiosity>TimeLoop</Curiosity>

          <RumorFact>
            <ID>SS Tower R1</ID>
            <SourceID>TT_WARP_TOWERS</SourceID>
             <Text>A tower on Ash Twin with pointed edges.</Text> 
        </RumorFact> 
          <RumorFact>
            <ID>SS Tower R2</ID>
             <Text>Nomai visited the other tower on Ash Twin with rotating doors to investigate if they would open on their own.</Text> 
        </RumorFact> 

          <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SS Tower EX1</ID>
             <Text>The tower's rotating doors activate as the sand column flowing towards Ember Twin passes overhead. The Nomai call this phenomenon the 'sunless day'.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SS Tower EX2</ID>
             <Text>The Nomai waited for the current sand transfer cycle to end to see if the doors' vision orbs no longer rose on their own.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SS Tower EX3</ID>
             <Text>Nomai were warned to take utmost care when visiting the Sun Station, especially near its control bay.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
 </Entry>



<Entry>
           <ID>SOLAR_TOWER</ID>
            <Name>Solar Towers</Name>
             <Curiosity>TimeLoop</Curiosity>

      <RumorFact>
            <ID>SLR_T R1</ID>
            <SourceID>ET_SOLARINTRO</SourceID>
             <Text>Solar towers were built on Ash Twin's poles.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>
      <RumorFact>
            <ID>SLR_T R2</ID>
             <Text>The solar towers were built to power the Ash Twin Project's end-of-cycle transmission.</Text> 
        </RumorFact>

         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SLR_T EX1</ID>
             <Text>Towers of colossal solar panels constructed at both of Ash Twin's poles.</Text> 
              <AltText>
                         <Text>Towers of colossal solar panels on both of Ash Twin's poles, built to power the Ash Twin Project's end-of-cycle transmission.</Text>
                         <Condition>SLR_T R2</Condition>
                    </AltText>
        </ExploreFact>
      <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SLR_T EX2</ID>
             <Text>The Hourglass Twins' poles are completely safe from the sand funnel. A Nomai referred to the sand transfer as a 'sunless day'.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SLR_T EX4</ID>
             <Text>Ash Twin's core is insulated from the supernova for 35 seconds.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
         <ExploreFact>
            <ID>SLR_T EX5</ID>
             <Text>The Ash Twin Project's end-of-cycle transmission begins only after the sun completely collapses into a supernova, and takes 30 seconds to complete.</Text> 
        </ExploreFact>
 </Entry>

</AstroObjectEntry>