<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Hearthians</color>]]>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		OENO: The expedition has concluded.. We have found no signs of any survivors on the bramble's exterior.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: In that case, we should plan an expedition into the bramble's interior as soon as possible. That is the only path forward left.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: No, Plume, we cannot attempt this risk. Our current methods of travel are far too incompatible for traversing the bramble's dangerous and winding interiors..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: Worse, countless hordes of anglerfish dwell in nearly every arm of the bramble. We were incredibly fortunate to have escaped the bramble at all.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: Perhaps.. If we could find their <![CDATA[<color=orange>nest,</color>]]> we could cull some of the anglerfishes' numbers slowly with time..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: <![CDATA[<i>What?</i>]]> Plume, you.. you cannot mean that.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: Putting aside the dangers of this plan, we cannot treat innocent lives with such wrath - even that of hostile creatures such as these.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: The anglerfish bear no ill will against us. We should not seek vengeance against them for their instincts.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: But my brother could still be alive.. Our friends may be holding out hope for us inside - as long as the anglerfish stand in our way, our only choice will be to abandon them!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: Plume, I understand your pain deeply.. But the odds are impossibly low for any of them to have survived for the length of time it took our clan to even reunite.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: We cannot endanger more lives, including that of the native species.. We can only keep learning in their stead.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>12</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>11</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: We will find this <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Eye of the Universe. </color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>13</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>12</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: It was by sheer fortune that we should have survived in place of those who perished.. I believe we must devote ourselves to this mission they gave their lives for.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>14</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>13</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: Only then will we be able to honor their losses, and face the other clans again without shame.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>15</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>14</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Plume, Oeno! I have found something! Please, come at once!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>16</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>15</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: C-Cassava. What is it? Have you.. found a survivor?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>17</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>16</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: I'm afraid not, Plume.. But please, follow me. I have constructed platforms on the side of this glacier that will lead us to this discovery!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>

		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>DBG EX0</FactID>
			<Condition>11</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>DBG EX0.5</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	<RevealFact>
			<FactID>DBG EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>17</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>