<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Hearthians</color>]]>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PLUME: To think we would not find our friends, but these familiar species instead, frozen within this glacier...
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: This.. This is an incredible discovery, Cassava. Both these species, inside this ancient glacier...
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: Hypothesis: Both of these species may once have been native to the frozen planet destroyed by the bramble.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
	<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationA />
			<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: When the planet was shattered, they must have been carried within the fragments of the planet scattered across the star system, crashing on the planets that would become their habitats today.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationA />
			<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: If that is true, that these stowaways survived such displacement - and continue to thrive in their new habitats - is nothing short of awe-inspiring.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationA />
			<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: In the heartbreaking absence of any trace of the survivors here.. this discovery is a beacon of light.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationA />
			<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: I hope to learn more about this fascinating universe and its many secrets. I am sure it is what Keek would have wanted more than anything.
 		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationA />
			<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: We are with you, Plume.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationA />
			<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: I am certain that if we put our minds together, our clan will accomplish anything we set our hearts to!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>

	<RevealFact>
			<FactID>DBF EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>3</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	<RevealFact>
			<FactID>DBF EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>3</Condition>
		</RevealFact>


</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>