<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Hearthians</color>]]>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PLUME: To think we would not find our friends from the crash on the bramble's exterior, but these familiar species instead, preserved within this glacier...
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: This.. This is an incredible discovery. We now can confidently conclude that both these species once originated on this planet destroyed by the bramble.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: When the planet was shattered, they must have become stowaways within fragments of the planet scattered across the star system, crashing on the planets that would become their habitats today.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
	<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationA />
			<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: That these species survived - and continue to thrive on these alien planets - despite their displacement, is nothing short of awe-inspiring! Their resilience inspires me greatly.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationA />
			<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: In the heartbreaking absence of any trace of the survivors here.. this discovery is a beacon of light.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationA />
			<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: I wish to learn from these species' perserverance and undying courage in the face of hardships.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationA />
			<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: They have much to teach all of us. I am certain that if we simply work together and perservere, our clan will accomplish anything we set our hearts to!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
</NomaiObject>