<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Hearthians</color>]]>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: This lone plant left by the expedition team appears to be completely unaffected by the presence of the deadly matter around it.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Beyond it, the trees, grasses, and flora of the star system appear bizzarely resilient to the deadly matter, despite its terrible effect on the star system.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: I can only assume the differences between the biology of plants and animals must have protected them.. But was this survival by miraculous chance, or engineered specificity?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: The bramble appears to be strong and healthy, even as it is engulfed by the deadly matter.. That can be no coincidence in my mind.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Our clan had long wondered if the bramble was a conduit of intergalactic travel for a more advanced civilization's intergalactic travel.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: If this is true.. Did they detect us, and perceive us as threats? Was this comet sent to deliberately purge the star system the bramble had taken root in?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: ...I must continue this investigation. Until I can answer this question, my journey has not come to an end.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


</NomaiObject>