<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationB/>
		<Text>
			KOUSA: The perpetual storm shelter has been constructed, Idaea!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<LocationA/>
		<Text>
			KOUSA: You may see this modified storm shelter currently active within the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Tower of Quantum Knowledge</color>]]> below us.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationA/>
		<Text>
			IDAEA: You have my deepest gratitude, Kousa.. I was not sure if it would even be possible to build a storm shelter that was active perpetually!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationB/>
		<Text>
			KOUSA: Of course, but.. Why did you wish to build a perpetual storm shelter on the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Quantum Moon,</color>]]> young one?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<LocationB/>
		<Text>
			IDAEA: Ah, I was reminded of your invention during a recent visit to <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Giant's Deep.</color>]]> I was truly impressed how they were able to protect Nomai from even the fiercest winds.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<LocationB/>
		<Text>
			IDAEA: From what I know, our elders have long been unable to escape the sixth location because of impossibly strong winds surrounding the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Quantum Moon's</color>]]> skies.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<LocationB/>
		<Text>
			IDAEA: I hoped that if a storm shelter were built on the sixth location, perhaps it might allow us to escape the strong winds surrounding the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Quantum Moon</color>]]> there.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<LocationB/>
		<Text>
			KOUSA: Young Idaea... How.. How have I never thought of that? 
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<LocationB/>
		<Text>
			KOUSA: Yes, yes... If this plan works, we may be able to reach our goals without ever putting the star system at risk! 
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<LocationB/>
		<Text>
			KOUSA: I must make preparations to set off for the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Quantum Moon</color>]]> at once. Will you accompany me, Idaea?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<LocationB/>
		<Text>
			IDAEA: I wish I could.. But I must return to my work on the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sun Station</color>]]> shortly..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>12</ID>
		<ParentID>11</ParentID>
		<LocationB/>
		<Text>
			IDAEA: Would you kindly write to the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sun Station</color>]]> using the projection wall when you return, Kousa?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>13</ID>
		<ParentID>12</ParentID>
		<LocationB/>
		<Text>
			KOUSA: Of course, my friend. I shall update you from the projection wall within the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Tower of Quantum Knowledge</color>]]> upon my return!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>14</ID>
		<ParentID>13</ParentID>
		<LocationB/>
		<Text>
			IDAEA: You have my gratitude, my friend! Be curious on your journey.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	

	<ShipLogConditions>

		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>BH_SSR R1</FactID>
			<Condition>7</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>BH_SSR R2</FactID>
			<Condition>13</Condition>
		</RevealFact>


	</ShipLogConditions>
</NomaiObject>