<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>YARROW: Oeno, it pains me to report that the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project</color>]]> has failed.. We should begin the evacuation of the lifeforms inside the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sanctuary.</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>OENO: No.. Not after everything we've done to prepare for it! Are we.. certain there is no way the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project</color>]]> will work, Yarrow?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>YARROW: Unfortunately, yes.. I began suspect something was amiss when the memory statue failed to pair with me after activating the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project</color>]]> as expected..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>YARROW: An update: Oeno, a memory statue aboard the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project</color>]]> has suddenly just paired with me!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>YARROW: But.. We were unable to power the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project..</color>]]> Why did this memory statue pair with me erroneously?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>OENO: How exciting, Yarrow! Even if it was delayed - does that mean that the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project</color>]]> is now functional?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>YARROW: An update: my disappointment has turned to exasperation.. It appears the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project</color>]]> is still inactive - it was only a safeguard that triggered the memory statue to pair with me.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>OENO: To have our hopes raised by a safeguard, after all the work we put into safeguarding the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project..</color>]]> How darkly ironic, Yarrow!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<ShipLogConditions>

		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SY EX4</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SY EX5</FactID>
			<Condition>7</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	</ShipLogConditions>


</NomaiObject>