<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		DAZ: Friends, who is the one who has illustrated this gorgeous mural of a jellyfish? I must offer my appreciation for this piece of work!
		DAZ: Friends, who is the one who has illustrated this gorgeous mural of a jellyfish? I must offer my appreciation for this piece of work!
		CAS: I am humbled to hear your praise, my friend... Oh, no.
		CAS: The waves have washed away the lower part of the mural yet again!
		CAS: I have already touched up this mural several times.. How frustrating.. Why are the waves on this planet so turbulent?!
		DAZ: Perhaps you should have the work moved to a safer place, my friend.. May I suggest..
		MIT: Friends, a cyclone is fast approaching this island!
		CAS: I have prepared gravity crystals in the cove nearby to keep us anchored to the ground. Let us seek shelter within the cove before we continue this conversation!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: It is my pleasure, love. This invention will be truly incredible: I cannot wait to see you walking beyond the projection pool!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		DAZ: Now, for the moment of truth... It is time to revolutionize projection technology!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Daz? Did something happen? Your voyager has just disappeared..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Daz, do you still read me? Daz..?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Cove R3</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Cove R4</FactID>
			<Condition>2</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>