<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		YARROW: Cassava: The <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project</color>]]> will soon be launched! Are you ready to launch the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Deep Storm Station</color>]]> ahead of us?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: I am ready, Yarrow. A memory statue aboard the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Deep Storm Station</color>]]> has already been paired with me!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		YARROW: Wonderful! Using the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Deep Storm Station's</color>]]> secondary negative time interval, you should be able to see 6 seconds into the future after the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project</color>]]> is launched.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		YARROW: If all goes as planned, I should instantaneously receive memories from the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project,</color>]]> before sending you the order to shut off the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Deep Storm Station!</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Yarrow, is everything alright? You were to write to me with news of the outcome after launching the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project!</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: I experienced several intervals of the 6-second negative time interval, before shutting it off to write to the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project</color>]]> to learn if something had happened.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		YARROW: Cassava! I-I apologize. I lost track of time trying to learn what happened myself, after failing to receive any memories from 22 minutes into the future..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Oh, no... The only thing that could mean is that.. The <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project</color>]]> did not work.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>

		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>DSS R9</FactID>
			<Condition>8</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>DSS R10</FactID>
			<Condition>8</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>