<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: The Inspired has completed its orbit around the star system, collecting as much of the deadly matter as it is safely able to.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: I have programmed it to maintain a steady alignment within Giant's Deep's shadow, far from the sun, where it should be safe from crashing into any celestial body.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: When I give the order, the Inspired will warp all collected deadly matter to its sibling warp core here.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: The deep oceans surrounding the Deep Storm Station should serve to completely insulate and contain the deadly matter within this space.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: I have already delivered the remaining species within the Sanctuary back to the surface of Timber Hearth after ascertaining the relative safety of the planet.
</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: My dearest hope is that these species will be able to live on to explore and learn more from the universe.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: I only wish I could see all the amazing discoveries they might make.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: ...I am ready.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: In my final moments, I am filled with gratitude for all that I have been able to learn and experience...
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: The universe, filled with beauty, mysteries, and dangers - simply is, as it always has been...
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: I shall become one with it without fear.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>DSS EX4</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>DSS EX5</FactID>
			<Condition>3</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>DSS EX6</FactID>
			<Condition>11</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>INSP R4</FactID>
			<Condition>3</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>