<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		Assessing potential methods of containment or eradication of matter:
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		Solution 1: Contain the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Inspired</color>]]> and the deadly matter within Dark Bramble
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: This will without question, exterminate the anglerfish, as well as any undiscovered species dwelling within the bramble - should any even have survived the comet's arrival...
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
			CASSAVA: Additionally, the bramble produces seeds that connect back to its interior. Ghost matter could easily leak back into the star system through these seeds..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			Solution 2: Attempt to orbit the Inspired around the sun, allowing its gravity to siphon off the deadly matter gradually
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
			CASSAVA: This would be too dangerous. The pressures within Inspired will be too unstable at such close distance to the sun, and could cause far more devastating destruction...
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			Solution 3: Compact all matter within the Inspired, and launch it towards the source of the comet
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
			CASSAVA: There isn't enough time to refine any calculations to this theoretical source. The slightest error could destroy any neighboring star system and any possible life on them..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			Solution 4: Replace the Inspired's core with a black hole warp core, and warp all matter to its sibling core within the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Deep Storm Station</color>]]> for containment
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<Text>
			CASSAVA: The deep oceans surrounding the station should cause all captured matter to be completely enclosed within this space, safely containing it and allowing it to decay slowly.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<Text>
			CASSAVA: This is the safest and surest method of long-term containment, with the least potential for collective harm.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>12</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>11</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Our journey may have reached its end... But if it means the survival of these species.. I will gladly give my life to pave the road for theirs.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>CONV CONV6</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Stowaways DSS 5</FactID>
			<Condition>12</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>